♪ How about some pajeon by the stream?
[S.COUPS] [JEONGHAN] [JOSHUA]
♪ How about working out twice a day?
[JUN] [WONWOO] [HOSHI] [WOOZI]
♪ How about we fly in the sky?
[THE 8] [MINGYU] [DK]
♪ Or zone out into the fire while you lean on me?
[SEUNGKWAN] [VERNON] [DINO]
♪ In the SOOP
♪ SOOP du ru du du ru du
(Yes, let's go there)
[SEVENTEEN IN THE SOOP 2]
[The following content
includes ads and sponsorship]
♪ SEVENTEEN is In the SOOP
[SEVENTEEN IN THE SOOP 2]
[The following content
includes ads and sponsorship]
Drinking alone?
[The first night has fallen in darkness]
Let's drink together.
Okay.
[The first night has fallen in darkness]
If this consistent guy is the same at 50,
[So sentimental] [While drinking at the tavern]
then you'll be moved.
[Laughter begins after a serious conversation]
Should we grill meat right now?
[There's a rowdy BBQ party at the tarp!]
Rabbit! Don't run away and come here.
Hey! Can we not see you if you bend over?
[Just happy] [Caught (?) Rabbit Kwon
that was running away]
[So much laughter]
[Able to laugh because they're together]
[The happiest of times]
If you're struggling, you're struggling.
You can make it obvious.
Were you having a hard time?
[And we've become closer
with warm consolation toward each other]
♪ Two of us, lalala
[Ending the first night with karaoke until dawn]
[Day 2 in the forest has come]
[Starting with JEONGHAN's morning fishing]
[Splash]
I fell in!!
- Eat, VERNON! / - What are you doing?
[Each person wakes up in time to eat]
[JEONGHAN's dakgalbi (spicy braised chicken)]
[Breakfast is 4 times better together]
I'm full!
[Day 2 at "IN THE SOOP"]
[How will SEVENTEEN rest?]
Oh, should I do something?
Let's have a tea ceremony.
[Getting a camping cart filled
with preparations for the tea ceremony!]
[(+Tea kettle)]
And...
[(+Tea kettle)] [(+Water)]
- Come if you're going to do the tea
ceremony as well, VERNON! / - Yeah.
Where are we going to do it?
That side... Tea ceremony...
There's a tea ceremony room.
[Packing the materials for the tea ceremony]
Let's go! [Headed to the tavern
that has the tea ceremony room!]
Is this all we need?
- No, I need to go to my room now...
- This and...
THE 8's hard work!
- Okay.
- The tea ceremony is below, right? / - Yes.
- Do you know how to get there?
- Yes.
Then I...
I'll bring the tea ceremony set.
[Tea leaves that he brought]
[Essential item for tea ceremonies!]
Just... THE 8! It's below this building.
[Tea leaves that he brought]
[Essential item for tea ceremonies!]
- Below this building... / - Isn't it below here?
[Tea leaves that he brought]
[Essential item for tea ceremonies!]
Yes, that's right.
- Do I go this way? / - This way.
[Let's meet at the tavern
after getting the tea leaves]
Be careful.
I feel like I'm experiencing the countryside.
[Glances]
JEONGHAN is going somewhere!
Going where?
I don't know. He's going somewhere with DK.
Are they going to the sauna?
- Welcome.
- Yes.
It looks like THE 8's house.
It sort of looks like you live alone in Jeju-do...
[Kekeke]
Oh my, customers came.
[Playing along]
I guess these are the chickens
that are here.
There are chickens?
Wow, there are chickens.
Are there chickens?
Wow, I've never seen chickens
like this up close!
[Nice to meet you, chickens!]
- They laid eggs. / - They laid them?
[Warm and fresh] [Eggs laid today]
Isn't it a little weird to eat those eggs?
- But all eggs are supposed to be like that! /
- That's true. [True]
We just wash and eat that!
No, chickens! Play freely!
[That's true ^.T]
We won't catch and eat you.
[The man only warm to his chickens...
Yoon Jeonghan]
In here...
Should we do it in here?
[Entering the tavern with old vibes!]
Yes, here.
SEUNGKWAN wrote "SEVENTEEN's IN THE SOOP".
[SEUNGKWAN's handwriting from last season]
That's right.
[The essence of a countryside vacation]
[The essence of a countryside vacation,
the tavern]
["IN THE SOOP" SEVENTEEN]
[Boo Seungkwan]
Over here...
["IN THE SOOP" SEVENTEEN]
[Boo Seungkwan]
It has vibes.
- It really does.
- It's so pretty!
- Hey, DK!
- Yes.
- Ddakji? / - Sounds good!
[Discovers ddakji ⤤]
Let's do it here.
[Tons of mood]
[Traditional games to bring back old memories!]
- Let's play with bare hands. / - Okay.
[Tons of mood]
[Traditional games to bring back old memories!]
The loser has to run to the house and come back.
[No reason] [Naturally, a penalty is suggested]
- Why are we doing something so tiring?
- That's right. That's tiring.
Are you going to do it?
Or...
[Tag the house and come back]
Catch a chicken?
[Tag the house and come back VS
touch the chicken]
Go inside the chicken coop briefly!
[Adding onto it]
In the chicken coop...
Pretend to be a chicken!
[Go in and]
In the chicken coop,
[Why is he enticed...]
- pretend to be a chicken. / - It's your style, right?
[Very satisfied❤]
- Hey, you do it as well, Minghao!
- Hey, you!
- Bring ddakji and come out. / - Come. Bring it.
[Tea ceremony teacher spontaneously joins]
Come here!
The loser has to go in the chicken coop
- and pretend to be a chicken.
- Pretend to be a chicken.
[(So excited)]
Here.
Since I'm with you,
[Tea ceremony mood]
[THE 8 wouldn't...]
things like come to mind more.
[Tea ceremony mood]
[THE 8 wouldn't... not participate!]
Yeah! It's nice.
[Tea ceremony mood]
[THE 8 wouldn't... not participate!]
How is this done?
[(He's also... SEVENTEEN)]
This ddakji...
This is the top.
And if this flips over, then you just lose.
We're all doing it left-handedly.
[- SEVENTEEN's Ddakji Rules ➊ -]
[Everyone is only using their left hands]
Huh?
[- SEVENTEEN's Ddakji Rules ➊ -]
[Everyone is only using their left hands]
Then how... Do the 3 of us hit whatever we want...
[Then how do we play with 3 people?]
Do we hit 2?
We'll hit 2.
Shouldn't it be done consecutively?
[Ddakji rules are being established again]
- Hitting 2... / - Yeah.
One.
[Ddakji rules are being established again]
One. Like this.
- Do we hit one at a time?
- Then let's say one person's flipped over.
Then you did one, right?
Then let's say the next one connected.
[Very serious]
Then what nobody could do...
If I do 2, that means I did the most.
Then...
Let's say there's only one chance.
[- SEVENTEEN's Ddaji Rules ➋ (by. JEONGHAN) -]
[Out of the 2, pick a person's ddakji to hit]
Let's pick 1 of the 2 and hit it.
[- SEVENTEEN's Ddaji Rules ➋ (by. JEONGHAN) -]
[Out of the 2, pick a person's ddakji to hit]
If I flip it over right away, you're out, right?
[Order of turns] [DK➔JEONGHAN➔THE 8]
I'm out.
I'm out right away.
[Take this!]
[JEONGHAN's ddakji ⤸]
You're good!
[JEONGHAN's ddakji ⤦]
It's the back.
[(Sneakily)]
- You can't move that! You can't!
- We can't move it?
Why are rules suddenly added?
[Outburst]
- Aren't you not supposed to move it?
- Then what if it falls off?
[Very strict traditional game]
- Huh? / - Let's say it fell.
- Then you're out!
[Very strict traditional game]
- Then it's out of bounds. / - Huh?
[Very immature]
It's out of bounds if it falls off?
[Relay of additional rules]
[Chaotic ddakji universe]
I don't know.
[Relay of additional rules]
[Chaotic ddakji universe]
I don't know what this is.
If it falls,
- let's put it in the middle.
- No, let's play a practice round.
[Then let's play a practice round!]
For now then...
There are no practice rounds!
- Let's play right away.
- Let's play a practice round!
[A spear and spear]
- He doesn't know. / - Right now, the back...
- Right away!
- No.
[Let's go for it]
[(Rolls...)]
It's out!
Let's put it in the middle.
Go ahead, Minghao!
[DK's targeted ddakji attack!]
Only me... Huh?
This flipped over.
[DK's targeted ddakji attack!]
[(Totally unwavered)]
Why does it keep flipping over?
[One round ended with no gain]
It's very dangerous.
My left hand has no accuracy at all!
[(Lame attempt)]
It's really hard with the left hand!!
[All 3 of them have
the same levels of skill kekekeke]
Hey! Minghao.
No, I'm on the bottom.
[Friendly ddakji cake (?)]
What is this? Right now, we're...
- Are we topping a cake? / - Okay.
[Friendly ddakji cake (?)]
- I'm going!
- Let's go!
Let's go!
[Several rounds continue]
[Several rounds continue and continue...]
A long time ago... You know, right?
But how does it go under?
[Several rounds continue and continue...]
- Yeah!
- On top...
I'll just move past it.
[DK's turn has come back]
Nice!
[(JEONGHAN's ddakji)]
[(Understanding what happened...)]
Oh, it's me?
Become a chicken now.
- You said we should play a practice game earlier.
- What are you talking about?
[Belated regret]
[The ddakji game has already begun]
- Let's go. / - But can I go?
[Belated regret]
[The ddakji game has already begun]
- You'll go in the chicken coop and
become a chicken. / - Chicken attacking...
- Me?
- Yes.
You said it was a good idea!
What if the chicken attacks me?
I don't know about that.
If you become a chicken,
the chickens might not attack you.
[Mistaking as the same breed]
[(Really)] [(If you)]
[Hahahahaha]
How many seconds does he have to stay?
"Cock-a-doodle-do!"
I just need to do this.
Go and cluck like this.
[Careful]
[(Locking up the door ⤤)]
[...cluck cluck!]
Say hello!
[Going backwards]
[(Who... who are you?;;;;;)]
It's a greeting!
[Stepping backwards]
[(Who... who are you?;;;;;)]
Try touching it.
Hi, chicken.
[❤]
They're calm.
[(Flinch)]
[(Wants to pull a prank)]
[Acting not surprised ⤣]
Then say "cock-a-doodle-do" and come out.
[End of the penalty] [You should]
Cock-a-doodle-do!
Let's go!
[?] [Cock-a-doodle-do!!]
What is that sound?
What are they doing?
They're having the 4th round there.
[Kekeke]
I'm done! Let's eat ramyeon.
I'm starving.
Yesterday's alcohol...
[SEUNGKWAN and DINO head to
the food zone to relieve a hangover]
Why did I drink?
[SEUNGKWAN and DINO head to
the food zone to relieve a hangover]
It was seriously epic.
Let's eat ramyeon!
[JUN just woke up and joined]
What kind of ramyeon are you going to eat?
But should we eat a bit of protein as well?
Bul*ak Ramen.
[(Protein...?)]
Sort of...
Protein?
[JUN opens the refrigerator first
while SEUNGKWAN and DINO are thinking]
Should we add strip loin to Cha*guri?
[JUN opens the refrigerator first
while SEUNGKWAN and DINO are thinking]
- Totally beef... / - Aren't you craving soup?
[(Thinking)]
[Picking ingredients with no hesitation]
- Soup? / - Yes.
[(Thinking)]
[Picking ingredients with no hesitation]
- Or... / - Let's eat soup.
[(A bunch)]
- Or fried dumplings... Let's add
some dumplings and cook it. / - Should we?
[(A bunch)]
What are you going to cook and eat?
I'm going to eat different ramyeon.
You're going to cook something separately?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Mine might not be what you want.
[Courtesy]
[Meanwhile, SEUNGKWAN is torn]
[(Kimchi ramyeon)] [(Thin ramyeon)]
[(Spicy ramyeon)]
[A snack shelf that tempts with
all sorts of ramyeon]
[(Nervous Bboo)]
Hey! *in Ramen, *eoguri, or *hin Ramyun.
That menu makes me very torn.
Or eat this.
[Then cup ramyeon? ⤸]
[Nope.]
- Why? / - It's too...
Coming all the way here and eating cup ramyeon...
[Shakes head]
What's the difference between coming all
the way here and having cup ramyeon
or regular ramyeon? [Kekeke]
[Warm]
We have to cook it!
[As SEUNGKWAN and DINO
are carefully deciding on the ramyeon]
[He picks the pot first and
starts cooking "JUN Ramyeon"]
[Ramyeon with fried tofu in it? ⤦]
[Carefully adds the noodles]
[And SEUNGKWAN and DINO are still thinking]
Should we cook 3 packs of *eoguri?
- 3 for you?
- Yes.
[Finally, SEUNGKWAN and DINO
start cooking the ramyeon]
[Boiling]
This is...
What ramyeon is it?
Sort of... like coconut curry?
- Coconut curry?
- Yes.
Tom yum goong?
It's different from tom yum goong.
It's like curry.
That's interesting.
[After adding the magical soup powder]
It smells like...
- It really smells like coconut!
- Yes.
It's a very interesting smell.
[In "JUN Ramyeon", which smells like coconut]
[In "JUN Ramyeon", which smells like coconut,
3 packages of *eoguri are added]
As long as there's oil...
[Adding beef loins to boiling ramyeon]
It's fine.
- Let's put in just a bit more.
- Okay.
[(Also adding cheongyang pepper~)]
Is it cheongyang pepper?
Yes.
Should I add chili powder?
Yeah, I think it needs to be added.
Okay.
I think it'll be good.
[SEUNGKWAN and DINO's beef loin ramyeon,
who know good food]
[As well as coconut ramyeon from JUN,
whose cooking is always trustworthy, are done!]
[Their individual tastes are]
[Their individual tastes are
in their hangover dishes that they finished!]
- Hurry up and try it!
- I'll enjoy the food!
Hurry up and try it!
[Steaming]
[Blowing the well-cooked ramyeon]
How is it?
[Yes~!❤]
Is it good?
It's so good.
I'll enjoy it.
[Wow-!]
It's good.
Success!
I think it'd be really good
if we added something like bean sprouts!
- But it's really refreshing.
- Yes.
[Noodle slurping that makes us
want to boil water right away]
1 package of ramyeon...
- 2 of *eoguri and 1 of *hin is good.
- 2 of *eoguri and 1 of *hin?
How is it?
Is it good?
Yes.
[❤]
A lone wolf style.
Can I try the tom yum goong ramyeon?
Tom yum goong.
It's not tom yum goong.
Coconut?
It's the color of tom yum goong.
- It's tom yum goong! / - It's tom yum goong?
[Certain] [Kekekekeke]
Try it! Try it, SEUNGKWAN!
Coconut ramyeon.
Yes, thank you (in Thai).
It's thank you (in Thai).
This is Singapore.
[Can't deny the strong taste of herbs]
Singapore... So...
Tom yum goong?
[They relieve their hangovers
according to their own tastes]
Oh, I'm full...
[JUN carries the pot and leaves first]
[Unspoken fight begins...]
Seriously...
[(My goodness, this guy!)]
- Well...
- You should wash the dishes!!
What game do you want to play?
[(Thinks)]
Cham-cham-cham?
Left, right, and staying still.
[With only these 3]
Let's decide who will go first.
[Rock-paper-scissors to decide who will go first]
This is to go first.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[DINO will go first]
[(Oh man)]
This is just doing dishes.
It's cleaning everything!
- Let's just make it doing dishes.
- We just... just get up!
- Let's clean together. / - No, cleaning everything.
[Why~]
What's so hard about cleaning this up?
[Why~ Let's clean together~]
Okay. You said it.
What's so hard about cleaning this up?
Okay. You said it!
[...]
Meanwhile, I'm already finishing the dishes!
I'm doing everything at once.
[Meanwhile, he's doing all the dishes!]
Hold on. Okay.
[Attention X] [Regardless, very serious]
It's left, right, and staying still.
Left, right, and staying still. Okay.
[Attention X] [Regardless, very serious]
Cham-cham-cham!
Nice!
[SEUNGKWAN's defense succeeded]
[(Gulp)]
Cham-cham-cham!
[(Sneak)]
This...
- It was so... / - I saw!
[A bet doing dishes that's sensitive to offbeats]
You went like this!
You saw!
You also...
- You know you're about .005 second
slow right now, right? / - I also... Okay.
[A competitive .005 second shoot-out]
- Let's do it right away. Cham-cham!
- Let's do it at once.
[One more time]
[Determining the winner with standard rules]
We have to go on "cham!" Okay?
[One more time]
[Determining the winner with standard rules]
Let's play the standard way.
[One more time]
[Determining the winner with standard rules]
Start!
- Cham-cham-cham!
- Okay!
You're good!
Cham-cham...
Cham!
[(It's a fake)]
Cham-cham-cham!
[The winner isn't being determined easily]
Hurry up and do it!
Cham-cham-cham!
[Giggles]
It hurts.
Hold on.
[(How long is this going to last...)]
I bumped into this!
Cham-cham-cham!
[Randomly changing the target]
You do it!
[(Meanwhile, he got caught)]
[(?)]
[(These punks...!)]
[This_is_the_final_final_game.txt]
- Is it me? / - It's my turn.
It's funny.
[Nervous]
Cham-cham-cham!
[(Congrats) SEUNGKWAN is chosen
for cleaning up + doing dishes]
I enjoyed the food!
That's why I said
we should clean together!
[EP.3 Faces that are non-frowning shine most]
You're going clean up with me?
Regret your past self and work hard on cleaning!
[EP.3 Faces that are non-frowning shine most]
I'm starting the day with bad luck
and it's nice!
Fighting!
[Sigh...]
I don't even want to look at you, so leave!
[????]
Leave!
Are you doing dishes?
[(DINO)]
That's why I told you, right? Huh!
Wear gloves!
[(Closing)]
I'll do it on my own!!
Try to use warm water!
[The winner's warmth]
My goodness.
[Annoyed]
Hold on. I take a long time to do dishes.
[BGM is essential for dishes that will take long]
But still...
I should do it with the right mood.
[❤]
[Looking (at the pot)]
[Going back to before playing Cham-cham-cham]
♪ It's not that I like you
♪ It's not that I love you
♪ I'm trying to trick myself
[I love doing dishes ❤]
[With the hangover ramyeon,]
[With the hangover ramyeon, SEUNGKWAN is
more at peace while doing dishes sentimentally]
[Shaking off]
[Whoa~~~]
[Even cleaning up the utensils neatly]
[(Crash)]
[Scissors disappeared into the stove ⤣]
[※ Not frozen ※]
How annoying.
[(This isn't how it should go...)]
Scissors!
[Anxiously]
[(Is it hot...?)]
What did I do wrong? Seriously!
Seriously!
I finished washing my hands!!!
[Saves the scissors with
the sound of his heart (?)]
[(Scrubbing hard)]
[The start of SEUNGKWAN's day
has mood, but no luck (?)]
[Taking the clean pair of scissors]
[And putting it in a deep and safe place... ★]
Done!
[Finishing in a refreshed way!] [❤]
I should drink coffee.
[(Confused)]
[First, turning the coffee machine ON]
[(Rebellious fingers)]
[Doesn't know how to use the machine ⤸]
[Pressing all sorts of buttons]
[(I want to drink coffee...)]
It's okay! I can drink this!
[Stick coffee]
[(Embarrassed)]
If people can't use machines...
[Blaming himself]
Coffee pots are also machines!
[Quickly changes]
I have to decrease my caffeine intake.
[Back and forth]
[What's important is
the unwavering heart towards coffee... ❤]
[(Shaking off the water?)]
Why am I shaking off water when
I'm going to put water in again?
[2nd time going back and forth]
Am I stupid?
[Boiling water goes well]
Are there no big cups?
This sort of isn't enough.
[The size]
Venti size!
[Picks the 2 biggest looking cups]
[Filling 1 cup with water first]
[Pours it into another cup to compare the size]
[Comparing in a pretty scientific (?) way]
[His final choice is the wine glass,
which is the biggest one!]
[Taking out ice for an iced americano]
[(Then a lot of ice...]
[(Then a lot of ice... spills out)]
[Frustrated + angry dandelion spore]
How annoying!
There's something on the ice, too!
There's no mood to it!
I'm starting today with no luck and it's nice!
[Today is SEUNGKWAN's lucky (?) day]
It's okay, SEUNGKWAN.
[(Self comforting)]
Isn't this what life is like?
Why is it falling out when I grabbed it like this?
How ridiculous.
[Although angered, he cleans up after
the ridiculous (?) situation]
How annoying.
It's okay, SEUNGKWAN. You did a good job.
[Tries to gather his composure]
[Stick coffee ⤸]
This isn't how you're supposed to do it.
I have to melt it first.
[The order came to mind
as he poured the powdered coffee...]
I'm seriously losing it.
What is this...
[Ah...] [Ha]
[Coffee flakes are sprinkled on the ice]
But this...
I have to melt it in.
[An innovative coffee making method]
[This is a "hot iced americano"]
[(Resuscitating the coffee)]
[Fortunately, the warm iced americano
looks pretty decent]
Oh, nice!
[❤]
Okay, I'm done now!
Mood!
Consider the mood!
[(Consider the coffee flake mood... ★☆)]
Consider the mood! The mood!
[A sip of mood in the sunlight]
This is insane.
[(With his leg)]
Wow!
[His sad history is automatically
deleted with a cup of coffee]
[And the brief encounter with
the forest landscape]
Wow! Why is the sky so beautiful?
[Had to come to the forest
to experience the beautiful autumn sky]
[In this moment, it's completely TIME OFF]
[SEUNGKWAN's emotional PLAYLIST]
[♬ "I got lucky" - SEUNGKWAN]
[(Original by: Kwon Jin Ah,
Lyrics by: Kwon Jin Ah, Song by: Kwon Jin Ah)]
♪ I was left with no trivial regrets or
♪ anything lingering
♪ I got lucky
♪ Because I had someone in my life
♪ who I loved more than myself
I'll take a walk.
It's really beautiful!
It's so insane.
[Saving the pretty scenery]
[Saving the pretty scenery
that only brings awe_★]
Hi, VERNON!
[(VERNON is here)]
[(Waves)] [VERNON is here)]
[(VERNON's mobile world)]
He's listening to music again, right?
[Knows VERNON well]
Hi, VERNON!
[(Monologue greeting)]
Hi, VERNON...
[Sad]
[The gentle breeze and]
[The gentle breeze and warm sunlight]
[As it fills the forest,
the afternoon of day 2 begins]
[Meanwhile, what about the other members?]
[Sleep zone]
[(Rolls around)]
[Enjoying sleeping in for the first time in a while]
[The sun has risen,
but SEVENTEEN is in the middle of the night]
[JUN ended his meal and
entered the playground again today]
[Where is JUN headed to right away?]
[In front of the canvas!]
[Gets the paint and brush right away]
[Even grabbing the canvas]
Let's go forward a little.
[A conversation with the sofa]
[Even secures a spot to paint]
[Ready to paint]
[1. Squeeze paint on the palette]
[2. Spread the paint with the brush]
[Ruthlessly begins brushing!]
[Afterwards, JUN was silently
absorbed in painting for a while]
[What painting will JUN complete?]
[While JUN is really into painting]
[In the tavern]
[THE 8 is preparing the tea ceremony]
You're here?
Boil the tea!
[Starting to prepare for the tea ceremony]
[Tavern] [THE 8's tea ceremony time
- with. JEONGHAN, DK -]
I think I sang too much yesterday.
My throat hurts so much.
I woke up in the morning
and it felt like there was a thorn in my throat.
[THE 8 silently prepares well on his own]
At the end of waiting,
is there beauty?
[(Nods)]
Gimme!
[While feeling the beauty of waiting...]
Your posture is nice.
I should sit up straight.
[(Tea ceremony mode ON)]
Don't the bad things leave?
Energy...
Good energy will come to you.
- Hold on. Let's have a time of meditation.
- Okay.
- Tell me how to meditate.
- How to meditate.
Sit down first.
Is there no meditation BGM?
Already, the sound of nature outside right now...
[Natural sound]
[Sound of nature is enough for BGM...]
- It's a natural sound. / - It's meditation sound.
- That's right. A natural sound.
[Sound of nature is enough for BGM...]
And just the back...
- We have to straighten our backs?
- You just need to straighten your spine.
[- THE 8's tea ceremony posture lecture 1 -]
[☑ Please straighten your spine]
Just the spine... Just straighten your spine.
[- THE 8's tea ceremony posture lecture 1 -]
[☑ Please straighten your spine]
And leave your hands comfortably.
[- THE 8's tea ceremony posture lecture 1 -]
[☑ Place both hands on your knees comfortably]
Just feeling your breath.
[- THE 8's tea ceremony posture lecture 1 -]
[☑ Feel your breath comfortably]
Deeply...
[- THE 8's tea ceremony posture lecture 1 -]
[☑ Feel your breath comfortably]
Exhale and inhale.
We'll do it until
the water boils.
[(Meditate)]
[~ Time of meditation ~]
Doesn't it smell like something is burning?
[(Peeks)]
[Can't resist being curious...]
[(Takes care of his curiosity
and focuses again)]
[With the sound of nature]
[With the sound of nature,
they focus on the sound of their own breath]
[The 3 people try to empty their
thoughts and feelings]
[(Peeks)]
[Maximum focus ⤣]
[(Rolls eyes this way)]
[(Rolls eyes this way) (Rolls eyes that way)]
[Getting fidgety ⤤]
[Boiling]
[THE 8 checks the tea kettle
with boiling water]
[(Taps)]
[THE 8 checks the tea kettle
with boiling water]
[(Okay)] [(I guess meditation has ended)]
I feel purified.
- Really?
- Yes.
Really?
Yes.
Great! It's a really good thing that you feel
refreshed even in a short amount of time.
Really.
Then that means you trained longer than I did.
[Kekeke]
I'm originally fast at accepting things.
The toxins in my body left.
[SO refreshing]
That means you have a clean soul.
- Clean soul.
- Yes, a clean soul.
What tea do you want to drink?
[What's the first tea that Mr. Tea Time will brew?]
[Tea]
Something without caffeine.
[What's the first tea that Mr. Tea Time will brew?]
[Tea]
Something without caffeine?
Then this.
[Pu'er "fer" tea that's low in caffeine]
What is this?
This is pu'er "fer" tea.
[Pu'er "fer" tea that's low in caffeine]
It's my favorite.
Pu'er...
It's just pu'er tea.
I like pu'er tea!
Pu'er tea removes oils.
[Knowledgeable] [(In the body)]
That's right.
- All teas do that.
- It's fermented pu'er tea.
[Pu'er "fer" tea]
[This pu'er tea is made by
the wòduī fermentation process]
[THE 8 is familiar with brewing tea]
Be careful. It's really hot.
[In this moment, even this time
of waiting isn't tedious]
Pu'er "fer" tea.
[Enjoying my hobby with the members today]
Hold on.
Pu'er "fer"...
- Are you going to throw it away once?
- Yes.
[Tea washing / tea soaking] [With the process of
bringing out the scent and taste of tea leaves,
hot water is poured over them in tea sets
and the first pot of water is thrown out]
Okay.
Nice!
[Tea that's been brewed with lots of hard work]
[Tea]
[(Stretching)]
What is this?
Is this stretching?
It's stretching that removes bad air.
It removes bad air and not bad energy?
It removes air.
[(Removing air is the point ^^)]
If bad air goes in,
- my daily life is hard. / - That's right.
[(Removing air is the point ^^)]
- Air is also important.
- This is a bit different from meditation.
This is just my own thing.
[DK's air training method that's
different from meditation]
Meditation is usually what you make yours.
[~ Removing bad air ~]
Then the bad air...
He's working hard, right?
[DK feels awkward] [...Heh]
It's really nice here.
[(Tavern)]
- I think it's really nice.
- It's really nice here.
I want to lie on that and take a nap.
There are even clothes here.
[On the big wooden floors of the tavern
that are perfect for taking naps]
- Let's sleep here if we get sleepy later. / - Okay.
[On the big wooden floors of the tavern
that are perfect for taking naps]
- Clothes here... / - There are also clothes?
[Wooden pillow, daily hanbok, and elastic pants]
[There are tavern kits
for the countryside vacation]
- Like hanboks? / - Yes.
[Wooden pillow, daily hanbok, and elastic pants]
[There are tavern kits
for the countryside vacation]
We're not supposed to do cheers.
[Flinches] [Hawk eye]
I wasn't going to do cheers.
Your hand was out...
[(You did it)] [Kekeke]
It's a habit...
[^^]
[(Tries to hold in laughter)]
It's good.
[The 3 slowly savor the tea]
Oh, it's nice!
Oh, it's really nice.
I really wish I had time like this everyday.
I think it'd be nice to have an hour
like this regardless of how busy we are.
But when we're very busy
because of a lot of schedules,
[DK's curiosity out of the blue]
you have time to do it,
[(The tea ceremony)]
but sometimes, you're too lazy to do it
because you're too sleepy. Do you still do it then?
I have to sleep.
- Your body is tired.
- So you can't do it.
But... if my body is alright
[THE 8's honest thoughts on tea ceremonies]
and I'm not crazy tired, then I try to.
[(Tea ceremonies somehow)]
- You do?
- Then it'd bring more healing.
But if you have to sleep, then you sleep?
If my body is saying, "This isn't okay" and
[THE 8's tea ceremony philosophy
is very set based on his own standards]
- "I can't do my schedules then", then I sleep.
- Of course.
[THE 8's tea ceremony philosophy
is very set based on his own standards]
I have to sleep.
But if I do this when I'm that busy,
[But the reason he still tries to do
tea ceremonies in the midst of busyness]
your mind clears up.
[But the reason he still tries to do
tea ceremonies in the midst of busyness]
Even if it's brief, "Yes, my work..."
"I need to work hard." This sort of...
[It becomes a small motivation for life]
- So you can do it... That's right.
- It gives me more strength.
[It becomes a small motivation for life]
Doing this in the forest and in a room
[(The tea ceremony)]
is completely different, right?
[Very]
It's different.
This is the best.
[(Doing it in the forest)]
It can only be felt at "IN THE SOOP".
Minghao's tea ceremony.
[Can only be felt at "IN THE SOOP"]
[(I ❤ tea ceremony)]
[(Dazed...)]
[Eyes are losing focus]
I should sleep.
- Go in and sleep.
- I should sleep here.
[Drinking the remaining tea
before taking a nap] [Tea]
But it makes sense we're sleepy.
[Drinking the remaining tea
before taking a nap] [Tea]
It's right when we should be sleepy.
- After eating and drinking something warm.
- He didn't sleep well.
[JEONGHAN moves
to the wooden floors to take a nap]
Sleep well!
[JEONGHAN moves
to the wooden floors to take a nap]
Are you going to sleep with that wooden pillow?
Yes.
[Wooden pillow is ready ⤤]
- What is this? / - Aren't those the pants?
Wow! I like pants like these.
I feel like I'm at esthetic (skin care clinic).
It's pretty much...
What did you eat, JEONGHAN?
[Scenario ON]
That's right.
[Getting into character as
the skin care clinic specialist ⤹]
- Here...
- You have to put a pack (face mask) on him.
It's really...
Even the music.
[Esthetic]
[Ending with THE 8's aegyo ❤]
[And the honest talk that the mood created]
To me,
it was a very big point in my life.
[THE 8 encountered the turning point
of his life not too long ago]
This time around,
although it's what I like,
[(This work)]
my emotional ability to keep liking
those things gradually decreased.
[Maintaining that]
Gradually, I can't follow those emotions.
["My emotions can't follow my emotions"]
- That becomes shorter.
- It gets very short.
That this was something very precious to me
and my members, company, and fans...
[CARAT]
I thought about those precious
people once more.
[From a certain point, he started thinking
of those precious people more]
I think those thoughts are good.
- But it was a time that made me realize that
once more. / - It became that for you this time.
[(Not too long ago)]
That's right. We're people, so we always...
[In some ways, it's the process
of becoming better people]
And these day, even happiness itself...
I'm trying to not look for
stimulating sources of happiness.
If I only look for that?
There's no end to it.
You have to find something
that's more stimulating.
- If you get a taste of something
that's stimulating once... / - But that...
But how much of that would exist?
[These days, he's been focusing on
the daily life more that stimulating things]
So these days, I'm bored. It could be boring.
[These days, he's been focusing on
the daily life more that stimulating things]
I really like it even when
I'm not doing anything now.
[THE 8 likes being satisfied with
the happiness of daily life]
- Anyway, I really like that
you're doing so well right now. / - Really.
But I think that's inevitable in life.
It's a nice time right now.
So my meditation teacher
said something like that.
He said that truth doesn't change.
But until we find truth,
our thoughts keep changing.
But how it changes...
You thought this way at this time,
but after a situation or incident,
[When you decide something
that was once certain is wrong]
your thought becomes wrong.
[When you decide something
that was once certain is wrong]
You grow more and more and in life,
[Not failure or despair, but growth]
your thought
is wrong again.
Supposedly, we keep looking
until we reach this truth.
[Various thoughts are in some ways
a process of finding truth]
So older people have their own thing, right?
- Yes, that's a possibility. / - I might think
"What an oldie" when I hear that when I'm young.
[I thought that]
Their thoughts too much... I don't live that way.
[Understanding now] [Life's know-hows
coming from the experience of adults]
But from living,
[Understanding now] [Life's know-hows
coming from the experience of adults]
the majority all think that way a lot.
[Everything comes from life experience]
We're all the same and those people...
[The realizations after time]
- Yes, they experience it.
- Because they lived life, they experienced it.
[The realizations after time]
- That's why nothing adults say is wrong.
- You have to listen.
At this age now?
I listen to what my mom and dad say.
- We didn't at all long ago.
- Long ago, not at all.
Rather than not listening at all,
I thought, "What changed?"
[When he was young,
he couldn't understand his parents]
- I couldn't feel or accept it. / - You can't accept it.
[When he was young,
he couldn't understand his parents]
I just thought, "No. This is wrong for me."
[THE 8 was stuck in his own thoughts
and just denied them]
But now,
I say, "What do you think, mom?"
Then she tells me.
[Now, he gets help from his parents'
thoughts and experiences]
Since they also experienced things like this,
[Now, he gets help from his parents'
thoughts and experiences]
they could think this way!
I know that and go my way.
What do you ask your parents?
- Just... relationships.
- Sort of... like relationships.
So these days, I practice things like that.
- What?
- Practicing how to be more thankful.
How it's done is...
It's sort of like praying.
I just close my eyes and do this.
[(With his hands together)]
I...
I'm thankful that I'm even
able to have this nice time at "IN THE SOOP".
I'm so thankful for DK, who has this time
to converse and be here with me.
["I'm thankful I can converse with DK"]
Just...
If you have this gratitude,
[If you start (once)]
the small to big things keep coming to mind.
[(Gratitude does)]
- I keep saying it until I can't think
of any more. / - That's good.
[Endless gratitude for the big and small things]
I'm thankful, I'm thankful.
Then there's nothing.
- Then if you open your eyes... / - Then it's a little...
[At the end of your thoughts]
"I'm living very well!"
The world also looks very good.
- If you look, there's a lot to be thankful for.
- It's really...
It's really interesting that even a moment of
someone passing by and smiling comes to mind.
- You don't even know who it is.
- Even the small things.
But you're even thankful for that.
[(You have that feeling)]
Then they keep coming to mind.
Minghao is a thankful person.
[Has he become the icon of gratitude?!]
I'm thankful that I'm even drinking with you.
[(The tea)]
What are you going to do after drinking this?
What should we do?
Should we take a nap?
You're not sleepy, right?
I slept so much.
Supposedly, we can ride
- ATVs toward the observatory.
Let's go. / - Let's go.
[Sudden genre change from
tea ceremonies to ATVs kekeke]
- Let's go! / - Hurry up and drink.
[Sudden genre change from
tea ceremonies to ATVs kekeke]
You're not going to drink it?
I'm not going to drink it.
- ATVs even made us stop the tea ceremony.
- Of course.
[ATVs even make Mr. Tea Time stop...]
I still prefer stimulating things like this.
[Stimulating things are needed at times - THE 8 -]
- How people think...
- You're not going with what's smooth?
Those are the ideal thoughts...
[(Very quick to justify with reality)]
This is reality.
Stimulating ATVs.
We have to live in a stimulating way!
We're young! [(?)]
It seems like everything
we said up until now
all became nothing.
[Kekeke]
No, this is just how it is.
[Emphasizing again]
[Life is about looking for truth...]
It's about time everyone wakes up.
They probably woke up, right?
[After the tea ceremony,
THE 8 and DK leaves the tavern]
[Doesn't know the members left]
[Doesn't know the member left
and JEONGHAN is fast asleep]
[As DK said, are the other members awake?]
- I feel like I'm going to die? / - Why?
[Someone suffering because of a hangover...]
Because I drank too much yesterday.
A common hangover of an idol.
A common hangover relief of an idol.
Thank you!
[MINGYU shares a pear drink
that helps with hangover relief]
You drank fast and a lot.
[(Yesterday)]
That's right...
I'll drink 2 more glasses.
Let's have 1 last drink.
[Drunk on the mood,
JOSHUA kept going as if there was no tomorrow]
S.COUPS! Love shot!
[Drunk on the mood,
JOSHUA kept going as if there was no tomorrow]
Cheers!
[Drunk on the mood,
JOSHUA kept going as if there was no tomorrow]
[(Today, JOSHUA regrets yesterday)]
JOSHUA. Should I make you
ramyeon for your hangover?
Should I make you ramyeon?
[(Passionately)] [(Nodding)]
I'll cook you a pack of ramyeon.
[Poor guy... I have to save (?) him]
- I feel so bad for you. / - Thanks.
He wants to be saved.
- Save me. / - Right now?
[(Please save me...)]
I woke up in the morning and here,
he took this and this.
[(Please save me...)]
[Remnants of his efforts to relieve his hangover ⤺]
He said, "Save me."
[Strategy (?) to save JOSHUA]
[MINGYU's hangover ramyeon, GO GO!]
[Drizzle a circle of oil on the pan]
[Slicing green onion~]
[Slicing green onion~
Add it to the pan and stir fry]
Good morning.
[Wakes up in the meantime]
[WONWOO joins in the food zone as well]
[In front of the stovetop as if
he's entranced by the smell of ramyeon ⤣]
Are you going to cook ramyeon, MINGYU?
Do you want me to cook it for you?
Yes, together... Then let's eat ramyeon together.
[- Adding a customer to MINGYU's ramyeon shop -]
[Adding a spoonful of garlic and stir frying]
It looks good.
It even smells good.
[Although I'm making it] [❤]
Make green onion oil add the soup powder.
[Not forgetting to add the powder & flakes
to the green onion oil]
There's no way this would taste bad.
[Adding a satisfying fiery taste]
Please pour water in here.
Bring it to a boil.
[(+Kelp)] [Waiting until water with
the stir fried ingredients boils]
What should I eat?
Are you not eating, MINGYU?
[???]
Me?
I'm not going to eat in the morning
so I can eat at night.
[MINGYU was shocked by
his own overeating the day before]
That's amazing...
[(The smell)]
[(Surprised)]
DINO! You woke up?
[All washed up DINO has entered
the food zone again]
What time did you wake up?
[All washed up DINO has entered
the food zone again]
Did you eat?
Yes, I ate.
I have to work out a little later.
[~A common morning conversation
between athletes (?)~]
I'm going to do some cardio right now.
I have to relieve the swelling.
It's really bad right now.
[MINGYU's leftover ramyeon
is starting to boil]
[Plates the noodles briefly]
[After adding cheongyang peppers
and eggs in the ramyeon soup,]
[It's finished once the plated noodles are added!]
[(Should I eat it?)]
[(Should I eat it?) (Should I not?)]
I cooked it so well...
Oh no...
I'll enjoy it, MINGYU. Thank you.
I'll enjoy it.
[How will MINGYU's hangover ramyeon taste?!]
Should I try it?
- It's so good! / - You're amazing at
cooking ramyeon, MINGYU!
[MINGYU's ramyeon brings awe
as soon as it enters the mouth]
It's really insane.
I eat MINGYU's ramyeon
in the dorms often, right?
- You realize it every time?
- When it comes to ramyeon, it's really...
- MINGYU is the best at it?
- Yes.
Compliments would even
make a whale cook ramyeon.
[Compliments even make MINGYU cook ramyeon]
My eyes were so swollen in the morning
that I was surprised. Really!
Is that why you're wearing sunglasses?
[The hidden secret behind
the indoor sunglasses ⤸]
I can't take off the sunglasses.
[The hidden secret behind
the indoor sunglasses ⤸]
How swollen are they?
That's insane!
They're very swollen.
Really? Why don't I know?
There's no real difference.
[In WONWOO's eyes, he's just cute❤]
No, there's no big difference.
You're the same in my eyes.
[The guys are enjoying the ramyeon]
[The guys are enjoying the ramyeon
and MINGYU looks at them]
[Thinks about something
for a long time through the sunglasses]
[(Swallows)]
I need to do cardio.
[(Swallows)] [(In order to remove swelling)]
It's really insane.
[Blitzes]
[Can't resist this ramyeon]
It's so good.
[Scoops a spoonful of egg
and takes a bite right away]
- You're the best. / - Seriously.
[Scoops a spoonful of egg
and takes a bite right away]
It's 3, but how do you cook it so well?
[(Slurps the soup as well)]
- It's amazing. / - Yeah.
Ah!
[@!!!]
[His awe comes from the bottom
of his stomach with a spoonful soup]
- It's this. / - 1 package of ramyeon
[His awe comes from the bottom
of his stomach with a spoonful soup]
is what I can cook
and make well.
[Chews] [Deep in a dilemma again...?]
Several packages of ramyeon are...
- There's soupless ramyeon, right?
- Should I eat, too?
[2nd blitz]
I don't think I should eat in the morning,
but what should I do?
Wow! I really need to stop eating.
No!
[Hands reaching for chopsticks
are faster than his mouth]
So what should we do?
Should we make rice as well, MINGYU?
[Hands reaching for chopsticks
are faster than his mouth]
Should we make rice as well?
[Should we not?]
Are we mixing in rice, too?
Then what?
Should we mix in rice, too?
This soup would be so good with rice!
- Right?
- The soup is really good.
[MINGYU, who said he wouldn't eat
because of the swelling...]
I'm a bit better after eating this.
[MINGYU, who said he wouldn't eat
because of the swelling...]
[Inhaling]
[Scraping off the plate as well]
It would be really good with rice mixed in.
[(I want to eat it mixed with rice)]
Let's mix in rice!
I'll microwave instant rice.
[(Natural toss)]
[Moves as if he'd been waiting kekeke]
Don't you think 1 is enough, MINGYU?
[Inhaling with no rest]
[Doing dishes right away to stop eating]
Let's mix in rice right away.
It's hot!
It would taste good with rice mixed in...
[Fixated]
WONWOO is so cute.
It's hot!
[Fixated]
The ramyeon was really good!
- It's insane.
Yes, seriously...
[Gets JOSHUA's spoon as if it's his]
It's hot!
It's been so long since I drank...
We have to go again today.
It's been a while since
I've been struck with reality.
Why are you struck with reality?
Is it because it's been so long
since we've had it?
[Takes a spoonful of rice after worrying ⤣]
But we have to have it when we're here!
Not on a regular basis.
[Takes a spoonful of rice after worrying ⤣]
But I did hold back so I could have it here.
Did you properly enjoy it yesterday?
[(Alcohol)]
Whew... I drank properly.
No, it sort of...
- That sort of... / - JOSHUA.
[MINGYU was about to drink a canned drink]
He drank as if it was his first time.
[Tons of empty cans]
I guess you're lacking
a lot of fluids, JOSHUA.
I...
This drink and... What is it?
[(Remnants of hangover relief)]
[Getting playful ⤥]
I drank these 2.
[(Remnants of hangover relief)]
[Getting playful ⤥]
I must be crazy.
[Shocked] [(Drink a can of beer ^^)]
What's wrong with him?
[Shocked]
- I still don't understand the notion of hangover
alcohol. / - You don't know the notion?
Hangover alcohol...
You don't know it now, right?
- Down this. / - No, seriously!
[The guys raise the youngest tough]
- I really can't! / - Then... "Oh?"
"Oh? It goes in."
You'll get this feeling.
But your rate of recovery is no joke either.
I'm not able to take off my sunglasses
right now because I'm swollen.
[(What are you talking about)]
Let us see.
Take them off for a second.
Yes, wear them.
- I was surprised, too.
- It's very bright here.
How swollen could you be...
Yes, wear them.
WONWOO said he doesn't know that difference.
- I don't know.
- Oh, yes.
- You're not that swollen. / - That's right.
[While DINO is teasing and encouraging MINGYU]
- Really? / - You're not that swollen.
- What are you saying?
[While DINO is teasing and encouraging MINGYU]
[What about the other members in the forest?]
[Whether it's resting alone]
[Or playing in dreamland still]
[Still in dreamland] [Tavern]
[Meanwhile, S.COUPS, who woke up,
is going to wash up]
[SEUNGKWAN, who drank coffee,
is busy organizing his luggage]
[JUN is working hard
to fill in the painting as well]
Yahoo!!!!
[Whose excited voice is
resonating in the forest now?]
[THE 8 is enjoying an ATV drive]
Hey, it's nice!
[THE 8 and DK is enjoying an ATV drive]
I didn't know there was a place like this!
It's nice!
It's really nice.
[THE 8 stirs up a sandstorm]
[THE 8 stirs up a sandstorm
and DK is watching]
Do it again!
[Taking out a camera he took himself]
- Come closer and do it. / - One more time?
[Reordering a sandstorm riding]
[Passionate photographer DK and model, THE 8]
[(How is it?)]
You look cool!
[Photo by. DK]
[Photo by. THE 8]
Do you want to go down now?
Let's go!
[Meanwhile, the members at the food zone]
Should we fly kites?
[After eating]
Do you want to fly kites?
[Planning to fly kites in the field to digest]
But would kites fly in this weather?
I feel like a bit of wind is blowing...
[(A bit of wind is blowing...)]
I'll be trying to fly a kite.
I'm curious whether it'll fly or not.
If you run, it'll fly, MINGYU.
[Quick execution skills]
[Runs over to the playground to get a kite]
Wen Junhui!
Yes!
[(Glances)]
- You're going to do that? Sounds fun.
- Yes.
It'll probably work well right now!
The winds are strong!
That's right! I'll try it!
I'm too lazy to wait.
[T T]
I have to wait until it dries.
That's right. Dry it well.
[Knows about painting well]
[Fidgets]
Got it!
DINO! I'll run and come back.
Yes! Go ahead.
[MINGYU runs]
[Running first]
[Unintentional cardio]
[The kite flies high and well]
- The kite is flying. / - Is it HOSHI?
[MINGYU]
- MINGYU.
- Is it MINGYU?
How cute.
[Hahaha]
The kid chasing a kite!
[MINGYU is serious about flying a kite]
DINO!
[Look at me]
You're incredible!
[DINO isn't here]
- Are you flying a kite?
- Yes!
You're flying it well!
[(Great weather for flying a kite.mov)]
Minghao! Did you not go?
[(ATV)]
We went!
Oh, that was quick.
30 minutes?
Around 20 minutes back and forth?
Is it nice?
It's really nice!
It's very much worth going.
Do you want to go, MINGYU?
Should we go?
[Enticed]
- Do you want to go right now?
- Yes.
[(Right now...?)]
[DK is sort of wanting to fly the kite]
Wow! It's flying far away!
[(I want to try it)]
It's flying so far!
Is MINGYU a kite flying expert?
[Proud]
[How are DK's kite flying skills?]
[The kite is flailing?!]
The kite is falling. Reel it in!
Reel it in!
[⤤ Kite expert's delicate touch]
It's fine! It's going up.
[MINGYU's coaching]
[The kite starts flying again]
Wow!
Wow! It's insane!
What was the children's song about kites?
[(Wants to sing a line after seeing a kite)]
[♬ "Flying a Kite" - SEUNGKWAN]
[(Lyrics by: Kwon Yeonsoon /
Song by: Han Soosung)]
[Today's conductor]
Maybe because SEUNGKWAN slept well,
but he seems very bright today.
Let's go in there.
He's happy after drinking yesterday.
[(Happy Bboo-estro)]
He feels so great right now!
He's so cute! Oh my!
[Kekeke]
He's so lovely.
[❤]
♪ Wagging the tail!
♪ Wind is blowing
♪ Boom boom dancing
Wow. I sang this easily
when I was in elementary school.
♪ Wind is blowing
[Experience winning all the children
singing competitions at one time]
♪ Wind is blowing
♪ Let's fly a kite
[The time when everyone
becomes happier with just one kite]
The kite is flying today.
[JOSHUA and WONWOO are
at the food zone after cleaning up]
It really is flying.
Yes, it's flying away.
It's very high up.
I'm happy! I definitely felt it yesterday.
Sleeping all together like this for the first
time in a while brings back old memories.
Do you not need to apply sunscreen, JEONGHAN?
[JEONGHAN and MINGYU
are getting ready to ride ATVs]
Should I apply sunscreen?
[JEONGHAN and MINGYU
are getting ready to ride ATVs]
Let's apply sunscreen.
[JEONGHAN and MINGYU
are getting ready to ride ATVs]
- Where is S.COUPS?
- I don't know.
I woke up and he was gone!
- Huh?
- Here he is.
- I washed up.
Really? You woke up early,
but why did you wash up now?
I kept sleeping.
What are you doing?
We're going to ride ATVs!
[(ATVs...? I'm hungry...)]
MINGYU! Did you eat?
Yes, I ate!
[(Yes)]
[(Who should I eat with)]
- Eat well and rest!
- Okay!
Do you know how to drive it?
Have you only driven once or twice?
I've never driven this before.
[(ATVs are a first)]
DK! How do I do this?
[Asking DK for help this time]
Turn the key!
[Only the lights ON]
- Is there no revving? / - There is!
If you turn the key.
It's this.
It's this for this.
[(???)]
This is different from the one I rode...
[Flustered]
You just turn on the engine.
How do you turn on the engine, MINGYU?
How you turn on the engine?
[The engine isn't turning on...?]
The engine isn't turning on.
Minghao!
[SOS to THE 8 this time]
Let's ask Minghao.
- I don't know how to do this.
- Me neither.
[Will anyone know
how to turn on the ATV engines?]
Minghao!
[Will anyone know
how to turn on the ATV engines?]
[⤣ THE 8]
[Minghao is picking a kite right now]
[Very serious]
[He's serious about picking a kite,
so there's no way he'd hear]
I know how to turn on that engine.
[When they're about to give up on the ATVs]
- Want me to show you?
- Yes.
Look!
[WONWOO enters like a savior!]
If you do this, it goes forward.
[WONWOO's help]
[The engine finally turn on]
- I don't need to touch
anything else, right? / - Yes.
[WONWOO's help]
[The engine finally turns on]
[It's moving]
That scared me.
[(Running)]
- DK!
- Thank you.
Get out of the way.
- What are you doing, Minghao?
- Get out of the way.
[Minghao wants to fly a kite...]
Get out of the way!
- Why?
- Get out of the way!
[(Sad kite)]
Why? It's not working!
[Upset]
How do you fly it, MINGYU?
- Protect it well!
- Okay.
Why doesn't this work?
Is it the other way?
Come here for a second.
[Really wants to do it] [He blocked their way
and asked for kite flying tips]
It's the other way, right?
[Really wants to do it] [He blocked their way
and asked for kite flying tips]
No, it's right.
[Really wants to do it] [He blocked their way
and asked for kite flying tips]
Run from over there.
[A quick kite flying lesson]
But it...
[A quick kite flying lesson = just run]
[(I'll just try running first~!)]
[The ATV finally leaves after
he shares kite flying tips!]
I'm going, MINGYU! Let's just go.
[The ATV finally leaves after
he shares kite flying tips!]
Let's go together!
[They excitedly enjoy the nature surrounded]
[They excitedly enjoy the nature surrounded
by the river and mountains on ATVs]
[The moment of enjoying true rest
in the open forest]
[(Heh heh)]
MINGYU!
I don't want to go anymore...
- Why?
- It's too bumpy.
That's why?
Can I go back?
What are you saying?
Follow me!
Go!
[As expected, sparta]
Hey!
[Leaving again]
[Really enjoying being off-road]
[Flailing]
MINGYU! Look at this!
[(Kekekekeke)]
[The most difficult uphill road begins]
[Wavering]
[Hahahahaha]
Hey!
- I don't want to go! / - Go!
[T T]
[Doesn't get through to him]
[Flat roads finally begin ⤤]
[How exciting]
♪ My life is a vacation.
[Becomes relaxed enough to sing]
[Following the forest roads thick with trees]
This is the end!
[It's the peak]
[A photo time on the peak]
Take one for me up front, too.
[(Click)] [(V)]
How do I look?
You look cool.
[#First_ATV]
[#Pretty_satisfied]
[#Refreshing_wind]
[#Totally_excited]
Let's go!
[Meanwhile, what about the other members?]
It's dying! Run!!!
[Running]
[THE 8 and DK aren't done
with flying kites]
[Running this way]
[Running this way and that way]
This isn't working!
[Why isn't it working T T T]
[(He's running hard keke)]
Why isn't it working?
[There's no quitting]
[(Why... isn't it flying?)]
[Running until the kite flies]
Minghao!
[Even if he swings his arms (?)]
[(Yes, it'll drop)]
[Kite flying isn't as easy as it looks]
Why did you bring a kite
that looks like you, MINGHAO?
- Looks like you? / - Looks like you.
[※Take caution of the pronunciation※]
A kite that looks like you?
A kite!
- Oh, this broke.
- It broke.
How did it break.
[They find out the kite is broken]
Look at this. Bring a different one.
Everything dies if I touch it.
[DK's kite ⤤]
JOSHUA! How do you save this?
I guess we're not meant to be.
[22]
It's flying like a bird right now.
[Only JOSHUA's kite is flying like a bird]
- It's pretty! / - Right?
[Feeling vicarious satisfaction]
[Floating]
[JOSHUA gave the spinning wheel to THE 8]
Yes, you can unwind it a bit now.
A bit of wind is blowing.
[JOSHUA gave the spinning wheel to THE 8]
[(The 8 is flying it)]
That's right.
It's so pretty.
It's the perfect time to fly a kite.
[(I'm going to do it sitting down!)]
I feel like the kite is getting very close...
Is that just me?
Right now, the kite looks
like it's going to fall in a frail way.
I'm not the only one feeling that, right?
There's no wind.
[T T]
I guess we need sunglasses to fly kites.
I can't open my eyes well!
Unwind it.
[Not tired]
I unwound it.
[Not tired, just lying down briefly]
[The kite suddenly flies higher
because of the wind]
- Nice! / - It worked.
[The kite suddenly flies higher
because of the wind]
- It worked.
- Nice!
- Nice! / - It worked!
[Gets up] [This is it]
Nice! Yo!
That's right.
This tree... What do we do about this tree?
[But]
[Obstacle] [Branches are stuck in the string]
Why did it get stuck?
I think this is how it's done.
[Obstacle] [Branches are stuck in the string]
It's fine.
- Just let it go with it... / - Go with it!
[Gives up]
♪ Going together
[(Even the branches)]
Nice!
It's working!
It's flying!
This is bad... What is it?
What do I do?
[2nd obstacle]
- From there. / - What?
[2nd obstacle = tangled string]
This is tangled.
Should I just unwind it?
Or I can just do it like that. It's okay.
I already unwound this.
[Even the tangled string goes with it~ ♪]
[⤦ Branches stuck here]
[String tangled here ⤤]
There are branches stuck there and
this part is tangled.
[⤦ Branches stuck here]
[String tangled here ⤤]
Something is being added one by one.
You have to pull this in a little.
[With one small kite flying well,]
Pull it, DK!
[They can smile like children here]
Pull it!
[This is the 2nd energetic
afternoon at "IN THE SOOP"]
Yes, grandma!
Yes, I can talk on the phone.
[Whose voice is this talking to his grandma?]
No, I was actually going to call you!
That's right.
I'm in Andong right now! Andong!
But your kimchi is
so popular right now, grandma!
The members really like it.
All of your food is good, grandma!
Okay! We'll enjoy it!
Yes, I love you!
[Grandson with a ton of aegyo] [❤]
Yes!
[The phone call with his maternal grandma
who gave the popular kimchi ends]
Because of the bees, I really...
[(SEUNGKWAN passes by)]
What are you doing?
[(SEUNGKWAN is passing by)]
I'm going to carry this and play there.
[Yoga mat]
What are you doing...?
[(Calls SEUNGKWAN right away...)]
Did you cook and eat ramyeon? DINO?
Yes, we cooked and ate it.
- What did you say you were doing?
- Over here...
I'm going to do like a new millennium
health exercises routine
on the front deck of the house.
[(Exercises...?)]
Oh, really?
Should I do exercises as well?
- What is he doing?
- He's going to do exercises.
SEUNGKWAN.
Yes, I'm going to exercises here.
[SEUNGKWAN finds a spot and sits down]
Should we do health exercises together?
[Featuring in SEUNGKWAN's life,
DINO also joins quickly]
- Should we do it together? / - Okay!
[Featuring in SEUNGKWAN's life,
DINO also joins quickly]
Do I have to bring a mat, too?
If I knew, I would've brought another one.
Quickly run and come back.
[There's no other choice]
DINO! Can you...
[OK run]
- Bring foam rollers if there are any
in the strength zone. / - Okay!
[When you come]
[Sprints a long distance to the strength zone,
which is furthest from the sleep zone]
[Passes the halfway point and
runs a long distance again to the sleep zone]
Going back and forth would be cardio.
[Kekeke]
It's too spread out.
[Exercising more with rest at "IN THE SOOP"]
As if I'm jogging...
SEUNGKWAN!
There are foam rollers?
That's awesome!
[The tools are ready,
so it's time to exercise]
This place is the essence of nature!
[(Can't hear anything after that cardio)]
Should we do our legs?
[Stretching time automatically causes groaning]
Did you do your back yesterday?
No, the day before.
Yesterday, I did shoulders.
Wow, this is a good foam roller.
[(Leave, toxins built up by alcohol...)]
[(Me as well)]
[This is like... the exorcist...?]
It's refreshing.
[Just from the sound,
SEUNGKWAN seems refreshed]
- VERNON!
- Yes.
[(Hi~)]
Why?
[(Saying hello)]
- What are you doing?
- I'm going to read a book now.
[#A_book #Coconut_water
#As_long_as_there's_just_sunlight]
[They're each enjoying the free
afternoon in their own ways]
Do you know any foam roller stretches?
I...
Foam roller? First off...
[Caretaker Boo Seungkwan, who has 5 years
of pilates experience, will show you]
Towards the butt.
[First, exercises to relieve the hip muscles]
Put it there.
This relieves the hip muscles here.
- Is it here?
- Yes.
[Going back and forth]
Just...
I feel like I need a nap.
It's sort of...
- Is it too drowsy?
- Yes.
[Fights his sleepiness and follows caretaker
Boo Seungkwan when he switches positions]
[Décalcomanie]
It hurts so much!
Try things like this, too.
Back and forth.
Huh?
[(What?)]
[(OK!)]
DINO. Do this and then this.
And then sit. Sit like this.
[Ctrl+C] [Ctrl+V]
Try sitting.
And the feet...
The top of your feet smooths out.
[While SEUNGKWAN works hard on stretching]
That's right.
- SEUNGKWAN.
- Yes?
Aren't you supposed to hug this and sleep?
[Kid DINO considering sleeping]
What is that called?
- A body pillow?
- That's nice!
And...
We have to relieve the armpits.
[Strict professor Boo] [Calms DINO down
as he enforces armpit stretching]
We sort of...
[Strict professor Boo] [Calms DINO down
as he enforces armpit stretching]
You look like a You*uber...
[(Can't hear anything because it hurts)]
[Going back and forth this time again...]
Wow, I guess my back workout
went well the other day.
[Going back and forth this time again...]
DINO! The last one.
[This is really the last one!]
After you lie down, this...
The arms..
[(What should I do?)]
Next...
[(You're doing a good job, right?)]
Make circles as you come down like this.
Like this.
As you push them down.
[Finishing off with shoulder exercises lying down]
Okay.
- Should we take some deep breaths to end?
- Okay.
But it's a bit better than before.
- It's a bit better.
- Yes, more than before.
You look like the pension manager!
[Free (?) manager takes care of
the pension while riding an ATV]
Huh?
[Free (?) manager takes care of
the pension while riding an ATV]
Can we check out a little later?
But you can use it because
there's nobody the next day.
[No reservations] [Generous (?) manager says yes]
- Thank you!
- Have fun!
- Okay!
- Don't get hurt.
- Okay.
You can't get hurt.
Is that ATV yours?
[Never-ending scenario]
Did I buy this last year?
[MINGYU is so cute!]
It's nice!
[Scenario]
[Sly pension keeper and guest - The end -]
[SEUNGKWAN and DINO are still stretching]
Can you press down here for me?
I'll press down for you, too.
Press it down all the way.
[Engraving patience as a virtue in his hips]
[Engraving patience as a virtue in his hips hoo~]
[Pressing down ⤣]
Okay! It's fine!
Your turn.
[It's your turn now kekeke]
Bye bye!
Slowly inhale.
[If he presses down as much as possible]
It's crazy...
Okay. 2, 3.
[After being refreshed from stretching]
[The last course is meditation]
[SEUNGKWAN also meditates
after glancing at DINO]
after glancing at DINO and fails]
- SEUNGKWAN.
- Yes.
How are you these days?
I think I'm searching for peace.
- Cr...
- Very...
[In about 10 seconds,
they are in danger of laughing]
Are you tired?
[SEUNGKWAN] [In about 10 seconds,
they are in danger of laughing]
I was also a little tired.
How are you?
These days, my days are...
It looks like JUN's messy room.
[(Resisting laughing)]
Whose room?
[(Fail at resisting laughing)]
Let's feel nature...
For me, this sound is
like the sound of pouring soju.
[Always about hangovers kekeke]
I think that's called Andong soju.
[Is that maybe called Andong soju?]
Andong soju.
30 percent.
[Suddenly like a commercial]
- Andong soju... Andong soju commercial.
- That's nice.
It's a good idea.
[Forever awaiting a call from liquor companies]
Like a meditation...
Like meditating to the sound of soju.
[Forever awaiting a call from liquor companies]
As it flows. Andong soju.
[With the stream of consciousness,
meditating ends]
That's nice.
[With the stream of consciousness,
meditating ends]
Look at how the clouds are moving.
[The clouds in the sky belatedly catch his eye]
[SEUNGKWAN doesn't want to miss this moment]
- Hey, but I... / - Yes.
Speak.
[I won't miss what DINO says either!]
You say speak.
I was lying down and looking at the sky earlier
and this came to mind.
Clouds just move this quickly, right?
Even when I'm here, the world is still spinning.
[Even if "I'm" stopped]
Really...
Organize your thoughts and speak.
[Ruins the mood]
No, listen!
So...
I can let go more of my concerns and worries.
[The many concerns and worries]
No matter how much I'm struggling,
they will all pass by either way.
[The current difficulties will pass by either way]
- That's right.
- I had a strange feeling.
[JEONGHAN is captured on
SEUNGKWAN's camera]
It's JEONGHAN.
[JEONGHAN is captured on
SEUNGKWAN's camera]
JEONGHAN!
[Click~]
Yes?
Hi!
[(Can't say hi)]
[Fisher Yoon just wanders
around the river all day long]
My arm hurts.
[Fisher Yoon just wanders
around the river all day long]
[Can hear people in the strength zone]
[Member DK is first to attend
the afternoon workout session]
[Lightly warms up first]
- Hello! You're here? / - Hello! You're here?
[Members MINGYU and THE 8 also came]
Everyone! Would you like to do
my routine today?
[Today's trainer, MINGYU]
We're going to do the back today.
[Today's exercise: back]
[Yesterday's exercise: chest]
- You did your chest yesterday, right? / - Yes.
[Today's exercise: back]
[Yesterday's exercise: chest]
- Please stretch.
- I ate well yesterday.
I also ate really well yesterday.
[◀◀◀ Last night]
[Strength zone of madness]
Go, go! That's right! Go!
[We have to go again today!!]
You have to go!
[The 97s' back exercise moment]
3!
[Vocal team representative, 97 DK]
4!
[The skilled guy who can
do a routine by himself, too]
Wow, DK! You're crazy right now.
[Back muscles]
Really?
Wow, your back is crazy!
It's crazy!
Wow! DK! Nice!
[Beautiful back muscles]
Nice!
2. Last one.
[(Me too?)]
[Hip hop team representative, 97 MINGYU]
[Trainer MINGYU's back exercise routine]
[1. Pull-ups]
[2. Lat pull-downs]
[Trainer MINGYU's back exercise routine]
[3. Arm pull-downs]
Even from the isolation, it's already delicious.
[NO picky eating] [Nutritious back]
Is that right?
How many?
[(Right now)]
10?
- You don't know, right? / - Yes, I don't know.
[Kekeke]
I said something roughly.
[When confused, start again! Ke]
[This time, it's performance
team representative, 97 and THE 8]
[He may look smaller sometimes]
[But his sturdy body is trained with
many hours of dancing]
How many was that?
- 10. / - Don't pull, but straight down.
[Expert MINGYU's focused care]
[The back exercise answer key
is distributed for free]
It's delicious!
[For muscles]
[Hip hop + performance + vocal collaboration]
[Came to exercise,
but watching from the front row ⤦]
Okay!
[Came to exercise,
but watching from the front row ⤦]
Go!
Hold on. It's delicious. What is this?
[In the meantime]
Why is yours delicious?
[Additional goods]
[Creating a random new dish?!]
The triceps are delicious.
[Additional goods]
[Creating a random new dish?!]
That's right!
That's right. Relaxing... You're doing well.
[Training is getting more intense]
You need to focus on relaxing it to feel it.
It has to relax well.
[Training is getting more intense]
Is it working?
It's working, but I'm not sure.
Don't move our body forward.
Just let your arms go.
[If you don't know, I'll teach you until you know]
- You feel it here, right? Here?
- Yes, I feel it here.
[Definitely full (shaking)]
Hold on. I can't stretch!
I can't stretch.
[Definitely full (shaking)]
Here.
- You feel it, right?
- Yes.
So when you do it later on,
a creek will form here.
- Really? / - Water will be dripping...
[(Creek attraction)]
If we meet like this everyday,
there's no way I can't exercise!!
Nice!
[Strength zone]
Tomorrow, we'll do shoulders!
[Strength zone] [#Tomorrow's_
workout_preview] [#Breaking_shoulders]
[Bouncing]
Where is the ball?
[SEUNGKWAN is running around
the forest looking for the ball]
Oh, here it is!
What is this?
Wow! There's a bouncy ball!
Who wants to play with a ball?
Hold on!
This is a dejavu!
[Refer to season 1]
[Night has fallen at "IN THE SOOP"]
Muk-jji...
[Opening the "SEVENTEEN IN THE SOOP 2"
volleyball competition]
- I will be the right wingback! / - Okay!
[Very serious] [(No going easy 🔥🔥)]
- Okay!
- WONWOO! Do a spike!
[(A spike...?)]
Do a spike!
[Got it]
[Everyone is surprised by WONWOO's spike]
Run!
[Passionate SEUNGKWAN]
The ace is here.
[★⚝The ace, WONWOO, is here★]
It was so scary...
[JOSHUA (The same team)]
- It's 10 against 7! / - Let's do something erratic.
[Who will win the close game?]
It's okay!
- Let's go! / - Let's go!
[Leaving the forest for today!]
The weather is so nice!
[Riding in the cool breeze]
Normally, "IN THE SOOP" is
[Peek-a-boo]
tough when you leave the forest.
[Peek-a-boo] [(?)]
Wow, look at that slope.
[Passion x3] [IN THE SOOP Alpine Club]
We're just going up.
[Going up]
This place is rough.
[Going up and up]
Hiking was never my hobby...
Wow, it's so beautiful!
[What sights await them?!]