♪ How about some pajeon by the stream?
[S.COUPS] [JEONGHAN] [JOSHUA]
♪ How about working out twice a day?
[JUN] [HOSHI] [WOOZI] [WONWOO]
♪ How about we fly in the sky?
[THE 8] [MINGYU] [DK]
♪ Or zone out into the fire
while you lean on me?
[SEUNGKWAN] [VERNON] [DINO]
♪ In the SOOP
♪ SOOP du ru du du ru du
SOOP du ru du du ru du (Yes, let's go there)
[SEVENTEEN IN THE SOOP2]
[This video contains ads and sponsorships]
♪ SEVENTEEN is In the SOOP
[SEVENTEEN IN THE SOOP2]
[This video contains ads and sponsorships]
Do we only need this?
[Morning of the second day at
the forest where the winds are blowing]
- This and THE 8's sincerity. / - Okay.
[Morning of the second day at
the forest where the winds are blowing]
What tea do you want to drink?
[Tea ceremony time that is
filled with THE 8's sincerity]
It feels like I am getting purified.
[Body]
- Really?
- Yes.
[Enjoying ATV with their whole bodies and wind]
Nice.
[Since they're driving through
a thickly wooded road]
I didn't know that there was a place like this.
[Since they're driving through
a thickly wooded road]
♪ My life is a trip, trip
JOSHUA.
[MINGYU's JOSHUA saving plan(?)]
Do you want me to cook a hangover ramen?
[(PLZ cure my hangover)]
[MINGYU's JOSHUA saving plan(?)]
I cooked it really well. What do I do?
[Green onion oil flavor is added]
[MINGYU's ramen is the best for hangover]
Wow! MINGYU!
You are really great cooking at ramen.
[Filled with amazement as soon
as you put it in your mouth!]
Compliments even make whales make ramen.
[Compliments even make whales make ramen]
SEUNGKWAN.
There's a foam roller? So nice.
[SEUNGKWAN, DINO's stretching time]
The day these days...
[Meditation that they enjoy in nature]
I think JUN's messy room.
Who's room?
[Healing continues]
Let's feel the nature.
[What is going to happen in the forest today?]
[Peaceful afternoon at "In the SOOP"]
[Enjoying their own free time]
[Members enjoying their hobbies]
[There is a member who is still in their dreams]
[Slide!]
[There is a member who just opened their eyes]
[Scratch]
I went to sleep early but it's already 4 p.m.
[(Yesterday)]
Why did I sleep for such a long time?
It's 4 p.m.?
[Characteristic of rest days: only my time goes fast]
[Characteristic of a main dancer:
rhythmic even lying down]
Who wants to play ball?
[(Who is that?)]
[SEUNGKWAN is bored after cooking]
Who wants to play ball?
[(I will play alone if there's no one)]
[Goal]
Wait.
This is déjà vu.
Let's play ball.
[Last season, "In the SOOP"]
[Playing with DK while
breath is coming out from his mouth]
[Situation where he tossed
the ball onto the roof as soon as he started]
[Titled, legendary 5 second ball game]
Why is your life a skit?
Wait.
[Speechless when he thinks about it, too]
No. I can't even do this when I want to.
[Written, directed, starring: SEUNGKWAN]
[Gives a skit today, too]
That was so funny.
[Written, directed, starring: SEUNGKWAN]
- SEUNGKWAN, are you playing by yourself?
- Huh? Yes.
Guys, let's play volleyball.
[THE 8 is heading towards
SEUNGKWAN who is playing by himself]
[MINGYU is practicing golf by himself]
[Discovered something]
- Bad... Yes. / - Let's play badminton.
[Suddenly changed to playing badminton]
What is this? It's badminton?
[Surprised] [Reason that MINGYU is surprised?!]
[XL size extra large badminton]
It's not tennis?
- This is just tennis. / - This is really tennis.
[Ball is extra big, too]
Sharapova.
[Alt character: Boo-rapova]
Nice.
Boo-rapova.
- Up to 5 points. / - Okay.
[Up to 5 points]
[Back]
[And forth]
[Mistake when he does a double take]
1 to 0.
[While a dynamic game is underway]
It went over?
[▶▶ REPLAY]
[▶▶ REPLAY] [Went over]
- What are you saying?
- It went over, right?
- It hit the floor and went over.
- No.
I was on the ground and hit it over.
[2:0]
2:0.
Nice. 2:1.
My true skills are coming out now.
We need to go with a long game
to see whether we have the basics or not.
[Boo-rapova's facts]
[Important thing about badminton is the basics!!]
This is the difference.
[Rally that continues]
[The opponent's mistake is my opportunity]
Yes, the difference is whether
you can do this or not.
[Tossing back what was said]
[THE 8's desire to win is ON]
[Boo-rapova shows his skills properly
after getting criticized]
Nice.
[Boo-rapova shows his skills properly
after getting criticized]
[Current score]
[THE 8 2 : 4 SEUNGKWAN]
Let's finish it right away.
[Current score]
[THE 8 2 : 4 SEUNGKWAN]
[THE 8 who is looking to turn the game around]
[Boo-rapova who is not giving him any room]
[Tiki-taka]
[Ends nicely with a strong smash]
He definitely has the skills.
[He's the type who accepts it quickly]
Thank you!
[Match of the century ends with Boo-rapova's win]
SEUNGKWAN, me too!
- THE 8, do you want to play with me? / - You go.
[Switches members THE 8 → MINGYU]
- SEUNGKWAN, it's been a while. / - MINGYU.
[Come on in]
It's been a while.
[MINGYU vs SEUNGKWAN]
[Plays properly with a normal size badminton]
Should we try a real game?
[MINGYU vs SEUNGKWAN]
[Plays properly with a normal size badminton]
Okay.
[MINGYU vs SEUNGKWAN]
[Plays properly with a normal size badminton]
THE 8, be the referee.
Okay.
[(This game's referee)]
- 10 points? / - 10 points.
[Match is a 10 point game]
Okay.
[Here]
[Here and there]
[MINGYU scores first]
1:0.
[SEUNGKWAN goes with an attack right away]
[Scores right away!]
1:1.
I am not me from the past!
- SEUNGKWAN, I'm going to do it for real. / - Okay!
[I am going to do it for real now!]
[Power]
[Power power]
[Power power power]
Wow! He's so good at smashing.
[Overwhelming physique]
[Power GYU's power smashing]
[Smooth]
[Smooth but strong at times]
[Even a quick sense of speed!!]
[Powerful in badminton]
[SEUNGKWAN, master at controlling
perfect strengths and weaknesses]
I accept.
[Powerful in badminton]
[SEUNGKWAN, master at controlling
perfect strengths and weaknesses]
3:3.
7:7.
[Head metronome]
[Neck and neck match where your mouth drops]
[Strong tug-of-war match]
- Hurts. / - Okay.
[Current score 9:9]
- Last. Let's finish. / - Let's end now.
[Surely]
[Will surely win]
[Slips]
[Catches the open spot]
[Slipped for a moment]
[MINGYU loses his balance]
It's done.
[Slipped for a moment]
[MINGYU loses his balance]
I barely won.
[SEUNGKWAN wins]
[Enthroned as the true master of ball games]
- Play again? / - No.
[SEUNGKWAN wins]
[Enthroned as the true master of ball games]
- Let's rest.
- Let's stop.
I really lost weight.
[I really gave it my all in that game...✰]
I lost all the ramen that I ate yesterday.
Oh, I ate some today, too.
[I really gave it my all in that game...✰]
[Nocturnal tiger who finally came outside]
[Half asleep] [Suddenly changes directions]
I sleep this long?
I was wondering what you were doing.
HOSHI, are you chest today?
[Workout]
- WOOZI is going to do it.
- Do you want to do it together?
[(Workout)]
I think WOOZI is going to come out soon.
[GOOD timing]
[WOOZI washed up and is drying hair]
My body still feels like it's sleeping.
- It's not waking up.
- Yes.
Strength zone.
[Name where it seems like you need
to do some lifting Kekeke]
"Strength zone" is a name where
it seems like you need to do some lifting.
[Kekeke]
It's nice to have someone to workout with.
[Lifting mates WOOZI, DINO
entered the strength zone together]
It's not easy to work out right after you wake up.
[⤦ Director WOOZI comes to
work to the strength zone]
Which part are you working out? Chest?
[JUN who was watching
also enters the strength zone, too]
Yes, chest.
[JUN who was watching
also enters the strength zone, too]
I can't wake up.
[Two people who are still not waking up]
My body is not waking up either.
HOSHI, snap out of it...
[Self spell]
Don't overdo it! Working out.
No.
You can't overdo yourself
when working out anytime.
[What director WOOZI]
[Does before so he doesn't get hurt = exercise]
You can't get hurt.
[What director WOOZI]
[Does before so he doesn't get hurt = exercise]
You do it so that you don't get hurt.
[What director WOOZI]
[Does before so he doesn't get hurt = exercise]
[If you warmed up your body and mind]
[It's lifting TIME]
How many kilograms are this?
- 10kg?
- 10.
Should we just put 20kg on there right away?
30kg, 60kg.
[Wake up muscles]
[WOOZI increases the weights hard]
Isn't that still about HOSHI?
Yes. I am about 61kg...
We can just lift you and do it.
[Current weight=HOSHI's weight]
Push. Okay.
[With DINO's support, finished one set]
- Thank you.
- Okay, good.
I did it thanks to DINO.
DINO is a pro at support.
[Continuing to be HOSHI's support]
But DINO holds my hip right here.
The stability...
One, two.
[Stability that only people who got knows]
- Press down all the way. Yes. / - Okay, last.
[Tiger's power up]
- Last.
- What?
- Don't give up. / - Press. Okay.
[Pushing him]
[Gym director WOOZI that made a comeback(?)]
Wow! I really did this thanks to DINO.
DINO was doing upright rows.
[1+1]
[Support and shoulder workout at the same time]
You use these a lot.
You use these more than you think.
[1+1]
[Support and shoulder workout at the same time]
I did these and it's not bad.
This is a true partnership.
[Kekeke]
Hi teacher.
[In the meantime]
- Hello. / - Hello.
[JEONGHAN is studying Japanese]
[⤣ Visitor DK]
Japanese again?
[(You are taking Japanese classes again?)]
The weather isn't nice.
Hi.
[(Takes up the best spot)]
Fishing or camping.
[Uses JEONGHAN's voice who's studying as a lullaby]
What was a nap?
[DK is taking a nap]
- Hirune. / - I even took a nap.
I'm hungry.
I want to eat some Korean food right now.
[Wants Korean food]
[Hunger alarm rings on time]
Korean food is nice.
[Wants Korean food]
[Hunger alarm rings on time]
[MINGYU who washed up in the meantime
is putting on lotion]
Finished.
[Shower]
What should I eat for dinner?
[S.COUPS is still deciding what to eat for dinner]
MINGYU, what should we eat?
Let's think about it.
[S.COUPS is still deciding what to eat for dinner]
What should we eat?
[(Looking for a menu)]
MINGYU, make a dumpling stew for me like this.
[Found a dumpling stew picture
that makes you salivate]
- What? Looks good. / - Right?
[Found a dumpling stew picture
that makes you salivate]
- Pork belly doenjang? / - Back ribs for me.
[Or]
I was thinking about grilling back ribs.
[MINGYU's choice is grilled back ribs]
- Grilled back ribs is good, too. / - Grilled back ribs.
Should I go eat? I'm hungry.
[Should I go to the food zone
since I picked the menu?]
It's cold since the sun went down.
VERNON! VERNON!!
[Time to not get bothered
"VERNON noise cancelling"]
What is he doing all day long?
[Did something just pass...?]
One, two.
[Hungry S.COUPS, MINGYU entered the food zone]
Yes.
Is there charcoal at the campsite?
[Hungry S.COUPS, MINGYU entered the food zone]
Char... You can make a campfire.
You can eat anything if we do that.
[Scanning the ingredients in
the fridge since they're hungry]
Let's eat it with a meal kit.
It was good when we cooked this yesterday.
[Temptation of the simple meal kit]
- Gangneung style jjamppong soft tofu.
- This looks good.
[Temptation of the simple meal kit]
This looks good.
[Today's menu]
I should eat this one.
Beef bulgogi stew.
[Today's menu]
[S.COUP's Pick beef bulgogi stew]
I am eating jjamppong soft tofu today.
[Today's menu]
[S.COUP's Pick beef bulgogi stew]
[MINGYU's Pick jjamppong soft tofu]
I need to eat grilled back ribs, too.
[Today's menu]
[S.COUP's Pick beef bulgogi stew]
[MINGYU's Pick jjamppong soft tofu]
[+ barbecued back ribs]
Let's grill the back ribs.
[Today's menu]
[S.COUP's Pick beef bulgogi stew]
[MINGYU's Pick jjamppong soft tofu]
[+ barbecued back ribs]
Let's grill the sausages.
[Menu choices that don't end for a long time]
These are lamb skewers.
Lamb skewers?
Let's ask JUN and THE 8 to grill the lamb skewers.
[(JUN and THE 8 can do that tomorrow♡)]
Let's ask them to grill this tomorrow.
Today are back ribs.
[★Today's main menu : back ribs★]
- How to cook back ribs. / - Grilled back ribs.
[⤣ Searching for grilled back ribs]
It came out really well here, too.
[MINGYU in charge of cooking
is getting a private lesson]
[So sincere]
Bring the pork galbi sauce.
[Teacher inside the phone's
secret is pork rib sauce]
- Bring it. / - Where is it?
[Teacher inside the phone's
secret is pork rib sauce]
[⤣ Bunch of different sauces]
This is maple syrup.
- MINGYU.
- Okay.
There's no pork galbi sauce...
It should be there. I saw it yesterday.
[Starts off with a dead end]
It's not here.
It should be here. But really...
[(Finds a suspicious sauce)]
- I saw it yesterday. / - This is steak sauce.
[Checks that it's not it and puts it back]
We need to use that if they don't have it.
- Should we put some Bul* sauce?
- But that seems good, too.
[Spicy sauce]
- Isn't all of the skin peeled off? / - I think so.
[Chef MINGYU is prepping the meat]
What meat...
[First, he washes and cuts the thick back ribs]
The meat is so good.
Pepper, salt!
Curry powder looks good, too.
[Sets up the seasoning that he's
going to use to flavor the back ribs]
Basil.
[Sets up the seasoning that he's
going to use to flavor the back ribs]
It's mala.
[Add mala sauce!]
We need to go with mala!
Then, let's do one with Bul* sauce
and go with a sauce each.
- One curry, one Bul*. / One salt flavor.
[Curry ver. spicy ver. salt ver... Endless recipe]
We are going to make a lot of different back ribs.
[Flavors]
This is a cooking vlog?
It's not hard.
I don't know if we will be successful or not!
Meat. Cooking is always what? Feeling.
[What is cooking? Feeling]
Feeling.
I'm going to watch.
[(MING-tube's biggest subscriber)]
[First back rib]
[First back rib is salt flavor]
[Pours a lot of basil to get rid of the meat smell]
Salt flavor.
[Simple is the best!]
Should we do this one with curry?
[Second back rib]
[Second back rib is curry flavor]
Next...
[Creativity is fully charged]
Basil with olive oil.
[Basil flavor]
All-around mala sauce.
[Basil flavor] [Mala flavor]
- Next... / - Steak sauce.
[Basil flavor] [Mala flavor] [Steak flavor]
What is it this time?
[Teacher]
Should we go with Bul* sauce this time?
[(This time is spicy spice?)]
Give me Bul*. Bul*.
This is extremely spicy Bul*?
[This is mega extremely spicy Bul*?]
Let's go with regular Bul*.
[Spicy flavor]
- Do we have regular Bu*?
- Yes, I think we're going to die with extreme.
- We're going to die. You can't even eat it.
- It's only one piece anyway.
[Pride of eating spicy things]
[We need to go with extreme spicy~]
You can't even eat spicy things.
[Bickering]
I eat it well these days.
[Bickering back and forth]
[⤣ Sprinkles a packet first]
[Just goes with a spicy one]
One more! One more!
[With the anxious request by the subscriber]
- Open up the extreme Bul*? / - Yes.
[With the anxious request by the subscriber,
opens up the extreme Bul*!]
The color is completely different.
[Strong dark red]
It's real.
[Finished making extremely red spicy back ribs!]
This is extremely Bul*.
The sun is already setting.
[Night at "In the SOOP" that came in the meantime]
[One person who is looking at the sky
get dark on top of the canoe]
[Being still and looking at the sun getting darker]
[THE 8 enjoying the relaxation of the quiet forest]
[Spending it in their own way]
[Time in the forest where they
spend in their own way]
[At that time, JOSHUA finds the food zone]
- Mala plus curry.
- Yes.
- Maka.
- What are you doing?
- We are going to eat grilled back ribs.
- Maka.
- Come and follow me.
What else do you want me to put?
[(Recipe creations that aren't finished yet)]
What else should I put in?
You haven't tried this yet?
[Found something]
You haven't tried honey
when you cook meat, right?
I don't think that's good.
[...Honey?]
You are going to be really surprised.
I don't think that's going to be good.
[(Sweet honey as a sauce for back ribs...)]
I haven't tried that.
- You haven't tried a steak with honey in it? / - Yes.
[You don't know this thing that's really good?]
It's really good.
Okay. Honey is going in.
I am going to put it up right now.
[Big journey of back ribs recipe] [Wrapping it up]
[Big run of back ribs recipe]
[Wrapping it up with honey back ribs]
[(Is this really right?)]
[Which back ribs is going to be the best one?]
[Full]
[Chef MINGYU's various grilled back ribs are ready]
It looks really good.
[Full]
[Chef MINGYU's various grilled back ribs are ready]
How good would it be if we wrap it up in kimchi?
[(Perfect with kimchi)
[(There are sweet potatoes, too)]
[Wrap it pretty in aluminum foil like back ribs]
[Really finished once he stacks it up!]
[Food zone]
[EP4. Today was a very fun day as well]
[SEUNGKWAN who was coming out
of the sleep zone this moment]
VERNON, you don't want to eat?
Let's go eat!
[SEUNGKWAN who was coming out
of the sleep zone this moment]
You don't want to eat?
[VERNON]
[VERNON is in noise cancelling mode right now]
[(VERNON...)]
You don't want to eat?
- What?
- You don't want to eat?
- VERNON, they finished all the food in the kitchen.
- I want to eat.
- Come to the kitchen! MINGYU said to come.
- What did you do right now?
[SEUNGKWAN, VERNON are
heading to the food zone]
[THE 8 who was riding a canoe heads
towards the food zone, too]
WONWOO, you're not going to eat?
[Dinner members who are gathering one by one]
THE 8, do you want to go eat?
Do you want to go eat?
[Dinner members who are gathering one by one]
What is it?
Pork ribs.
[Dinner members who are gathering one by one]
We made jjamppong and beef bulgogi stew, too.
[In the kitchen that got busy quickly]
[Another dish is starting!]
- What are you going to do with the green onions?
- Me?
Stir fry. Stir-fried meat.
[JOSHUA's stir-fried spicy pork]
[(Tap)]
[(Drip~~~)]
[Recipe X, measuring X]
[Stir-fried spicy pork being made easily]
- Like this here. / - It looks good.
[Evenly like this]
- Add a bit of curry powder. / - It looks good.
[Done if you leave it out so that
the sauce can soaked up on the meat]
[And the kitchen that's still busy(?)]
There should be a manual.
[Jjamppong soft tofu meal kit recipe ⤦]
[Chef MINGYU reading the meal kit instructions]
THE 8, can you take out the squid for me?
SEUNGKWAN, give me the squid and abalones, too.
[Chef MINGYU's food start again]
[Lights the stove skillfully]
[Adds all the meal kit ingredients
into a pan with oil]
[Doesn't waste and adds all kinds of seafood]
[+Abalone]
[+Shrimp balls]
[Add some fire flavor with a fancy snap]
[When the ingredients that
are cooked deliciously and broth meet]
Why does it smell so good?
It's done when you keep on boiling it.
[Meal kit transformation]
[Fresh seafood and meal kit jjamppong meet!]
[100 point dish is made when you add
soft tofu in the end!]
Yes.
[100 point dish is made when you add
soft tofu in the end!]
[In the meantime, one person
who can't leave the refrigerator]
I want to eat dumpling stew.
[Dumpling stew that he saw on
social media won't leave his sight]
I don't know. I want to add dumplings
into this gopchang stew.
[Second transformation
(gopchang stew+dumpling=?)]
[1. Puts it in]
[2. Puts it in again]
[3. Puts them all in]
[4. Puts in a lot of dumplings]
["Putting everything in at once
and cooking it... That is what a meal kit is!"
- by. S.COUPS -]
I'm all done.
[Second meal kit's transformation]
It needs to cook now.
[Second meal kit's transformation is also well done!]
Wow! It smells spicy!
What is this? Looks good.
[MINGYU came over because of a good smell]
I added some curry powder.
[So good]
[JOSHUA's stir-fried spicy pork
that is cooking deliciously]
- JOSHUA, please cook it well. / - Okay.
[JOSHUA's stir-fried spicy pork
that is cooking deliciously]
[And next to that...]
[And next to that... Pot that is boiling(?)]
[10 minutes ago]
Who wants to eat corn cheese
and Bul* Ramen if I make it!
[10 minutes ago]
I will eat it.
- I'm sure we will eat it. / - We will eat it.
- So, I will do that.
[SEVENTEEN that doesn't say no when eating]
[That's how the 5th dish started]
[Only two ramen]
Two tablespoons of mayonnaise.
[Make corn cheese while the noodles cook]
[Pour the spicy sauce when
the noodles are done cooking]
[Shake it so it's spicy]
[If you put the corn cheese on top
and put it in the microwave oven]
[A spicy, sweet corn cheese
Bul* Ramen is complete!]
This looks really good. Crazy.
[A spicy, sweet corn cheese
Bul* Ramen is complete!]
[In the meantime, at the tarp zone
next to the food zone]
[If WONWOO lights the fire
on the barbecue brazier]
[Perfect teamwork]
[Chef MINGYU puts the back ribs on top]
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope that it's good.
[Various flavors of back ribs that are getting golden]
Aren't we making a lot of food right now?
Everyone is making everything
that they want to eat right now.
I think that all of the members can come.
Yes. Sesame can go in there.
[Dishes for the members are getting done]
Okay, done.
I'm walking by.
- Be careful. / - Okay.
[Let's hurry up and eat~!]
Hurry up and come on out.
[Members bringing out the done
dishes and gathering around]
Nice.
[Members bringing out the done
dishes and gathering around]
Guys! The stir-fried spicy pork is here.
[Stir-fried spicy pork] [❤]
[MENU]
[Menu1. Braised back ribs]
[Menu2. Corn cheese buldak]
[Menu3. Stir-fried spicy pork]
[Menu4. Dumpling gopchang stew]
[Menu5. Jjamppong soft tofu]
You're eating?
Yes.
[Called the members who were resting
in different parts of the forest]
Come to the place where we eat.
There are a lot of good things.
[Called the members who were resting
in different parts of the forest]
Eat.
[Called the members who were resting
in different parts of the forest]
What? There are a lot of people suddenly.
[When they are surrounded in harmony]
Good thing we made a lot of food.
WOOZI, eat.
[Comforted with the member's heat in no time-]
[First group meal in the forest]
Thank you for the food.
- Wow, SEUNGKWAN! Looks good.
- It's kind of sweet.
You know!
[Scarier because it's a flavor that they know]
[SEUNGKWAN's corn cheese Bul* Ramen]
[(Bite!)]
[Everyone is in love with the sweet,
salty, and spicy collaboration]
It's really good.
[Everyone is in love with the sweet,
salty, and spicy collaboration]
[Tries Chef MINGYU's seafood
soft tofu jjamppong, too]
But meal kits really never fail.
[Flavor is doubled because of the meal kit
and the effort]
Meal kits never fail.
[Flavor is doubled because of the meal kit
and the effort]
[Meal kit lover tries
the gopchang dumpling stew he made]
I should only buy meal kits at home.
[❤]
[(Nom nom for JUN, too)]
The stew is so good.
[Nom nom for JUN, too)]
- Is this a gopchang stew?
- I think so.
No, this is dumpling... Dumpling.
[Dumpling stew]
I added the dumplings.
[No, I added dumplings into the gopchang stew]
- Huh?! / - I added the dumplings.
There is gopchang in here.
[Huh?!]
[No, I added dumplings into the gopchang stew]
- It's a gopchang stew. / - I added dumplings
into a gopchang stew.
It's even better when I know
I'm eating gopchang stew.
JOSHUA's is so good.
[Food to try now]
[JOSHUA's stir-fried spicy pork that's glossy]
It's good. You really made it well.
[Food to try now]
[JOSHUA's stir-fried spicy pork that's glossy]
[(One big bite)]
[(Bite!)]
You made it well.
[Frown of truth]
[Me too!]
It tastes like what my mom used to make me.
It tastes like stir-fried spicy pork that you eat at
a delicious Korean restaurant in America.
[Famous LA Korean town style spicy pork]
The sauce is really thick.
[Chef JOSHUA recreated LA flavor(?) in the forest]
I purposely made the sauce thick.
JOSHUA's is so good.
- But it's really good. / - It's good.
He really made it well.
[You and I complimenting
the stir-fried spicy pork]
This is so good.
[You and I complimenting
the stir-fried spicy pork]
- JOSHUA, no can do. / - It's so good.
[Empty plate in no time ⤦]
[Request for more are coming in nonstop]
- Right? / - I think you need to make more.
[Empty plate in no time ⤦]
[Request for more are coming in nonstop]
Should I make more?
[Empty plate in no time ⤦]
[Request for more are coming in nonstop]
Do you want me to make more?
I will make it right now.
- JOSHUA's is really good even
if you just mix it with rice. / - I know.
[JOSHUA is heading to the food zone
due to refill requests for his stir-fried spicy pork]
- I ate a lot yesterday. / - JOSHUA's is so good.
[JOSHUA is heading to the food zone
due to refill requests for his stir-fried spicy pork]
Did you wake up early today?
[During that time, pre-grill for back ribs are done
and Chef MINGYU is working with a torch]
Oil is coming up.
[During that time, pre-grill for back ribs are done
and Chef MINGYU is working with a torch]
[Fiery flavor is UP on the back ribs
that is flowing with oil]
Who wants to eat meat?
[~ Cook master MINGYU's back ribs is opened ~]
Me.
I guess this one is salt.
[~ Cook master MINGYU's back ribs is opened ~]
It's good.
[(Om nom nom)]
There is a lot more meat on the ribs.
The salt one is amazing.
[(Ripping the galbi)]
Food after a workout is the best.
[Eating after a workout is even better]
Huh? Where?
Wow! The galbi is really good.
[Master MINGYU's grilled back ribs are a success]
- It's good. / - It's good. This is good.
Our cooking skills definitely
got better than last year.
[With upgraded cooking,
their mouths are enjoying the dinner]
We got a lot better.
[With upgraded cooking,
their mouths are enjoying the dinner]
This is Bul*.
[Opens the spicy flavored back ribs now]
It's Bul*? Bul*?
Bul*, come on. Let's go!
[Opens the spicy flavored back ribs now]
Bul*. Curry. And what else is there?
[Spicy, curry, salt] [There's another flavor?]
- There's another flavor? / - Bul*, curry.
[Spicy, curry, salt]
Mala.
- What is this? / - This is basil.
[Prepared everything because I
didn't know what you would like]
It kind of feels like back ribs omakase.
[Chef MINGYU's back ribs course meal]
It's really good.
[Members are enjoying various flavors of back ribs]
It's good.
[Filled with individuality,
everything is the best]
Menu is all good.
[Filled with individuality,
everything is the best]
Man! The back ribs keep on going in.
- You're eating well. / - It's good.
[Proud lips ⤥]
I normally eat really well.
[In the meantime,
the 2nd round of stir-fried spicy pork is done]
Applause!
[§ Chef JOSHUA enters with his 2nd spicy pork §]
Respect.
- Hurry up and give it to me. / - Put sesame on it.
[Hurry up! I am getting dizzy...!]
- Put sesame on it. / - Sesame?
This is really good.
[Chopsticks that are diving into
the stir-fried spicy pork like moths]
JOSHUA, this looks even better.
[Chopsticks that are diving into
the stir-fried spicy pork like moths]
- I hope that it's good. I haven't tried it.
- No.
It's good even if we don't look at it.
- You need to be patient. / - Is it good?
[Hot]
I think JOSHUA's meat is crazy.
[Members eating well like it's the first meal]
You worked hard in grilling.
It's so good. What do I do?
[What did you do to this stir-fried spicy pork?]
What did you put in here?
JOSHUA, hurry up and eat.
- JOSHUA, teach me the recipe later.
- Okay.
- JOSHUA made this recipe?
- Yes.
- Wow, you're a chef. / - It's good.
[❤]
Oh, I'm full!
[(I am full...)]
JOSHUA, can we chop it into
thin pieces and stir-fry it?
Let's stir-fry the rice.
[K-dessert fried rice is the best...]
I'm done.
- Put in seaweed and stuff. / - I...
[K-dessert fried rice is the best...]
- Let's just taste a bit together.
- It's good.
That looks so good.
Two instant rice?
[Two rice?]
One.
This is two.
[Two rice?] [Answer is set]
Two.
[Okay with two rice!]
It would be good to stir-fry rice.
- You're going to stir-fry rice?
- Yes.
The guys wanted to have a bite each.
[Just having a taste~]
Amazing...
JOSHUA just made history with this meat.
- It's really good.
- This is really good, right?
JOSHUA is crazy.
[Scrapes the bottom of the pan
of this historical rice with sauce!]
[Presses it down and stir-fries it to a crisp]
- MINGYU, you know seaweed, right?
- I know.
[⤣ Firmly closed mouth]
[Very serious about fried rice...]
You are really passionate.
[Kekekekeke]
MINGYU is practically...
- We basically brought MINGYU here as a chef.
- "In the SOOP".
[Kekeke]
Chef of Season 2.
[Official chef = MINGYU]
But I think it's going to be good.
[Carefully adjusting the heat by Chef MINGYU
who all the members acknowledged]
[Visual where it has to be good!]
- To be honest, that has to be good. / - Yes.
It would be better when it's
cooked a bit more, right?
[Boom]
- It needs to be burnt.
- Yes. It's good when it's burnt.
[Clap]
The smell is already good.
- But it smells like that right now.
- What?
It smells like dalgona.
Isn't it burning too much?
[A serious smell that is
coming from the fried rice]
[(MINGYU running)]
[White smoke that seems serious]
It can't get burnt.
- Oh! Wait. MINGYU!
- It looks like a pancake.
- It's black on the bottom. / - Really?
- Really?
[Uh oh...]
You're right.
[Black]
But you eat it with the burnt taste.
[You're supposed to eat fried rice
with the burnt(?) taste]
[Add a bunch of seaweed
and tries to salvage it]
Done.
If you put sesame oil on it...
[Here]
Done.
[JOSHUA+MINGYU]
[Stir-fried spicy pork fried rice is complete!]
[Wow~ This it it~]
You really made it well.
- Wait. Let's try it. / - I am going to have a bite.
[(Loss for words at the visual)]
But I am really only going to have a bite.
I am only going to have a bite, too.
Really only a bite.
[Another promise he will not keep+1]
I think it's going to be hot.
[One bite]
Just one bite. I am going to have a bite.
It's so good?
- It's the best fried rice that I had recently.
- Really?
[Best fried rice that I had recently]
[(A bite for me, too)]
It does look really good.
- Wow! / - Wait a minute.
[❤]
- That good?
- It's good.
- Don't over exaggerate. Really!
- It's so good.
I really hate it when people over exaggerate.
- You tell us like it is. / - I will be brutally honest.
[WOOZI / really hates exaggeration]
- WOOZI's buildup. / - This is all buildup.
- This is a buildup.
- I am an epicure.
[Epicure WOOZI tries the fried rice]
I want to eat the fried rice as a side dish.
The sauce is good.
[Epicure WOOZI tries the fried rice]
[Hehe]
[Strong flavor that makes him smirk]
He just laughs.
- JOSHUA is really good at cooking. / - He's good.
- I know.
[As a reference...]
I will only have one more bite.
[Things they ate for dinner: 8 servings of back ribs]
[2 rounds of stir-fried spicy pork,
soft tofu jjamppong, gopchang stew,
corn cheese Bul* Ramen]
- It's good. / - It's good.
[Of course, there's a separate stomach for fried rice]
- It's really so good. Man...
- It's really good.
My hand needs to stop but it keeps on going.
[Infinite inhaling that doesn't go through the brain]
- The taste is really deadly. / - To the directors...
[Fried rice taste is so deadly]
- Should we give them some? / - Devil's taste.
[Devil's(?) taste where you can't stop...]
But the taste is really devilish.
I think you can sell it.
[Eat]
[MINGYU's dinner show] [Eat and eat]
MINGYU really eats well.
MINGYU, you said you were full.
[Finished completing from
cooking Vlog to eating Vlog⭑]
- Oh, I'm doomed... I am really in trouble.
- But we brought it?
- I think my stomach is going to explode.
- This wasn't here?
You know how it is when it's tight, right?
[Stomach's full because of the never-ending eating]
I am really in big trouble.
I am exactly in that state, too.
[Stomach's full because of the never-ending eating]
It's always impossible to manage your weight
when you come to "In the SOOP".
MINGYU, are you going to
take out the sweet potatoes?
[With that said, yes to sweet potatoes?]
- Take out the sweet potatoes. / - Take them out.
- Roasted sweet potatoes is crazy.
- Korea's...
You eat carbs and eat carbs for dessert.
[Carbs for meal+carbs for dessert=fantasy]
Sweet potato is really good.
[End of barbecue is sweet potato]
It's over if you eat sikhye now here.
If you drink sikhye,
that's a triad of carbs.
Put kimchi on top...
[One piece of kimchi on top
of a cooked sweet potato]
I will just chew it.
[Even the dessert is perfect in this dinner]
It kind of feels like a holiday.
- Peel the chestnut...
- Peel the sweet potato and that...
[It's a holiday when you're all gathered
and eat something good]
- Yes. / - It's been a while since we got together.
[It's a holiday when you're all gathered
and eat something good]
But hasn't it been a while that we ate together?
Even though we were always together?
- Yes.
- Right?
We were always together but eating together...
[Today's meal feels kind of new]
- It's hard to be on the same time to eat. / - It's hard.
It's not easy.
[Today's meal feels kind of new]
- That's crazy. We were always together
but eating together...
- Yes. / - You're right.
[It's been a while]
We see each other once a day
and there's a lot of time we spend together.
We do rehearsals
and people who want to wash up go wash up.
[Since they all do their own thing during schedules]
People who want to eat go eat.
People who get their hair and makeup done
[Since they all do their own thing during schedules]
get their hair and makeup done.
I don't think there's a lot of time to eat together.
["When was the last time we all ate together...?]
Unless it's at a place like this,
[(Like "In the SOOP")]
there aren't many days when I eat
with the members like this.
[(Meals)]
These moments when we can talk like this...
[These moments together]
They're fun and it's a sight
I haven't seen in a while.
[These moments together are fun and
haven't been seen in a while]
I think I am grateful.
The fact that I can spend time
with the members for a long time.
I probably means that these short times are
slowly getting more precious.
[The small joys that
the time spent all together brings]
I'm so happy we're all together.
[After a long time]
This looks nice. I will take a picture.
- Yes. / - Yes.
[Want to remember it for a long time,
now that will be remembered for a long time]
One, two, three.
[Want to remember it for a long time,
now that will be remembered for a long time]
[Dinner time that we finally had together
at "In the SOOP"]
No! I really can't eat anymore.
[After their stuffed dinner meal ends]
I am so full. It's so nice.
Should we clean up and go now?
Then later at night, around 11 o'clock,
[- Recruiting party attendees to have a drink -]
would anyone like to light the campfire
and have some soju?
[- Recruiting party attendees to have a drink -]
But more than that, before...
Let's digest with some mafia or foot volleyball.
[What about a game to digest before that?]
- Okay. / - Let's do that.
- Do you want to play foot volleyball?
- Are we playing foot volleyball?
- I will if we play. / - Nice.
[A game? I will if we play~]
There are a lot of people who will. Let's do it then.
SEUNGKWAN, do you want to play volleyball?
Let's play!
Do you want to play with the bouncy ball?
It's been a while.
- The one where you hit the ground?
- Yes! The one we played long ago.
- The fake soccer that we played all the time?
- Fake soccer.
[Chaotic volleyball that is summoned]
- We need to do it. / - Do you remember playing
it at 5 a.m. long time ago?
[Memory of playing this chaotic volleyball
at 5 a.m. when they were trainees]
- Crazy. / - At Cheongdam.
[Memory of playing this disastrous volleyball
at 5 a.m. when they were trainees]
- Total...
- Ground two times.
It's done if it bounces twice at once.
[SEVENTEEN's chaotic volleyball rule]
[1. One person can only bounce it once]
[2. One person is not allowed
to touch twice in a row]
Yes.
[SEVENTEEN's chaotic volleyball rule]
[1. One person can only bounce once]
[2. One person is not allowed
to touch twice in a row]
Now.
[SEVENTEEN's chaotic volleyball rule]
[1. One person can only bounce once]
[2. One person is not allowed
to touch twice in a row]
One.
[SEVENTEEN's chaotic volleyball rule]
[1. One person can only bounce once]
[2. One person is not allowed
to touch twice in a row]
- Two and... / - We need to get it over now.
[SEVENTEEN's chaotic volleyball rule]
[1. One person can only bounce once]
[2. One person is not allowed
to touch twice in a row]
- Pass it over. / - Yes.
[SEVENTEEN's chaotic volleyball rule]
[1. One person can only bounce once]
[2. One person is not allowed
to touch twice in a row]
- This is it.
[SEVENTEEN's chaotic volleyball rule]
[1. One person can only bounce once]
[2. One person is not allowed
to touch twice in a row]
- 15 points. / - Let's go.
["15 points"]
[Team MINGYU - MINGYU, DK, SEUNGKWAN
vs Team JOSHUA - JOSHUA, WOOZI, DINO]
JOSHUA serves.
["15 points"]
[Team MINGYU - MINGYU, DK, SEUNGKWAN
vs Team JOSHUA - JOSHUA, WOOZI, DINO]
Don't try to get it right away.
Nice.
[Starts with JOSHUA's fire serve]
- Okay. Slowly, one at a time.
- Okay. One at a time.
[Lightly taps]
Nice block.
[Lightly taps???]
Nice.
[Peek-a-boo]
Hey DINO.
[No Kekekekekeke]
Our team's best center!
[Perfect defense]
No, DINO's ball...
[WOOZI bursts out laughing from
MINGYU and SEUNGKWAN's defense Kekeke]
He was playing from underneath.
[- Fan service ceremony one more time -]
Is this side 1?
[(Referee)]
[Current score MINGYU team 1 : 0 JOSHUA team]
This side 1. 1:0.
[(Referee)]
[Current score MINGYU team 1 : 0 JOSHUA team]
[(DK's serve)]
Mine.
[JOSHUA → DINO]
- DINO. / - Put it up.
[JOSHUA → DINO smooth connection]
- WOOZI, okay. / - Nice.
[WOOZI successfully attacked this time]
- DK, get ready!
- Make it.
[(DK, get it...!)]
Get it over.
[DK's spike that hits nicely directly down]
- You were practically Kim Yeon-Koung!!
- This is it.
[(DK)]
That was close.
[Current score 2:0]
- I feel like I'm watching "Haikyu!!"
- That was close.
[Current score 2:0]
SEUNGKWAN, you know, right? Folding your legs.
[(Basic posture when you score)]
DK always...
[Agreeing with the highlight scene Kekeke]
You need to become a chicken leg.
MINGYU needs to do it directly.
[We need to go with this feeling!]
We can make it together again and go.
[We can go with this feeling!]
- Let's do a play where we make it. / - When...
[↑ MAX confidence from the start ↑]
- I am always ready for a back attack.
- Always be ready.
[↑ MAX confidence from the start ↑]
- Back attack. Yes. Back attack. / - Whenever.
Service ace.
Nice.
[JOSHUA's fire serve🔥]
DK!
[DK's good attack]
[DK's good attack] [(Calm defense)]
DINO.
[DINO's quick attack]
- Okay. / - I will do it.
SEUNGKWAN.
Back attack.
[MINGYU said it was a back attack
but tossed it to the front]
Pass this over.
[MINGYU said it was a back attack
but tossed it to the front]
You said to get ready for a back...
[(Chaotic teamwork)]
I'm sorry but you can do it.
[Half sorry half upset]
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry but you can do it.
- Okay.
[Half sorry half upset]
2:1.
[Current score]
Oh, something different!
[SEUNGKWAN gets it]
- Receive. / - Sorry. / - Nice.
[Seungkwan receives and MINGYU passes it over]
- Okay WOOZI. / - Block.
[WOOZI passes it over right under the net!]
Block!
[MINGYU gets that]
- One touch! / - One touch.
[SEUNGKWAN's spike continues]
- One touch.
[(WOOZI, get it...!] [(WOOZI is going~)]
[WOOZI is going~)]
Nice. Good.
[Ends with him rolling]
We needed to go with a rubber ball.
[Sad]
[Current score MINGYU team 3 : 1 JOSHUA team]
[Game continues]
- Nice. / - Miss.
[JOSHUA team's repetitive mistakes]
[And spike DK's performance]
- Nice. / - Nice.
[Current score is 6:1 so
the difference is getting bigger]
We have 6?
[Current score is 6:1 so
the difference is getting bigger]
[(Provoking them with JAM heh)]
It's okay.
[Team JOSHUA that is getting fired up]
- It's good. / - It's okay.
5 points? We can catch up right away.
- I'm going. / - DK...
[- Game continues -]
- MINGYU almost hit in the back of the head.
- Almost got hit.
[Completely focused]
- Nice. / - We can make this.
[(DK's calm pass)]
[(Kind of taps it-)]
We can make it.
[My turn...!]
Nice.
[Ding~] [My turn...!]
[Discouraged]
So nice.
Oh, WOOZI is tying his shoes.
[Kekeke]
No way.
[You... Making this mistake...]
WOOZI.
No.
You can do it.
[WOOZI!]
We will show what turning it around is.
[Okay, time to fire back!]
Okay.
[In the passion where they throw their bodies]
Nice.
I will acknowledge if you save it.
[Here you go, a home run]
- Nice. / - Out.
[Team MINGYU is shaking a bit]
- 9:4.
- It was so good.
[9 : 5]
- DINO.
- DINO, hit it.
Okay.
[9 : 6]
MINGYU, go out a bit more and receive it.
[Team JOSHUA is catching up]
A bit spread out.
[Let's focus]
It's not late if you start running after
you see the direction I hit it in.
[(Coach as a side job)]
[Let's focus]
[Desire to win is UP]
SEUNGKWAN gives it to the back.
[Desire to win goes UP]
- Okay. / - Toss... / - No.
Trying to give it to MINGYU.
[Ball is barely staying alive]
- Okay, save it. / - One touch. / - One touch.
- Okay. / - Nice.
[Ball is barely staying alive]
- Okay, save it.
- One touch.
- Okay.
- Nice.
Get it over.
- Okay. / - Pass it over. / - Nice.
[Master at saving the ball]
- Okay. / - Nice. / - Get it over.
- Nice.
- Get it over.
[SEUNGKWAN holding the ball
that is going over to the other team?!]
What?
[SEUNGKWAN holding the ball
that is going over to the other team?!]
I grabbed the ball that was going over.
[9 : 7]
- Sorry. / - Good.
- 7:9? / - We brought it. Brought the flow.
- Good. Let's go.
[Team JOSHUA are good and in the groove]
It's 7:9?
We are going to win this.
[Team JOSHUA are good and in the groove]
"We are going to win this."
[(Why is everyone so serious? Keke)]
Nice.
Sorry. It's okay.
[Ball that they saved by throwing themselves]
- Nice. / - No.
[SEUNGKWAN's attack where
he went for an empty spot]
- No!!
- Nice.
- 10:7. / - Nice, nice. Very nice.
[Succeeded in an attack with
SEUNGKWAN's experienced skill]
- You two just need to make it. / - Nice.
[Game that is slowly getting more intense]
- Nice. / - In!
[Their hearts are already national athletes]
- Got it over. / - Okay.
- Nice. / - Nice. / - In!
[- On set of "In the SOOP" Olympics -]
[Fascinated]
Nice.
- You saved it?
- JOSHUA!
- Get it over.
- Saved it. JOSHUA!
[Nervous all of a sudden]
- JOSHUA.
- Get it over.
[Legs gave out in an important moment T T]
- Left the ball and only his body flew.
- He flew.
JOSHUA flies.
- So close.
- Bring the mood.
- 14:9. / - It was good.
[Current score]
[Team MINGYU 14 : 9 Team JOSHUA]
Match!
It's match? Already?
[Team MINGYU wins with one more point]
JOSHUA.
[Careful and careful since it's the last point]
- Need to get it over. / - Get it over.
Make it.
[Careful and careful since it's the last point]
No.
[DK's power spike]
Saved it.
[DK's power spike ➨ JOSHUA defends]
Okay.
[WOOZI's elbow smash]
Good.
[Perfect teamwork]
Make it.
Nice.
[(Impenetrable defense)]
[Ball that went high because of JOSHUA's receive]
Block.
[Will Team MINGYU win like this?]
[Team JOSHUA's comeback?]
[What will be the results to
"In the SOOP" Olympics volleyball?]
Nice.
[Ball that got caught in the net]
[15 point game]
[Team MINGYU 15 : 9 Team JOSHUA]
- Okay.
- That was close.
[(Hitting the ground
because of the disappointment)]
- 15:9. / - Over.
[Game ends with Team MINGYU's victory!]
Make new teams?
Or go with the next set?
[Rest is luxury, GO on with a fast game]
- Who wants to play? / - Come in.
- Who wants to play?
[Rest is luxury, GO on with a fast game]
- HOSHI, play!
- HOSHI, play once. There's nothing to it.
You can be a star, too.
- I watched "Haikyu!!" / - Okay.
[Volleyball anime]
- WONWOO, play. / - Okay.
[WONWOO joins and does a 4 vs 4]
- Then, let's go with a 4 vs 4 game. / - Okay.
- Split the team. / - Split up the team.
- Let's split up the teams.
[Before the game, splitting the teams again]
Rock-paper.
- Rock, paper. / - Done.
- Done?
Okay.
[Teams decided in one go]
- Let's go. / - Let's go. / - It's okay
[JOSHUA, HOSHI, WONWOO, WOOZI vs
MINGYU - MINGYU, DK, SEUNGKWAN, DINO]
But we have good defense.
[JOSHUA, HOSHI, WONWOO, WOOZI vs
MINGYU, DK, SEUNGKWAN, DINO]
Then...
- What should we do with the positions?
- Position. Just any...
- I will be the right wingback! / - Okay.
[Watched some soccer]
- Do you want to fall back as a wingback?
- Is this soccer?
[Why does wingback come out?]
That's the only thing that I know.
I'm going.
Go.
[A light warm-up before the actual game]
Nice.
Okay, WONWOO.
- Let's make it slowly.
- We have a war within ourselves.
[Buildup volleyball that is made slowly]
- We are internal conflicts. / - Internal conflicts?
- One touch.
- HOSHI, save it!
- Yes. Good job.
- Good.
Save it!
[A long rally considering it's a warm-up]
- Save it. / - Save it. / - Slowly. / - Okay.
- Nice.
Okay. WONWOO?
Do a spike!
[(Spike...?)]
WONWOO! Do a spike!
[(3 pointer basketball shot)]
[Kekekekekekekekekekekeke]
- WONWOO is using an excavator.
- Why... Why are you dunking...
- He kind of has an X-Man vibe.
- Why are you dunking?
No, there wasn't a basketball hoop here?
[(Basketball hoop that only WONWOO saw)]
It's going here.
Oh! This is my fault.
I was going to spike.
I wasn't going to put it in another's teams area.
[It's my fault because I forgot the object
since I was in a hurry...!]
WOOZI, we need a detailed briefing.
[Kekeke]
I didn't know you would put it in our area.
It's this funny?
Put it in like this.
- How many points? / - Neatly 7 points.
[Officially game START]
- Starting now? / - Start now.
Nice.
- WONWOO!
- Nice.
DK.
- Slowly.
- MINGYU.
MINGYU.
[MINGYU hits it lightly and makes a fake]
- Nice. / - As expected.
[Kind of a far distance to touch the ball...!]
[(Spectators gathering)]
It's a drill. A drill.
[WOOZI / today's hunter]
- Drill. / - Sad. / - Can't predict it.
[Making fun with a patented ceremony Kekeke]
So disappointing, right?
[Hehehe]
[Making fun with a patented ceremony Kekeke]
[(Reserved as the next ceremony)]
Our team is fun.
[Current score] [Team JOSHUA 0 : 1 Team MINGYU]
Nice.
[Fire spike🔥]
This...
[Flawless home run]
- Nice. / - Nice.
[Score is tied again with JOSHUA's performance]
Those big hands.
- HOSHI, can you serve? Okay.
- I will try it.
- HOSHI, let's go. / - You watched "Haikyu!!"
[- Volleyball learned from an anime in real life -]
- Nice.
- Okay. Nice.
- Make it.
- Spike it.
- Put it down.
- Nice.
- Nice. / - Yes.
[Power shot]
Save it and get it over.
[(Tiger running)]
- Nice.
- Yes.
- Yes. / - You need to save it and get it over.
[⤣ Spider defense]
You need to get it over.
[(Proud)]
- Nice. Good. / - Nice.
[Extended rally again...?!]
- All done. / - Save it. Make it.
Nice.
[!!!]
- Nice. / - Close.
[Hit WOOZI's hand but the ball didn't go over...]
[Current score] [Team JOSHUA 1 : 2 Team MINGYU]
[Starts the game again]
Different!
WON!
[(WOO)]
Get it over.
The rule is to let it bounce once.
Bounce it once.
[(Keeper of rules)]
And then get it over.
I almost fell backwards
because the ground is not smooth.
I know, backwards...
[(Laugh button, reminding WONWOO)]
Slapstick.
[Kekeke]
[Current score]
[Team JOSHUA 1 : 3 Team MINGYU]
Nice.
[WOOZI's pass]
[WONWOO gets WOOZI's pass]
[WONWOO gets WOOZI's pass
and WONWOO attacks?]
One person can't hit it twice.
[Our WONWOO...]
Ace is here.
[★☆Today's ace is WONWOO,
going my way in v-ball☆★]
- Ace is here. / - He was resting and hits it
and gets hit himself.
[★☆Today's ace is WONWOO,
going my way in v-ball☆★]
He showed us things to look out for.
[★☆Today's ace is WONWOO,
going my way in v-ball☆★]
WONWOO, I will be in front.
[With WONWOO's performance(?)
Team JOSHUA 1 : 4 Team MINGYU]
Nice.
[With WONWOO's performance(?)
Team JOSHUA 1 : 4 Team MINGYU]
[Ace's reaction speed is slower than others...]
WONWOO...
WONWOO is the star.
Sigh. We can't do it like this!
[Current score] [Team JOSHUA 1 : 5 Team MINGYU]
Nice.
[WONWOO received it well this time]
Man.
[!@#$%^]
Nice.
[★2nd weak link enters★]
Hey.
Even the same team.
[Same team but strategy is a secret]
[And Team MINGYU saw something
and bursts out laughing?!]
[JOSHUA / born in 1995, born in LA]
[Big shock that the same team is a mafia(?)]
- But why is this so much fun? / - So fun.
[Weak links are all smiles]
[Match point] [Team JOSHUA 1 : 6 Team MINGYU]
HOSHI, save it.
WOOZI, pass it over.
[Since it's the match point,
being careful with each and every toss]
- Okay. / - Make it. / - Okay.
[Since it's the match point,
being careful with each and every toss]
- DK. / - Make sure.
- Slowly.
Shoot.
[! DK power spike !]
[- The end -]
Come here.
[MINGYU, SEUNGKWAN's blocking ceremony]
[About the time when chaotic
volleyball is about to end]
I can't go to sleep today.
[About the time when chaotic
volleyball is about to end]
It seems like SEUNGKWAN is so happy.
[At the archery zone?]
[JUN is doing archery]
[(Focused fingers)]
[Aiming the arrow carefully towards the target]
[Q. What do you do when you rest?]
When I rest?
I even went to an archery cafe
a couple of times in Korea.
There's a solo archery place but
I couldn't do it for a while.
[Took my gear]
So, I wish that I can use it this time if I can.
[At "In the SOOP"]
Are you going to bring your equipment?
[Q. Are you going to bring your own gear?]
Yes.
[❤]
[JUN brought this own gear]
[Left his gear at the archery zone]
[And finally lost in archery that
he couldn't do for a while]
[※ We blocked off the area around
the archery zone and filmed safely ※]
[JUN is obsessed with archery
not caring about morning or night]
[While JUNG is enjoying archery after a long time]
[WONWOO who changed into clothes
for the sauna]
[Brings sikhye and boiled eggs that are a must]
[Go go to the sauna]
[★☆Sauna that's made ONLY for SEVENTEEN☆★]
[First guest WONWOO enters]
Wow, it's so nice.
[♡]
[Closing the door so that the heat
doesn't seep out is a must!]
[First time entering the sauna,
picture to show it is a must❤]
[(Bragging good things to the members)]
[Ta-da] [I came to the sauna]
[(Should I enjoy it while lying down?)]
Wow, this must be really good.
I want to go in right away.
[(???)]
- WONWOO. / - You came? / - Hello.
[S.COUPS, JEONGHAN who heard the news entered]
It's so nice here.
I am getting sleepy.
It would be nicer tomorrow!
It's going to be really cold tomorrow.
- It's going to be cold tomorrow? / - Yes.
[It would be nicer tomorrow!
It's going to be really cold tomorrow]
I should come tomorrow, too.
- Here? Nice! / - It's really nice.
[I should come tomorrow, too]
- Yup. Is it locked? / - Open up.
[New guest who came to the sauna?!]
It works.
- It is really hot? / - No, it's not hot.
[DK, DINO who is dressed in sauna clothes enter]
- It's warm. / - It's warm.
What did you do? Did you guys do something
while we were working out?
[Volleyball]
I was by the fire over there...
[(Peeled egg goes to DINO's mouth)]
- I was at the campfire. / - You too?
You were at the campfire?
[(Peeled egg goes to DINO's mouth)]
S.COUPS, too?
Yes, I was there, too.
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
DK sweats really easily.
I am sweating a lot right now, too.
[Awesome]
Shiny.
[Finished getting used to the sauna]
[S.COUPS, DK are all glowing]
Why am I not sweating?
[Finished getting used to the sauna]
[S.COUPS, DK are all glowing]
I am not either. Is it not hot right now?
Why am I sweating so much?
[Sweat]
Was I here for an hour?
[(Experiencing the charcoal sauna alone)]
- I think you came first right now. / - I know.
I want to lie down.
No. You are going to get DK's sweat on you.
[JEONHAN's urgent voice?]
- Take it off.
- I don't want to.
- Aren't you going to shower anyway?
- I still don't want to.
[Playing a joke to him who doesn't
like getting sweat on himself]
[Wahhhhh T T]
He changed now. I'm disappointed.
[SEVENTEEN that's peaceful(?) today, too]
Wow, I should go now.
I am sweating so much!
Wait, are you okay?
[⤾ Shiny(?) S.COUPS]
- I should wash up because I'm so tired.
- You are getting hot, too? / - My body gets hot.
- Everyone enjoy and go.
- I'm cold.
- Good night. / - Good night. What are you doing?
[S.COUPS, JEONGHAN sauna OUT]
It really has the sauna vibe.
A cold breeze when someone opened the door.
[Sauna vibe from the door you open and close]
Oh, it's nice.
What do you think about this "In the SOOP"?
It is a different feeling than before, right?
I like this better.
- Me too. I think this "In the SOOP" is better.
- You like it more?
I think that's good about this "In the SOOP".
Since you are with the members,
you get to talk to the members no matter what.
[DINO likes having deep conversations
with the members]
That's so nice.
What did you talk about yesterday?
I don't remember because we drank...
But.
[(Kekekekeke)] [(Kekekekeke)]
- It's good to talk but you need to remember.
- I know.
- Doesn't it not matter even if you talk
if you can't remember?
- That's the point.
[Members don't know what to do
with DINO's new style of communicating]
I just like talking.
[Members don't know what to do
with DINO's new style of communicating]
You just like the fact that you talked.
Let's talk a lot from now on.
- Not remembering a single thing now.
- I know. He just likes the existence of it.
I'm kidding.
I really talked a lot with S.COUPS yesterday.
I think I get more honest the more I know.
[Time where he got to know more honestly about
members he thought he knew everything about]
That's why it was good.
[Time where he got to know more honestly about
members he thought he knew everything about]
Let's try a lot of things
and live happily... Let's do that.
Are you talking in your sleep?
[Sentiment is crashing down]
I...
[Emotions falling down]
- Just sweat it out. / - There's that.
[Blocks out the emotions]
When I am with the members,
from a certain moment...
I think my habit became to stay happy.
Feels like I can't calm down well.
I become really high energy.
But this is not fake.
I did that because I was really high energy.
I do that because I feel good.
DINO likes the members.
I want to keep on teasing
and making jokes.
["DINO likes the members"]
- I'm like that, too.
- I want to do skits when I'm with you.
[Members' emotions that he feels even
if they don't tell him]
- Yes. I know what you mean. / - You know, right?
[Members' emotions that he feels even
if they don't tell him]
But I don't do it if I think "it's too much"...
Those things between us...
I don't think we did.
[^^]
As expected, we go well together.
Really.
Wow, it's nice because I'm sweating.
I don't think I can do it now.
It's too hot.
No, stay a bit longer.
No, I am hot.
Who are you, dude!
[Who are you?]
I am the pacemaker at the sauna.
[As expected, the best pacemaker]
DK, you kind of have an Aladdin feeling.
[(Aladdin...?)]
[#How_to_have_a_fun_time_
in_the_sauna_even_when_you're_sweating]
[DK-ladin(?) and snake DINO show]
[(Attack there, too)]
[Perfect tiki-taka Kekeke]
- Oh, I'm sweating.
- Yes.
Why isn't the sweat clear?
I didn't put on any makeup.
It's weird.
- It's your toxins. The bad things.
- My toxins?
- You drank milk yesterday, right? It's that.
- Yes.
The police, right? There's a scammer here.
[Fraud telephone hotline 112]
Last 3 seconds.
1.
2.
- 3. Okay. Good job.
- No.
No.
[DINO, you stay here. We are going to go]
I want to go.
I really sweated a lot.
[As much as they withstood it,
wind that feels even cooler]
It's the best.
- Why? What? / - It's the best.
[Meets MINGYU+THE 8
who came to the sauna now]
- Why did you come now?
- Sauna is so nice.
I thought everyone wouldn't be able to go in.
- No. 6 people can go in.
- No. Can't go in.
- Really? / - 6 people is okay if you don't lie down.
- MINGYU, sweat is just...
[Five stars★★★★★]
[Three people's review of sauna
is filled with recommendations]
- I think I was really there for a long time.
- What?
- I was there from the beginning.
- You were really there for a long time.
- I was there first.
- What is this?
These are egg peels.
You go there and eat them.
[Friendship(?) where they share good things]
- Egg peels normally have good nutrients.
- You are going to go in?
[Speaking with eyes]
[Friendship(?) where they share good things]
If you're going to go in, go there MINGYU.
- If you bring sikhye and this from the lodge.
- Sikhye?
[Shares the ultimate tip]
[Bring sikhye from tavern
before entering the sauna]
- They don't have any inside.
- You can have this because I only had a sip.
[Shares the ultimate tip]
[Bring sikhye from tavern
before entering the sauna]
Do you want to have some sikhye before we go?
Let's have some.
There's sikhye?!
[So happy]
THE 8.
[Quickly shares the great news to THE 8]
- They have sikhye. / - There are egg peels, too.
- Then, sikhye...
[Quickly shares the great news to THE 8]
There have eggs, too.
Awesome.
It's so cool right now.
The fridge under this.
[Then, GET the sikhye right away]
You got rid of a lot of sweat.
- I sweated a lot. / - The best. / - You sweat a lot.
[Then, GET the sikhye right away]
- THE 8! Stay in there for 30 minutes.
- Oh, sure.
- Sikhye and then this is egg.
- Let's have a cup of sikhye.
- What else is there to eat?
[(People who are sincere about sikhye)]
- Eat first. WONWOO. / - There's makgeolli, too.
[Gulp]
[(Gathering of people who are sincere about sikhye)]
Eat.
[Gulp]
[(Gathering of people who are sincere about sikhye)]
It was hard, right?
Eat.
But it's so cool right now!
- Wow, crazy!
- MINGYU, there's makgeolli.
- You have to go crazy. / - Really crazy.
[Sharing and drinking the cool~ sikhye]
Let's hurry and go, THE 8.
Did you bring your phone and go in?
[Sharing and drinking the cool~ sikhye]
I brought my phone.
- But it wasn't that hot. / - Really crazy.
[(Angry because it's so good)]
So crazy.
- So crazy. / - Leave it out if you're
going to stay there for a long time.
[It's really crazy-ME!]
Crazy.
[CrazyME!!!]
Should we go then?
[With great expectations,
THE 8, MINGYU enter the sauna!]
Let's go.
[With great expectations,
THE 8, MINGYU enter the sauna!]
Wow, awesome!
[With great expectations,
THE 8, MINGYU enter the sauna!]
[Let's lie down right away~]
[Picture to show you were there
that you can't forget about]
[#Here_at_the_sauna]
[#Crazy^3^]
I am sweating right away.
[Sauna is getting hotter with the firewood burning]
- It's getting hotter, right? / - Yes.
This is really crazy.
Why didn't I use this yesterday?
I think the alcohol I drank yesterday is coming out.
[Feels like the alcohol is from yesterday
is finally coming out]
Really?
[Feels like the alcohol is from yesterday
is finally coming out]
Finally.
[Feels like the alcohol is from yesterday
is finally coming out]
Can't believe "In the SOOP" made this.
There's really nothing they can't make.
There's sikhye.
[Three who are done with the sauna
are already making a schedule for tomorrow(?)]
What I feel is that tomorrow...
[Three who are done with the sauna
are already making a schedule for tomorrow(?)]
- I feel like I would do it every day.
- Me too. I think I would do that, too. So nice.
Tell me when you do so I lock the door.
[^^]
- To lock the door? / - Yes.
- Let's take 4 best shots! / - Okay.
[With this fresh feeling]
DINO, you sit in the middle!
Treatment for the youngest!
Should we do this pose?
[Older members are following the youngest
and making the pose]
Nice.
[Older members are following the youngest
and making the pose]
1, 2.
[Older members are following the youngest
and making the pose]
3.
[(♨Finished showing off the sauna♨)]
[#All_sweated_out] [#Attended_sauna]
[#Going_to_go_every_day]
- Done.
Okay, let's go.
Wow! They're still singing?
It's a concert.
[Singing noise they heard before going
to the sauna is continuing]
[♩♪♬♪♩]
[HOSHI, SEUNGKWAN is singing a medley
of memory songs in the playroom!]
[♬ "Love Love Love" - HOSHI, SEUNGKWAN]
[(Original : Epik High feat. Yoong Jin of Casker /
Composed : Tablo, Mithra / Produced : Tablo)]
Okay, DJ Tukutz. Let's go.
[Today's DJ, HOSHI] [A fancy DJing performance]
[Site of the a fierce dance battle]
[Sharp movement]
[Sharp movement, HOSHI goes first]
[(Oh, you're pretty good?)]
[Perfect teamwork like they planned it in advance]
["Love Love Love" performance
where they lit the stage with is over]
I want to do a boy group song
from the past.
Boy group song from the past?
Memory boy. Memory boy.
Sounds good.
[(Move) Professor Boo's ego that
he forgot about (Move)]
"CLAP"?
- What? / - Do you remember?
[Body that moves as soon as the intro starts]
There was TEEN TOP's "Clap"
before SEVENTEEN's "CLAP".
[Short description]
[♬ "Clap" - WOOZI, SEUNGKWAN]
[(Original song : TEEN TOP /
Composed : SUPER CHANGDDAI /
Produced : SUPER CHANGDDAI)]
Yes.
[(Why? Do I look like the most exciting
person from the forest?)]
You're good.
[(Very satisfied)]
[Very immersed]
[BACK TO THE 2010]
Here.
Stop.
[You know here, right?]
♪ MAN
[MAN] [Laughing]
[(Satisfied)]
[♬ "Oh Yeah" - HOSHI, SEUNGKWAN]
[(Original sung : MBLAQ / Composed : RAIN /
Song : Taewan, RAIN, Jang Jae Min)]
[(They really play well)]
♪ Feels so sad
♪ No one in this world can replace you
♪ I'm someone who loves you
more than anyone else
[Perfect synchronization like they are hypnotized]
I am Lee Joon!
[⤤]
[Perfectly impersonates the ♡ face on stage]
[So nice]
[(Amazed)] [Peeks]
[Guys... Professor doesn't get tired]
Come on.
[DINO is reacting to the song ↷]
[Three people in audience discovered them first]
[(Look over there!)]
[(You want to join?)]
[Even after the bystanders MINGYU, DINO leave]
[Excited at the classic song party]
[Using the excited members' voice
who are at the party as a lullaby]
[JOSHUA who is sleeping well even
in this chaotic situation]
[After a long big of medleys from the past ends]
Let's go.
I went there a lot up until middle school.
[(JOSHUA is sleeping)]
[HOSHI, WOOZI leaves the playroom]
I don't think we go since we are singers.
[(JOSHUA is sleeping)]
[HOSHI, WOOZI leaves the playroom]
I don't know what to do.
VERNON.
[Found VERNON who was walking]
[U-turns right away ⤸]
Yo.
[Found VERNON who was walking]
[U-turns right away ⤸]
What did you do?
I am writing lyrics right now.
Oh! Which one?
The one that's coming out soon.
[Soon]
- Oh, that one?
- Yes.
[While the members were having fun, VERNON]
[Film day was before release day]
[Working hard on his first solo mixtape "Black Eye"]
[Even in the food zone where no one was at]
[Even at the fire pit]
[At the playroom]
I wasn't rearranging but fixing my lyrics.
[Even on his walk]
What is that?
Just the grammatical things and stuff.
[VERNON worked hard even in the forest
for good music]
Oh! I am going to try to sleep early today.
[Night at the forest that came in no time]
Good night!
[SEVENTEEN's sweet sleeping moment today, too]
Good night.
[♥]
[SEVENTEEN's sweet sleeping moment today, too]
- Good night. / - You too.
[♥]
[SEVENTEEN's sweet sleeping moment today, too]
[Night at the forest that's darker than in the city]
[Members turn off the lights
and fall asleep one by one]
[Everyone, good night~☾]
The vibes are so nice.
[On the other hand, the lawn is still loud]
Nice. It's nice because we lit up the fire.
Ta-da!
[Members gathered around
the fire pit being sentimental]
THE 8 is drinking, too.
[Members gathered around
the fire pit being sentimental]
[(Gulps)]
[(Sips, too)]
Really awesome. Awesome.
So nice.
Still from the sauna...
[Feels like the heat from the sauna is still there]
Isn't all of your bloating gone
after the sauna?
- I couldn't rid of it so... / - Only you...
- Because.
[^.T T]
I guess it won't fast because I ate a lot.
[(Did eat a lot for all of it to go away at once)]
In the tavern here,
they have marbles and ddakji.
[Marbles, tops, and ddakji are another memory]
Ddakji is fun.
I did a tea ceremony with Minghao.
[THE 8]
Bushuro...? What tea was it?
- Oolong tea. / - What was the name of the tea?
[Hehe]
- Oolong tea. / - Oolong tea.
Pu'er tea.
What?
[Kekeke]
And it's even oolong tea.
[Just]
I couldn't remember.
- I just threw it out in Chinese.
- Pu'er tea.
[Word Kekeke]
Is that Chinese?
[Keke]
[Couldn't think of it so said it in Chinese kekeke]
But there is that.
I don't do that when I am with my friends.
But when I am with my members,
I am sentimental like this
and even when I get in the mood...
[In the mood]
[...Hmm?]
There is that.
- That. / - Going like this.
[Completely agree]
- I keep on wanting to play games.
- That's because since we were trainees...
[Our own time where we want to joke around]
- Oh, right. We together... / - Oh right.
You made that.
- Yes.
- You made that.
I was walking around Gangnam Station
and both of us were annoyed at the same time.
At the same time.
[DK, DINO]
Hmm?! There was this that happened together.
[While DK, DINO walked along Gangnam Station]
- I still remember. / - I know.
[Memories from when he was
young that he can't forget about]
That left a strong impression.
[Memories from when he was
young that he can't forget about]
- It was you two? / - Yes.
[Memories from when he was
young that he can't forget about]
- This is a kindling, right?
- That...
No, that's a marshmallow.
[Stick]
Should we cook some marshmallows?
Yes. Let's grill some. Give me one, too.
Give me one *kat.
Stick me one, too.
Save me.
[(Save the marshmallow~)]
[Sudden skit with one marshmallow]
- But why is DINO putting it in so deep. / - It hurts.
- It hurts.
[#Mood] [This is when you want to play]
I want to do a lot.
- To do a lot?
DK, I am going to put it here.
[(Marshmallow)]
Can you hold it like Arthur?
[Arthur DK that appeared at "In the SOOP"]
How do you grill it?
- There are people who are good at doing it.
- Browning it perfectly.
MINGYU, the person who is good is
right in front of me.
- Is that you? / - Yes.
[(That person is me)]
You need to turn it lightly.
[Master pose]
DINO grilled it well on top.
[Grilling marshmallow]
[Discovered DINO's new specialty]
- You're good at grilling. / - On top.
[Grilling marshmallow]
[Discovered DINO's new specialty]
Just do a bit more lightly... Oh, yes. Done.
[Looking]
[Oh?]
[Torch that burned on top of the marshmallow]
Hey! The last one...
You needed to take it out
but you put it in some more.
[(The marshmallow)]
It was perfect.
It was on fire!
[Completely]
Can't eat that.
[Oh?!]
[Oh?! Wow!]
[(What is that kekekekekeke)]
What are you doing?
VERNON didn't sleep.
[VERNON finished working on the mixtape]
Yo.
It's going to be hard if you stay there.
Really?
It's going to be kind of hard
because the wind is blowing southwest.
Southwest.
[Southwest direction kekeke]
Okay, southwest.
[VERNON searches it right away]
Northeasterly wind?
It would be legendary if southwest is right.
Okay.
[Oh? Oh?!]
Is it right?
Hey! Southwest is right!
- Hey! Southwest is right. / - DINO.
[Legendary]
- You were a professor.
- What?
I told you that I check the wind.
[Getting hit by the wind]
I told you since we played kickball.
- Southwest. / - I am checking the wind today.
[Getting hit by the wind]
I was hoping that you would get it right, too.
[Don't know why but VERNON was
hoping that he would get it right, too]
I was spacing out and looking at the fire.
[Pfft] ["Southwest" that makes him
laugh thinking about it again]
Why is it funny?
[Pfft] ["Southwest" that makes him
laugh thinking about it again]
- No, you're just doing that. / - Really. / - Sorry.
[(Just said one thing)]
Just laugh.
- You are just at a high level now. Just.
- This is not funny.
[(Funny)]
But people burst out laughing
when he opens his mouth!
- You became a happiness evangelist.
- Now, he...
- His level is really high. Level's really high.
- Level's really high.
DINO wasn't this funny long time ago.
[Funniest member these days]
But he's really...
- I think he's funny.
- Yes, he got funny all of a sudden.
[Funniest member these days = DINO]
It's coming up. You see it, right?
Oh? Tree?
- I need to go in. Good night!
- Good night.
[Walking around now]
- You didn't see JOSHUA, right?
- JOSHUA?
Shoes are here.
These are JOSHUA's shoes.
He's sleeping.
[Found JOSHUA in the playroom's
sweet dream zone]
- You're sleeping here?
- Yes.
Are you going to sleep here?
I slept here!
[(Pat)]
[Playroom]
What should we eat?
But I also got kind of hungry, too.
[Playroom]
Mian bao xia?
- We have Mian bao xia? / - Yes.
[Take Mian bao xia]
I want to eat sweet and sour chicken, too.
[Take Mian bao xia and sweet and sour chicken]
- Sweet and sour chicken is so nice. / - Yes.
- Should we go to the food zone?
- Should we?
- Let's take a look a bit.
- Let's look at it a bit and come back.
[Only looking and coming back]
We need to go once out of respect.
[JOSHUA, SEUNGKWAN going to
the food zone out of respect]
Why is he laughing so much?
[...?]
- I know. / - Does it look fun?
[DK who walked with SEUNGKWAN
is sudeenly a sleep mode]
[Like that, JOSHUA and SEUNGKWAN
head towards the food zone...]
This is VERNON's voice.
[Like that, JOSHUA and SEUNGKWAN
head towards the food zone...]
I guess he's still not sleeping.
[Like that, JOSHUA and SEUNGKWAN
head towards the food zone...]
I guess he's not sleeping.
The tree is now...
I guess the humidity is leaving now.
[Sincere talks are going back
and forth in the fire pit zone]
Smoke is coming up.
[Sincere talks are going back
and forth in the fire pit zone]
If my father didn't dance and sang really well,
- I would have sang, too.
- I'm sure.
I think it's the coolest that I became a singer.
- That's interesting for me, too.
- Me too.
I didn't have any thoughts of being a singer.
You didn't have any thoughts of being a singer.
Yes, I didn't.
Aside from having any thoughts
of being a singer or not...
- Just wasn't in my sight.
- Just a singer...?
That's just good.
[Singer...?]
I am here... "Firefighter"!
[(Suddenly)]
Yes, yes!
- It's kind of like that.
- It's like this.
It's that feeling.
Didn't even think or consider it.
But somehow became a trainee.
That's kind of interesting for me, too.
When I do an interview...
"When did you start dreaming
about being an artist?"
It's not that for me.
About quitting...
[(Trainee)]
I didn't accept my pride.
Let's bear it and try it.
What is this? It was kind of like this.
["Let's bear it and try it! What is this?!"]
Hearing that, I right now...
The thought that goes by right now...
[To me]
Nevertheless, I think I am grateful
that we are still here right now doing this.
Yes.
All these different people gathered...
[Such different 13 boys]
Debuted and 2, 3 years and now 1, 2 years...
This is how it became.
- We are looking for that.
- That's possible.
What it feels like when we were trainees
and when we were doing modern dance...
We had dance lessons for 4 hours
each for two sessions.
- 8 hours.
- That was really... Man.
That day is just...
It's not where you think
"My skills would get better by doing this".
- It's heavy. The day is heavy.
- Let's just live the day. Let's bear it...
- How did we really live like that?
- And if we work really hard like that...
I would have been able to bear it if I had
the certainty that I would debut as SEVENTEEN.
Of course.
But there's nothing.
There's nothing. You don't know
what's going to happen tomorrow
- but we lived that hard.
- Whether we're doomed or not when we debut.
[Don't know what's going to happen tomorrow]
No one knows.
That's why 40, 50, 60 trainees all leave
[13 members that withstood that time]
and this is what was left.
- We need to respect our young selves.
- Just bearing it.
["We need to respect to our young selves"]
To look at one thing really positively,
there's that.
Our schedules are really hard right now, too.
There's that thought,
"We were able to do it then."
That's true.
I was late to school once.
There was a time when I got in trouble for a month.
But do you know what
the punishment for a month was?
Make one verse of a song per day and go.
Which one? What?
"One verse of a song" a day.
That's why you did a remix of "11:11".
[The backstory of "11:11" remix(?)]
That's why I remixed "11:11".
- That's why he remixed that.
- I. I started. I started that.
[The backstory of "11:11" remix(?)]
- Really? / - I was so bored.
SEUNGKWAN, come here. I was doing that...
[The backstory of "11:11" remix(?)]
I wouldn't gain. Get full even if I ate.
But there were a lot of people
where they would tell them to do things
that didn't make sense.
MINGYU.
[MINGYU,]
- SEUNGKWAN. / - Oh, yes.
[MINGYU, SEUNGKWAN]
But if you look at it,
it might have been helpful.
- So funny. / - It's such a memory.
- In the practice room then.
[Memory talk that doesn't stop]
I couldn't sleep a lot then
so I went into the bathroom to sleep.
He would come in there urgently.
[(Manager)]
But I wasn't there.
[He came]
So, everyone was all over the place.
Where is DINO? The door is locked.
[Interested]
"He is 100 percent sleeping!"
- We thought at that time he's sleeping
when the bathroom door is locked.
- Yes.
- Of course.
- "He's sleeping." So, S.COUPS...
He's was so mad.
[(14 years old DINO at that time)]
Came out, "What were you doing?"
Sorry! I fell asleep while I was pooping.
So, "I was so tired..."
[Kekekekekekekekekekekeke]
He knows I am so tired.
[Fear at that time that won the shame kekeke]
- A 14 year old couldn't say,
"I dozed off because I was so tired." / - Really.
[Fear at that time that won the shame kekeke]
- What human says that.
- What dude! What dude!
Oh, my stomach hurts so much!
[What dude(?)]
[(Ugh...)]
[(Zzzz...)]
I was being smart and said that!
- Did you get tranquilized?
- No.
Even if you stay up for 3 days...
[Trip down memory lane that's fun
no matter how many times you talk about]
- You don't sleep while you poop.
- You would rather...
[So funny]
You should have said that there was
no toilet paper while pooping.
[So funny]
Crazy.
So, S.COUPS...!
- He said it. / - I think that's S.COUPS?
[...Isn't that S.COUPS?]
No?
Is it S.COUPS?
[...Isn't that S.COUPS?]
- Speak of the devil.
- Tiger.
- Really speak of the devil.
- Yes. Speak of the devil.
I'm getting goosebumps. Goosebumps.
[S.COUPS that appears whenever
you talk about him Kekeke]
Funny.
[S.COUPS that appears whenever
you talk about him Kekeke]
- So funny.
- Speak of the devil.
Funny. Funny.
- That was the most I used my brain in that state.
- I know.
That's the only excuse that I can say.
- We were talking about when we were trainees.
Trainee talk.
- Trainee talk.
That middle school kid...
But do you know what gives
me more goosebumps?
He doesn't get old after 10 years.
[Time]
That face is...
- His face is when he was a trainee.
- It's exactly that.
[He looks the same as when he
did when he was a trainee!]
- He looks the same. / - We look the same as then.
[He looks the same as when he
did when he was a trainee!]
Really the same.
[He looks the same as when he
did when he was a trainee!]
I thought that I was hearing things
when I was sleeping.
[(?)]
Laughing sounds...
- It was really quiet, this moment...
- I heard things and then I didn't.
- There's nothing better than things about the past.
- Really.
- Side dish is really just old talk.
- It's honestly giving us that we got old.
It's not even less than a year ago.
[Memories from less than 10 years ago]
- No. Less than 10 years ago.
- About 10 years ago. / - 10 years ago.
[About 10 years ago]
It's really about 10 years ago.
[Memories from about 10 years ago]
Should we make some kimchi fried rice
and go to sleep?
No. We need to hold it in.
What do you mean hold it?
Don't hold back.
This place is heaven.
- Eat if you want to eat.
Lose weight if you want to.
- The whispers of a devil.
[At that time, in the food zone]
[JOSHUA, SEUNGKWAN's strange
movements where they're not holding back
because they're in the forest?!]
Okay.
[JOSHUA, SEUNGKWAN's strange
movements where they're not holding back
because they're in the forest?!]
SEUNGKWAN.
Did you get the feeling?
I got it.
You got the feeling?
I am getting a bit faster.
I know! If there's a time machine now,
[While JOSHUA and SEUNGKWAN
is finding the feeling(?)]
I was to tell 10 years old DINO.
[While JOSHUA and SEUNGKWAN
is finding the feeling(?)]
To Chan.
[While JOSHUA and SEUNGKWAN
is finding the feeling(?),
three people have a nice walk]
What?
[While JOSHUA and SEUNGKWAN
is finding the feeling(?),
three people have a nice walk]
- Chan, it's okay. / - S.COUPS.
[While JOSHUA and SEUNGKWAN
is finding the feeling(?),
three people have a nice walk]
- Boil and cook it.
- You just need to live and withstand it.
Yes, that's right.
- We are going around once here.
- No, why does it smell like sesame oil?
[Covering the forest in the night]
The savory smell...
[Sesame oil that is covering
the forest in the night...?!]
I want to eat.
[Sesame oil that is covering
the forest in the night...?!]
What is that smoke?
What's up with the smoke?
[What is that smoke?!]
What are you guys doing?
There are clouds in here.
[Cloud controversy]
There's some kind of cloud on top.
Hey! There's a cloud. Window!
[Cloud controversy]
What? What do we do? Open it.
[The cloudy smoke that is filled in the food zone...]
There are clouds here.
[Is oil smoke]
We died and are born again.
- Why?
- No.
The oil was so strong in the beginning
and it burned right away.
Are you okay?
It's okay. It didn't burn.
[SEUNGKWAN can't close his mouth]
[Look at the color]
The visual is awesome.
- I hope that it's good.
- It smells like kkanpunggi.
Kkanpunggi.
It kind of looks like kkanpunggi.
Put some green onions and
powdered red pepper on it, too.
[Recommend green onions&powdered red pepper!]
Let's chop some peppers.
- Sweet and sour chicken.
- It's sweet and sour chicken?
[Chicken was successful in getting revived
with JOSHUA's sauce!]
- You are good at making it. / - Me too.
[Chicken was successful in getting revived
with JOSHUA's sauce!]
Let's go.
You go there first.
I will do the dishes and go.
- At 3 in the morning... There won't be an idol
who fries chicken? Right?
- It's really spicy.
Amazing.
But try this. It's crazy good.
Hurry up and put the meat in.
Let's eat when the members come.
No one brought the chopsticks.
[※But there are no chopsticks※]
You're right.
- Good work.
Did you bring chopsticks?
Don't you think the members took them?
[Chopsticks?]
Did you bring chopsticks?
- No chopsticks. / - Oh man.
[♥]
There's no Co* zero, too.
[♥] [♥]
Do you guys not have hands?
I have SEUNGKWAN.
[!>.<]
I guess they are coming.
WOOZI, DINO, SEUNGKWAN,
JOSHUA, MINGYU, S.COUPS, DK.
DK?
MINGYU, S.COUPS, SEUNGKWAN.
[Calmly gets chopsticks and heads to the fire pit]
Can you get one and give it to me?
Wait.
This is also a vibe.
[(Om nom nom)]
The song is nice.
It feels like it's not cooked
because it's tender to me.
[(Chicken meat)]
It's so tender.
I am going to go home when that all burns.
[Sweet and sour party at 3 a.m. in the morning]
I think it's going to be there until the morning.
Why?
Why do you like it so much?
Just at this time...
I like that all the members are here!
I slept in the playroom.
- Why does everyone go sleep at the playroom?
- No, the playroom...
- You sleep really well there.
- You sleep really well at the playroom. / - You do.
[Experienced sleeper1] [Experienced sleeper2]
[Experienced sleeper3]
- You sleep well there. / - The temperature is perfect.
[Experienced sleeper1] [Experienced sleeper2]
[Experienced sleeper3]
You can't get out when you lie down in the sofa.
[Temperature that brings sleep
and the comfiness of the sofa]
And you know how you can't sleep if it's too quiet?
I know what that is.
So, when the members are talking
loudly in the side...
- If I am sleeping and they're being funny...
- I would say it's funny and lose my energy.
A couple of ballads come out in a row.
Then, you go!
[Into your dreams]
But I think that SEUNGKWAN is really on
his cheating day whenever he comes here.
[Totally agrees]
- Yes. / - Completely.
Anyway, WOOZI... Didn't you see me
drinking for three or four days straight?
[WOOZI stays with the members in the morning]
- Yes! You're here often. / - Right?
Right? Starting from Singapore.
[(Charges his breath)]
If a big piece of wood is going to burn...
- I think we need to stay until morning.
- That...
When you blow it with your breath...
[TIP from a self proclaimed breath master(?)]
You need to blow it for a long time
with a medium strength breath.
Light as possible.
[TIP from a self proclaimed breath master(?)]
At least for 5 seconds.
Look carefully.
[And demonstration that he shows himself]
Don't your eyes burn?
Closer.
- Go a bit more.
- Bit more closer.
[(?! Kekeke)]
- Look. / - You're good.
- You're good. / - It burns right away.
[Fire that burns strong]
What is this?
This is DINO.
[^O^]
I hope that he really burns.
I really don't know about anyone else.
I think I would beat SEUNGKWAN.
- I will bring it if you beat me in a fight today.
- You! You die. You die and I will die.
[(Requests in a life or death fight)]
He's nice so he can't say,
"No, I can beat you".
- But he really thinks that he will lose.
- What!
You think that I am like this because I'm scared?!
[(He's a complete fighter)]
Kind of scared. Kind of scared.
You worked hard in pumping weights?
No, aside from all of that...
But I...
SEUNGKWAN.
[Taking this mood and saying his honest thoughts]
There's a lot that I learn as the youngest.
- You?
- Yes.
- From us?
- When you're on a team.
Yes, really.
Because the good thing about
being the youngest is that.
[What DINO thinks is a good thing
about being SEVENTEEN's youngest]
Some members lived this kind of life
and others lived this kind of life.
[The fact that he can get different kinds
of energy from 12 members]
I learn a lot from that.
[The fact that he can get different kinds
of energy from 12 members]
But DINO, that...
It's not because you're the youngest.
There's something that I learn
from the younger members, too.
Like how you feel something while you look at us,
just things around me.
You realize things while looking at the 12 members.
[Not because you're the youngest but it's
possible since you're a member of a team]
It's not different because you're the youngest.
[Not because you're the youngest but it's
possible since you're a member of a team]
I see.
[Not because you're the youngest
but it's possible because you're a member of a team]
I realize a lot, too.
Of course! I realize things because
I'm one member of a team, too.
["That's why I am so grateful to the members"]
- Yes, that's right. / - I think so.
That's why I am so grateful.
["That's why I am so grateful to the members"]
I'm going to be honest.
I think that all 13 of us are the same.
What's the same?
S.COUPS has more experience
because he's 2 years older than me?
I'm sure he did when he was young.
Since I was in middle school,
we went through the same things.
[13 of them headed towards the same
thing since they were trainees]
We're the same.
[13 of them headed towards the same
thing since they were trainees]
I...
[13 of them headed towards the same
thing since they were trainees]
Since he's 2 years older than me,
he went through this so I will soon.
To be honest, you might feel that physically.
[Different, various energy that
came from the same experience]
All 13 of us are very different.
Members do it like this. He does it like this.
[We fill our weak points while looking
at each other in aligned with each other]
It's not a problem with age
but I think it's a problem with the person.
[We fill our weak points while looking
at each other in aligned with each other]
It's the character's problem.
[We fill our weak points while looking
at each other in aligned with each other]
But I thought about that.
The worries while living as SEVENTEEN.
My own personality while living by myself
and I feel like it's kind of changing.
That's why I was very courageous and said
what I said when I drank tea with you.
What did you say...?
[(!)] [(Kek)] [(Kek)] [(Kek)] [(Kek)]
- I don't remember. / - You really...
There's absolutely no nutrients.
[(DINO hunter)]
What was it?
Is it okay for me to be upset?
What did he say?
- So, there were a couple of things.
- When we talked about each other.
[Overload on topics]
He's upset.
No, I am not upset.
I will pay for "In the SOOP"
and watch it separately.
Yes.
It was nice today.
As long as we were happy.
[SEVENTEEN's time where it
was hotter than day passed]
[In the meantime, the day breaks]
We said that we would stay until
the big piece of wood is done burning but it's done.
- Keep the promise.
- Unbelievable.
[Stayed up all night because
it's been a while talking like this]
[Now moving to the sleep zone really to sleep]
[Quiet and peaceful then any other time]
["In the SOOP 2" 3rd morning]
[Members are sleeping even while
the sunlight coming in through the window]
[Everyone doesn't know the world
and is sleep mode]
[Wiggling]
[zzZZ]
[When it seemed like wouldn't wake up soon]
[One who woke up first]
[THE 8 who woke up first]
[Place that he heads to with a light step?]
[It's the food zone]
There is no one.
[THE 8's breakfast menu
on the 3rd day at the forest?]
It's here. Awesome.
[THE 8's breakfast menu
on the 3rd day at the forest?]
[Chinese style jajangmyeon
where he adds chopped up pork belly!]
[THE 8 style Chinese jajangmyeon]
[1. Puts chopped up pork belly, green onions,
minced garlic, and sauce in a pan and stir-fry them]
[While the sauce is made,
gets the egg to eat with it ready]
[Add green onions to the egg water,
stir-fry it, and you're done~]
[THE 8 style Chinese jajangmyeon]
[2. Add noodles into the boiling water and boil it]
[3. Done when you put cucumbers
and sauce on the cooked noodles]
[THE 8's breakfast meal is done]
Should I try it?
[★Picture is necessary before you eat★]
[(Should I eat now~)]
THE 8.
You came?
Good morning.
Yes.
It's good?
I want to try it.
[Tries a bite after coming beside THE 8]
A bite of meat.
It's good.
I don't want to eat toast anymore.
[Exclamation that comes out whenever he eats]
- Should I try this? / - Yes.
It's so good.
- It's not bad, right?
- Yes, it's good.
What do you call that? Just that.
- Is that jajangmyeon in China? / - Yes.
[Kind of unfamiliar but THE 8's jajangmyeon is perfect]
This is the real jajangmyeon.
[(Happy because he ate it deliciously-)]
[Someone who is coming into the food zone]
Mr. 8? It is THE 8.
- YO!
- Good morning.
- VERNON, eat with me.
- Sounds good.
- VERNON. / - YO!
[THE 8 Ver.]
- Did you sleep well? / - Yes.
It's nice because it's sweet.
[SEVENTEEN's breakfast that's
sweet from the morning]
Of course, DK.
[SEVENTEEN's breakfast that's
sweet from the morning]
But today...
- It did get colder, right? Right? / - Yes.
["In the SOOP" weather that got cold]
It got colder now.
What did you put in here to make?
This...
Doubanjiang!
No soy milk?
[Chinese traditional soy sauce]
Doubanjiang?
[(Confused)]
- Doban. Doubanjiang. / - Doubanjiang.
Gangdoenjang?
- It's kind of similar and just...
- Doenjang sauce went in it.
What do you think, VERNON? It's good, right?
I haven't tried it yet.
Always like asking before eating.
[(JEONGHAN)]
Should I say it's the anticipation...?
[Giving before eating]
Is it worth eating?
It's good.
[Sound that tells VERNON's truth Hehe]
- DK, what is your plan today?
- Me?
Later, I am just...
I am thinking about taking my camera...
And just thinking?
I don't exactly have plans...
That's good.
- It's better to have no plans here. / - Is that so?
[No plans is eventually plans on "In the SOOP"]
I guess I'm a J.
I feel kind of worried if I don't have a plan.
[(INFP)]
- No, there's a plan even if you're a P.
- Aren't you a J?
[(INFP)]
There is nobody who doesn't have any plan.
- You know, right? / - That's true.
[ISFJ (Realistic)]
What are you doing?
[(Smack smack~ ♪♩♬)]
[Comes back with a spoon and a space walk]
[VERNON is being VERNON, inhales the bowl]
You're so happy if they eat so well, right?
I called him. Really so good.
[(Purposely)]
Because...
If you don't purposely make him food...
[VERNON]
- He just puts jam on bread and that's it.
- I know.
That's why you think about him when you eat.
[(So)]
- You don't think about me?
- You want to make food for him.
You eat on your own.
Still.
I still hope that you think about me.
I will think about you then.
[Hehehe]
It's always the four of us in the morning.
[About the time when "In the SOOP"
official four breakfast members are done]
I think only the four of us eat breakfast.
[About the time when "In the SOOP"
official four breakfast members are done]
I think so.
[About the time when "In the SOOP"
official four breakfast members are done]
Right?
There's no time.
[◀◀◀Pre-meeting]
[Q. New hobby that you have these days?]
New hobby is mountain climbing.
[◀◀◀Pre-meeting]
[Q. New hobby that you have these days?]
Bike riding!
So, I want to wake up at "In the SOOP"
and make food and go to the mountain...
[(Want)]
Was it about 6 months ago?
[Bike hobby that he started to
have since beginning of 2022]
I started to get interested.
[Bike hobby that he started to
have since beginning of 2022]
I got a license right before our American tour
and I would practice.
[Bike hobby that he started to
have since beginning of 2022]
I would only ride it where
there was a lot of cars, buildings and stuff.
I have wanted to ride it at a place
where you could see nature.
I think we only need to bring water.
[(Mountain climbing stick+1)]
VERNON!
[Today's mountain climbing members
are THE 8, SEUNGKWAN, VERNON]
- Let's go. / - Yes.
[Today's mountain climbing member
is THE 8, SEUNGKWAN, VERNON]
I think that we will need some kind of sugar.
- Should we take some chocolate?
- Yes.
- Just in case. / - You know never when we go up.
[Prepares chocolate just in case]
Where is that?
- Let's go to the food zone and take it.
- We'll be back.
- Or should we go together?
- Let's go together.
Aren't all of our mountain
climbing styles so different?
[#SEVENTEEN #THE_8_SEUNGKWAN_VERNON]
[#Way_different #Mountain_climbing_look #OOTD]
- I didn't think about going to the mountain.
- But this...
[#SEVENTEEN #THE_8_SEUNGKWAN_VERNON]
[#Way_different #Mountain_climbing_look #OOTD]
These are mountain climbing clothes.
[(Jeans) (Flower print) (Navy)]
- Wind... / - This is right.
You don't need to bring a lot.
Yes, let's just bring a little bit.
- There are tangerines, too. / - Tangerines?
[🍊]
Yes.
- Should we bring tangerines?
- Tangerines are nice.
Let's bring 4.
[Chocolates and tangerines go into the bag~]
If we bring too much...
I'm so sorry but cold brew from the karaoke.
[I can't forget about my cold brew
when I go mountain climbing]
- Okay! Bring everything that you want to bring...
- I will bring some coffee.
[Kekeke]
- Bring coffee, too? / - Yes, coffee...
[(Amazed eyes)]
- Really? / - Okay, let's go.
[Scans the snack corner]
[(Is there anything else to bring...)]
I feel really secure because
I brought my coffee right now.
You right now...
You are going to fill up calories
and to get rid of them.
This is normally how it is.
This is how normally mountain climbing is.
[Suspicious of SEUNGKWAN's purpose
of mountain climbing]
Eating more while going is mountain climbing.
[Suspicious of SEUNGKWAN's purpose
of mountain climbing]
- Let's go.
- Yes.
This is quite heavy.
I put in too many snacks.
We will go mountain climbing and come back.
Let's go mountain climbing!
[THE 8, SEUNGKWAN,
VERNON really leaves to go mountain climbing]
It's such a nice weather to go running.
[(Bike)]
[WONWOO calls someone]
- Oh, WONWOO...
- Let's go.
[⤤ S.COUPS]
- Oh, WONWOO. / - Let's go.
[WONWOO's bike mate is S.COUPS, MINGYU]
- MINGYU just woke up and is showering.
Let's leave after he's done. / - Yes.
[WONWOO's bike mate is S.COUPS, MINGYU]
MINGYU, let's wash up.
MINGYU!
Why?
It's 2 p.m.
When did you wake up?
[Aftermath of the late night talk
hit hard for S.COUPS, MINGYU]
Let's go.
[Aftermath of the late night talk
hit hard for S.COUPS, MINGYU]
But I just slept right now, too.
[Aftermath of the late night talk
hit hard for S.COUPS, MINGYU]
I slept until 20.
Let's go.
The weather is so nice.
[♪]
Let's go.
[Let's hurry up and leave before it's even later!]
[Mountain team that left the forest?]
Oh, it's pretty.
- This drive is nice, too.
- I know.
You normally go mountain climbing
and eat baeksuk on the bottom and leave.
[Necessary corner]
Really!
[So cool]
You would really have no stress
if you lived some place here.
I don't think there's much to worry about either.
It's nice!
- The mountains are really nice.
- I know, it's kind of...
It's a perfect day to go mountain climbing.
[The leaves are colorful]
The leaves are falling.
[Good day to climb Cheongnyangsan]
We arrived.
Let's go!
I'm going mountain climbing.
[(Half excited half nervous)]
[Starts walking the entrance of the path]
Wait.
The slope... From the start...
[The slope is no joke...?]
Are we going to there?
[Today's climb]
[Past "Cheongnyangsa Temple"
in the middle of Cheongnyangsan]
[Today's climb]
[Past "Cheongnyangsa Temple"
in the middle of Cheongnyangsan]
There...
[Today's climb]
[Past "Cheongnyangsa Temple"
in the middle of Cheongnyangsan]
- Is that possible in an hour?
- Will we be able to go?
[Today's climb]
[Past "Cheongnyangsa Temple"
in the middle of Cheongnyangsan
and course where they go up
to the sky bridge up at 800 meters]
- I think we need to do some stretches before
we start going up there.
- Yes. We need to do some stretches.
[Before they start climbing, stretching is a must!]
Then, let's go there...
Let's do it on a flat spot!
Here?
[Arrives at VERNON PICK for stretching spot]
Let's stretch out our bodies for a bit.
It's going to be hard today.
We're stretching here?
[VERNON just puts his back down first]
[Stretching out in their own way]
- Man! Throw out this bag. It's already heavy.
- Give it to me.
[...]
No. Let's switch while we go some.
[(Myself an hour before regretting)]
- No, you need to eat it all.
- Me?
Why did I bring so much?
Snacks...
[Found the climbing stick]
- This is heavy. / - I will take this.
[Yes! Got rid of one thing...]
Three water.
- Let's go.
[Let's Go]
But still...
When there was a lot of snow or it was humid...
- It's a relief we didn't come then.
- Yes.
Hallasan, I...
- I went up there in March. / - Yes.
[VERNON went up Hallasan
when it was covered in snow]
- The road was still covered in snow in March.
- Yes.
[VERNON went up Hallasan
when it was covered in snow]
Since it's cold.
- I am trying to conquer one mountain at a time.
- You are?
[Mountain lover THE 8 is doing a challenge
do go up all the mountains]
I went to Bukhansan now.
You are talking like you are going to
go to Mount Everest or something.
No, just...
In my standards,
I'm climbing a high mountain one at a time.
[Climbing list where he's
going to stack the standards]
Mountain climbing in the olden times
wasn't going up a mountain
but climbing one.
We are climbing one.
[Let's work hard in doing it]
The sky is so pretty.
[THE 8 looks at the sky and trees within nature]
Trees.
In between.
Poet THE 8.
- The sunlight that falls in between.
- Wow, pretty.
This is what it is here.
[(Need to take a picture)]
- SEUNGKWAN, get it with your eyes. / - No.
- Get it with your eyes and
treasure it with your heart.
- Why?
You don't know how nice it is
when you look at your gallery later.
[(I want to treasure a picture!!!)]
[SEUNGKWAN feeling the mountain
with his whole body]
But this mountain is nice.
[Going up the mountain while looking at the view]
- It's pretty. / - Yes. / - Really.
What is this place? Buddhist?
Yes, Cheongnyangsa Temple
that's in Cheongnyangsan.
[Arrived at today's pitstop Cheongnyangsa]
So pretty.
You dress code is perfect today.
I don't know who's the flower.
Who's the flower?
[I'm here!]
Let's go!
[THE 8 is satisfied with the time
he's spending with nature]
I am so happy.
[THE 8 is satisfied with the time
he's spending with nature]
My heart feels so peaceful.
[THE 8 is satisfied with the time
he's spending with nature]
[Bye Cheongnyangsa~ Go Go to the next course]
Wow! Now, it's the mountain path!
The mood changes suddenly.
[(?)]
This is the real quiet time...
[And continues...]
Now really...
Time of silence.
[And continues... Quiet time]
[♬"Uphill" - THE 8, SEUNGKWAN, VERNON]
[(Original song: JUNG-IN, Yoon Jong Shin /
Composed: Yoon Jong Shin /
Produced: Yoon Jong Shin, Lee Eun Hee)]
[Only thing you hear is sound of their breath...]
[Before they went up]
[Let's remember their smiles
before they went up(^^)]
♪ Only occasionally when the wind is blowing
Look at the distant landscape
♪ As beautiful as we have come
[Rest a bit while you were walking]
[When you keep on climbing and climbing]
Oh! The sky bridge is in front of us!
[Sky bridge that is finally front of their eyes]
[Members are at a loss of words]
Wow, it's so pretty.
[At an altitude of 800m]
[Sky bridge that connects
Jaranbong Peak and Seonhakbong Peak]
Why didn't I know that this place was in Korea?
[At an altitude of 800m]
[Sky bridge that connects
Jaranbong Peak and Seonhakbong Peak]
Awesome.
[Amazement that just comes out]
- Awesome. / - What is that? / - So pretty.
Is that a village?
[Feeling the fresh winds]
[Scenery that they fill with their
eyes while filling the fresh winds]
Really awesome.
Look.
MINGYU really can't cross this.
[Mountain's vastness that pierces your heart]
We are in the same altitude as the cloud right now.
Let's take a picture.
[Mountain's vastness that pierces your heart]
[Treasure this moment]
I am going to be happy for a while
looking at the pictures.
Since there's no data on the plane.
Even watching dramas...
[Memory]
I look at my gallery when I'm bored.
[Memory that they will look at often]
Even though I saw them all the time,
the old ones...
[Memory that they will look at often]
I look at the once.
I am not bloated anymore. No?
[Satisfied]
Yes.
So nice.
["So nice" keeps on coming out and
where that's not a waste of time]
- THE 8!
- Huh?
Here...
It's cool.
- Why?
- It's Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongsangbuk-do here.
[This place's address]
Myeongho-myeon
[Address here: Myeongho-myeon,
Bonghwa-gun, Gyeongsangbuk-do
- It's Myeongho-myeon?
- Myeongho-myeon.
- Myeongho-myeon!
It's a mountain that we needed to come to today.
Is this the road that we go down now?
[Now, it's time to go downhill]
Be careful your knees.
[Sweet]
[(Careful not to fall)]
[(Phew)]
Done.
[(Phew)] [(Ha...)]
Done!
This is a 2 hour and a half course.
[Short but long 2.5 hour journey is over]
- Flat land. / - Over.
[Done coming down!]
It was fun!
[Happy]
Clear.
Good job.
It's perfect if we go back, eat, and drink tea.
But
baeksuk after mountain climbing is so good.
[Baeksuk after mountain climbing?]
It's really good.
[Baeksuk after mountain climbing? That's a must]
Let's go!
[To go eat baeksuk!]
[Arrive at the baeksuk restaurant]
[(Keeps on recharging with vegetables)]
[Nom]
You can't eat like this?
I can't really eat vegetables.
Amazing.
[★✩Baeksuk enters✩★]
It's chicken. Chicken.
More than chicken leg, you know the back bone.
Here.
[(VERNON, you eat first)]
Where should we put the bones?
VERNON, there's salt, right?
Dip it in salt that's in front of you.
Okay, thank you for the food.
Great job.
Nice.
[(You eat a lot, too)]
Wow! My favorite part.
Man, this is really...
- Awesome.
- Can you show the camera?
- This is really, wow. / - This is really...
[Ne-at deboning⤣]
We did really well to eat here.
[Very NICE to eat baeksuk after climbing]
- Tell me. / - Do you hear me?
[Bike team in the meantime?]
Ah. Ah. Ah.
[Talking possible] [Connected mics to the helmets]
It's heavy.
[(Bickering)]
[Brrr~ Turns on the bike engine]
I'm going to fart a bit.
Let's go!
[WONWOO takes the lead]
[Smiles]
♪ Lap around the block
[Officially starts riding]
[Laughing that comes out automatically]
Look at the view! This is what vacation is about!
[Path that goes through Route 35
and follows the Nakdonggang]
Wow, it's so nice.
[Path that goes through Route 35
and follows the Nakdonggang]
The air is so nice.
[Cool breeze hitting their bodies]
Wow, it's so pretty next to us.
- It's so nice. I think you can even go fishing.
- I know.
[Feels like you're driving inside a picture]
Nice, nice, nice.
[♪] [Hums a tune with his nose]
Nice.
[Wow]
So nice.
[Wow, so nice]
The weather is so nice.
- This is when I make a plan.
- What plan?
What am I going to do today?
Go in first.
and eat and...
["MINGYU's forest plans"] [1. Delicious meal]
And workout right away.
[2. Workout at the strength zone]
Get rid of your sweat.
[(Let's go in first)]
And take a shower.
["MINGYU's forest plans"]
[3. A refreshing shower]
And eat food in this state.
["MINGYU's forest plans"]
[3. A refreshing shower]
[4. Eat (again)]
- Eat again...?
- And lie down after you eat.
Drink.
[End of the day is obviously alcohol!]
Aren't you just a player?
"In the SOOP" is normally...
It's hard when you leave the forest.
[MINGYU's thoughts]
[Scenery that is out like a panorama]
It's cool.
I should eat at the camping site today.
[Camp zone]
Let's eat it at the campfire!
- The sun already set!
- I want to do it before the sun sets.
The sun sets too fast, right?
- The sun sets before 6 p.m.
- I know.
But MINGYU...
It's only p.m.!
[Checks time]
I think it's going to be 6 p.m.
when we go up to the temple and go back.
Oh really?
- We need to run up!
- Run up?
We would have looked cool if
all three of us ride Har*, right?
[Motorcycles]
Yes. We're in America if we ride like that.
[(Let's ride together)]
Crazy.
[Heading towards Cheongnyangsa
where the mountain team went to]
Is this the temple?
[Heading towards Cheongnyangsa
where the mountain team went to]
Is the place we're going Cheongnyangsa?
[Heading towards Cheongnyangsa
where the mountain team went to]
Yes, Cheongnyangsa.
Cheongnyangsan Provincial Park.
Provincial Park.
[Decide to go up to Cheongnyangsa!]
Let's just take a picture and check it out
and go home right away.
[Decide to go up to Cheongnyangsa!]
- Let's go.
[(MINGYU)]
I am not going to let you slide from here!
- We are going up. / - Are you leading from here?
[I am going to lead Cheongnyangsa]
- Okay?
- We will run.
[MINGYU's stamina that is
overpowering from the beginning]
Is it really okay to run? It's okay for me.
[MINGYU's stamina that is
overpowering from the beginning]
- Don't push yourself too hard. / - It's kind of hard.
[Found a slope]
There is a high slope.
[(Flustered)]
Come over here.
You need to press down on your legs and go up.
[Stimulating your muscles is a must!]
How long has it been working out like this?
I think it's been a really long time.
Hasn't Cheonggyesan been the last for you?
Cheonggyesan was the last for you, too?
So, the proper one...
- We all stayed up and went there. / - Yes. / - Yes.
[2015.01.01 at Cheonggyesan -
saw the sunrise and made a wish]
- Wasn't that our debut year in January?
Right? January 1st? / - Yes.
[2015.01.01 at Cheonggyesan -
saw sunrise and made a wish]
- Didn't we go down there
and eat something good?
- Baeksuk.
I suddenly remembered.
[(...)]
It is towards Seolleung.
Hey! What are you doing?
- Yes. / - Come up.
[(Heh)]
What are you doing?
[(I want to go back...)]
- Huh? / - Hurry up and come.
I can't go mountain climbing now.
[Mountain climbing is not as easy as before]
- But I do it when I go. / - Really?
Wow, but...
[(Took off all their jackets in no time)]
This slope is the worst.
[Flustered] [(Took off all their jackets in no time)]
[A slope that makes them kind of flustered(?)]
- WONWOO.
- Yes?
Hold this.
[(MINGYU running)]
Really?
Are legs from biking different?
[Passionate boy, Nobody can stop me]
I am really satisfied that there are stairs.
[Road that the mountain members climbed
a couple of hours ago]
Yes. The stairs are much easier.
[Road that the mountain members climbed
a couple of hours ago]
[Out of energy]
What? He's collapsed over there?
It's going to be cold when we get back
on our motorcycles after sweating!
Oh, MINGYU! You look good.
[(Flying squirrel that's tired)]
Oh, you look good.
[⤣ Can't miss out on stimulating his leg muscles]
Work out! Move your legs. Legs.
Eat more like this.
Check how many meters are left!
300m.
[Cheongnyangsa 360m →]
300m is so close.
I was always curious when I climbed a mountain!
Why do you go up when you're going to go down?
When you're going to go down.
You're going to go down.
[Biggest question]
- Why are you going to go up?
- You want to go up and down.
[Biggest question]
- I think we're here. / - I think we're here.
[Is it here?]
I'm sure there's going to be a zipline to go down?
[Climbed hard and arrived Cheongnyangsa]
Awesome.
[Members are busy capturing this vast view]
- It's so pretty. / - So pretty.
You need to take off your shoes and go up!
[Whispering]
[Cheongnyangsa has freshness and honor]
[Looks at the wide-open, great view]
[Deep in thought while breathing in the clear air]
The air is really nice.
[WONWOO comes and sits next to him]
MINGYU, sit here.
But how do you think they built this?
I know.
This stood on top of the road
where Wonhyo went by.
Oh really?
[Reading the sign]
Let's go.
[WONWOO puts his hands together
and closes his eyes for a moment]
Let's go.
Oh, it's nice.
It was good.
- I said hi to my mom in the end.
- Good job.
[That time, the members who are back at the forest]
[Spending their own time]
[Enjoying a relaxing nap]
Is there someone at the dorm?
Is there someone there?
Comfort that you can only feel at "In the SOOP".
["In the SOOP" that's peaceful today, too]
Guys, enjoy this comfort.
[Time of spacing out in the water
while looking at nature]
[HOSHI, DK's first canoe]
Oh, it's nice.
[(Nice because it's relaxing)]
[JEONGHAN who is looking
at them with a smile ???]
HOSHI, how is it? Are you okay?
[Hamzzi who fell in the water... No, HOSHI]
[Tiger HOSHI]
[DK who is about to fall in water]
- So funny. / - I cancel being nice after god.
[What happened to these guys?]
[Dark night]
Where is sikhye and stuff?
[Suspicious footsteps in the dark night]
[Heading to the sauna]
[When the door closes]
- Do you want to make a bet? / - What?
[Their game that starts]
Rock-paper-scissors.
[Don't trust anyone]
What is this?
[(So serious)]
[Picked by "In the SOOP", greatest twist of 2023]
No! Did you guys plan it? What's wrong?
[We invite you to that surprised twist]