♪ How about some pajeon by the stream?
[S.COUPS] [JEONGHAN] [JOSHUA]
♪ How about working out twice a day?
[JUN] [WONWOO] [HOSHI] [WOOZI]
♪ How about we fly in the sky?
[THE 8] [MINGYU] [DK]
♪ Or zone out into the fire while you lean on me?
[SEUNGKWAN] [VERNON] [DINO]
♪ In the SOOP
♪ SOOP du ru du du ru du
(Yes, let's go there)
[SEVENTEEN IN THE SOOP 2]
[The following content
includes ads and sponsorship]
♪ SEVENTEEN is In the SOOP
[SEVENTEEN IN THE SOOP 2]
[The following content
includes ads and sponsorship]
Shall we go eat?
I'm hungry!
Compared to last year,
[Starting with JOSHUA's
jeyukbokkeum (stir-fried pork)]
our cooking skills have improved.
[SEVENTEEN is serious about food]
It's really good!
[Showing off their skills fully]
It's a good thing I cooked a lot.
[The sound of it filling because
of news of a good restaurant]
It's good!
It's all good.
Hey, but hasn't it been a while
since all of us ate together?
We've been together.
We've been together, but eating together...
[An enjoyable dinner with everyone
gathered for the first time in a while]
But I have something like that.
When they're in it...
[(With the guys) Emotionally]
[Huh?]
[The laughter doesn't stop when they're together]
[Doesn't know time is passing tonight]
We're going mountain climbing!
We're climbing a mountain.
[(Breaking news) 3 flying squirrels
have entered Cheongnyangsan]
Today's dress code is perfect!
I don't know who the flower is!
[(THE 8 flower has blossomed)]
Wow, it's really pretty!
[The landscape opens up once they climb up]
[A commemorative photo is a must!]
♪ A spin around the neighborhood
[The bike team gets hit by the cool breeze]
Wow, it's so nice!
[Totally excited]
- I feel like we're almost there.
[Riding and riding until they arrive]
- It's seriously so pretty. / - It's so pretty.
[Capturing the beautiful sights
with their eyes] [❤]
The air is so nice!
[What awaits them today?]
[While the members who went out
are having a great time]
Are you doing it together?
HOSHI is getting off.
Do we need to do this?
Let's do it on our own.
[HOSHI and DK are suddenly on the rock]
- I'm so thankful. / - Say hello to HOSHI first.
Hey!
[SS of BSS]
[What kind of situation is this]
Thank you so much for coming with me like this.
[SS of BSS] [What kind of situation is this]
For being the sacrificial lamb.
[15 minutes ago]
Okay! A bet getting into the water
with Rock-paper-scissors?
[15 minutes ago]
How about that?
We play Rock-paper-scissors and drop off
the loser on that rock.
[Betting-TEEN mode ON]
[Looking at the river gave them the idea
of a bet getting into the water]
Rock-paper-scissors!
[(DK) ✌] [(JEONGHAN) ✊] [(HOSHI) ✊]
DK! It's really...
[Happy]
We'll depart at the 40 minute mark.
[Sad]
[Trait of Betting-TEEN)
People who don't want to lose are the losers]
Since I rode the kayaks a lot,
- go and drop him off, HOSHI.
- Okay.
It's nice!
Just like this...
Can't I just go back after riding the boat?
[Naturally attempts to negotiate]
DK. We played Rock-paper-scissors.
[But he doesn't go easy on him]
Hold on.
How far are we going?
- Hey, sorry. / - Hey, HOSHI.
[DK is slowly showing his true colors]
We have to go here.
Huh?
[??]
I don't think I can die alone...
It's such a waste for me to die alone!
[And currently]
1, 2, 3!
We said let's go on the count of 3!
[Lacking a spoon of courage
in their passionate brotherhood]
- For real. / - We're going for real.
[Lacking a spoon of courage
in their passionate brotherhood]
Pinky swear!
What are you going to do
if you don't go in?
If I don't go in, I'll give you 10 million won.
[If he doesn't go in]
Really?
[If he doesn't go in, he'll give 10 million won]
[Doe-eyed]
1, 2... On 3?
- 1 million won...?
- 1 million won.
Why is it decreasing?
- 1 million won...
- No, not money!
- Swear on CARAT. / - Swear on CARAT.
[+ CARAT] [Swearing on SEVENTEEN]
- Swear on SEVENTEEN. / - Okay.
1, 2, 3!
[Into the water]
3!
[JEONGHAN loves his happy ending (?)]
[At the end of struggles,
they succeeded in going in the water...]
Guys! Go save the boat!
[At the end of struggles,
they succeeded in going in the water...]
It's so cold.
[...Whatever]
It's so cold!!
Hold on.
[Dragged~]
Hold on!
Are you okay, HOSHI?
[Dragged~]
It's so cold.
[The October forest weather automatically
brings both hands together]
I'll go bring that first.
[(An oar has been washed away)]
How cute.
[After getting in the canoe,
DK goes to save the oar and HOSHI swims]
- Can I ride this alone? / - Yes.
[After getting in the canoe,
DK goes to save the oar and HOSHI swims]
Hey, aren't you cold?
I'm cold.
[Ack!]
[Going different directions,
but both sides are struggling]
HOSHI! How is it?
[HOSHI has adjusted to
the water temperature Kekeke]
It's nice, right?
[HOSHI has adjusted to
the water temperature Kekeke]
But why aren't you coming out?
So it's very cold,
but it's a good thing, right?
[As HOSHI enjoys playing
in the water a bit more]
[DK is looking for the oar in
a 17 million won spine surgery position]
I didn't know DK was such a jerk.
What did he do?
- He said if you didn't get on,
he would make you fall in? / - Yes.
He was about to attack me.
I take back saying he's the most kind after Jesus.
[Small revenge] [Kekeke]
[And in front of the strength zone]
[JUN is focused on taking a photo of something]
[Then he comes into the playground]
[After putting the photo he took just now
up against the picture]
[He sketches with no hesitation]
[And how much time has passed?]
[After each careful stroke
of the rough sketch on the canvas]
[JUN starts to add color]
[He puts his all in every brush stroke]
[He paint thoroughly until the end]
[And it's finally finished]
[On the painting with only the blue skies]
[On the painting with only the blue skies,
SEVENTEEN's "IN THE SOOP" took place]
[Meanwhile, at the peaceful sleep zone]
[Around the time
the reddish sun sets by the hillside]
[The mountain climbing members gathered
at the tavern for a tea ceremony]
Since it's cold,
[The mountain climbing members gathered
at the tavern for a tea ceremony]
should we close the doors?
[The mountain climbing members gathered
at the tavern for a tea ceremony]
[VERNON brings snacks and quickly joins]
- Is it here?
- Yes.
[SEUNGKWAN enters last while humming]
There are chairs here.
Pu'er tea can warm up our bodies the most.
[~ THE 8's tea ceremony class
has opened up again ~]
And
out of fragrant ones,
there's black tea and oolong tea.
[Warm pu'er tea] [Fragrant black tea]
[Fragrant oolong tea]
Let's start with pu'er tea.
[Warm pu'er tea⭕] [Fragrant black tea]
[Fragrant oolong tea]
Let's go with pu'er tea
[Warm pu'er tea⭕] [Fragrant black tea]
[Fragrant oolong tea]
and then I'll make you
other ones.
[The tea ceremony master plans
to let them taste all 3]
[Starting with a cup of pu'er tea
that will melt away the cold fall air]
Let's go!
[Starting with a cup of pu'er tea
that will melt away the cold fall air]
I'll enjoy it.
[❤]
It's pu'er tea, right?
Pu'er tea is slightly...
It breaks down fat and things like that.
[Sips it while thinking of how it breaks down fat]
[So hot!!]
[(Ack)] [(Silent screams)]
It's hot!
[How cute Kekekeke]
[After blowing it once more]
[One shot]
But my body feels warm after drinking pu'er tea.
[As expected] [A cup of THE 8's tea
warms their bodies and hearts]
Of course.
[As expected] [A cup of THE 8's tea
warms their bodies and hearts]
- Let's keep it clean and eat hot pot and
samgyeopsal (pork belly). / - Okay.
I guess the guys are here.
I don't think it's here.
[The biking members came to the tavern
immediately with a ton of ingredients]
It's here.
[The biking members came to the tavern
immediately with a ton of ingredients]
[As if they're at a countryside vacation,
old-fashioned kitchenware]
[And all sorts of savory ingredients
welcome them]
[~This is the tavern~]
This gives off really old vibes!
Hey! We have ingredients for baeksuk,
but we never ate it!
Let's make baeksuk and eat it tomorrow!
Should we make it to eat tomorrow in the day?
[As expected, the foodies don't
consider not eating]
We said we'll eat baeksuk.
Hey! What's with them?
[Discovered the tea ceremony club ⤤]
Hi, guys!
Hey, Minghao.
Give me a cup, too.
[WONWOO naturally sits down
with the tea ceremony club]
Are you most comfortable
when you spread out your legs?
What are they making right now?
Caldron lid samgyeopsal.
Seriously.
They're eating samgyeopsal everyday.
[Eating samgyeopsal everyday at the forest Keke]
- Like this.
- Flip it over.
[(Preparing the main griddle)]
That's right.
I'll light the fire.
[Shall we light the fire now?]
Do you want to open up a table and eat here?
I want to do that, but there's nowhere to sit.
[But they can't sit and eat...]
There's nowhere to sit.
Or should I carry the camping chairs
and come here, MINGYU?
- Do you want to? 4 camping chairs.
- Yes.
I'll bring the chairs.
[(Running S.COUPS)]
[While S.COUPS goes to get
chairs from the campground]
[MINGYU is preheating
the caldron lid, the star of the day]
[The tavern is filled with the smell of firewood]
Good!
[Right then, S.COUPS also carries
the camping chairs and returns]
Hey! Don't feed Jeon Wonwoo!
- Yes, sir! / - Hey, don't eat.
[Got caught-red handed talking
to the tea ceremony club]
I'll rush!
[Got caught-red handed talking
to the tea ceremony club]
Wow, what is this?
But this is...
What are we doing with this?
We're going to eat here.
This place is too far.
Hey, but the mood is amazing.
[From a well heated caldron lid
to camping chairs- ]
It's seriously so nice.
[Countryside vacation vibes in it of itself_★]
- Should we start first? / - Okay.
[(This mood calls for makgeolli (rice wine)]
[(Cheers)]
[Gulping ASMR]
I'll do about this much.
It's so sweet and refreshing.
[❤] [❤]
[(Gulp)]
- Wow!
- It's so sweet!
[Coating the caldron lid with fat~]
I'll do about this much.
[About to really start grilling
the samgyeopsal on the caldron lid!]
[Can't miss the photo ⤤]
Should I post this with
"Who wants to eat with me?"
I can probably post this, right?
[Good things should be shared with CARAT!]
When the meat is done.
Are you cooking it well?
Who is it?
- Is it Shua? / - Shua!
[JOSHUA is holding a ton of hot pot ingredients
and JUN also joins at the tavern]
There's a place like this?
[JOSHUA is holding a ton of hot pot ingredients
and JUN also joins at the tavern]
I think this is the best I've ever grilled
on a caldron lid.
[Browning]
Hey! It's cooking so well!
There's such mood to it.
- Right?
- Yes.
The view here is nice!
- It's funny how they're doing
a tea ceremony inside. / - Yeah.
[Everything has mood
during dinner at the tavern]
Today went by so fast.
What time is it?
6:30.
6:30?
[They only went mountain climbing,
but the sky has gotten dark]
I think I need to stretch.
I should use a foam roller for relief and sleep.
[Can feel the rough aftereffects
of mountain climbing]
Didn't they say there's a sauna here?
[Thinking about melting away the fatigue
from the rough mountain climbing at the sauna]
- Where the warm water is.
- It's right next to that.
[Think we heard there was a sauna here...]
- Right?
- There's a bath?
- There's both. / - A jacuzzi.
[A sauna and jacuzzi set
prepared just for SEVENTEEN]
A jacuzzi next to the sauna.
- It was really nice.
- Can you wash up there?
- No. / - No, you have to wash up
after you come out.
- Should I? I should go today then.
- I want to go, too.
- Want to go at 9? / - Should we?
[Let's spend all day together❤]
[Following mountain climbing and
the tea ceremony, they plan to go to the sauna]
Today, we'll do pull-ups, lat pulls,
barbell rows, seated rows, and barbell rows.
[Meanwhile, the strength zone
has opened up again for business today]
We'll finish with this.
4 sets of 20 repetitions, 5 exercises.
That's not much, right?
[After Trainer Woo's concise briefing]
4.
That's right!
[Officially starting 1:1 coaching]
5!
As if you're grazing your knees,
bring them above your knees and your back...
[Officially starting 1:1 coaching]
Just make it straight.
8!
9! Okay!
10!
[And Trainer Woo's pacemakers, HOSHI and DINO]
This is the last chorus of "Crush" at our concert.
You're almost there!
Do your best!
[Ay!]
When you said, "This is the last chorus of 'Crush',"
- it really struck a chord with me. / - Right?
[(Struck a chord 1122%)]
I thought, "Yes, it's over!"
That's right.
- Done!
- When we do this...
[When the concert is about to end]
- When we do this! That wasn't just me!
- It's over!
[When the concert is about to end]
- Right?
- That's right.
- When I start this,
- I think, "Well done, Chan!" "You worked so hard."
- We're there!
This is how I feel when I start this.
- I worked really hard today!
- Really.
- Cool down. / - How hilarious.
[The strength zone members
are having fun again today]
DINO! Let's do one last one.
It wasn't enough.
[Still at the tavern]
[The highlight of samgyeopsal on a caldron lid]
[The amazing combination of
samgyeopsal+kimchi make their jaws drop]
Please give me a lot.
- It's nice!
- Right here,
- let's divide this in half.
- Then put this a bit to the side.
[A bunch of smoke ⤥]
[(Cries) (Smoke)]
It's done.
That side also needs ssamjang
(red chili and soybean paste), right?
[(Cries) (Smoke)]
Yes.
Then...
[The insane meat grilled while
bearing stinging eyes]
Hey, MINGYU! The meat is insane.
[The insane meat grilled while
bearing stinging eyes]
This is a food that could never taste bad!!
It's here.
- I'll enjoy the food! / - Where's the makgeolli?
[❤]
- Are you going to have a drink?
- Should we over here?
First off, I'll make
a vegetable wrap first.
[Makes a wrap and takes a big bite]
It's good.
[The charm of samgyeopsal on a caldron lid
that makes them speechless]
Wow! The kimchi looks good, too.
Hey. The kimchi is insane.
[One bite]
It's really insane.
[One bite] [Two bites]
It's seriously insane.
Is this joy?
It seriously melts!
[Everyone silently just scarfs down the meat]
Right at this time, the spicy broth
has to be brought to a boil.
- It happened right when you said that.
- It worked.
[This is what the right time is...!]
Wow!
[Spicy mala red broth has come- ]
Meat! Let's go!
- Should I add a lot?
- Yes.
Put in the mala!
Didn't we bring bok choy?
I really like bok choy these days.
[If they dunk the boy choy
in the scorching spicy broth]
I like boy choy, too.
[If they dunk the boy choy
in the scorching spicy broth]
Is this boy choy?
[Then the hot pot that the members
will enjoy together is finished!]
Yes, boy choy.
[Then the hot pot that the members
will enjoy together is finished!]
But interestingly enough,
none of us can't eat mala.
Before mala got popular, JUN already...
- He made us familiar with mala.
- We ate it so much. / - Yes, that's right.
I ate a lot of mala.
- I used to not be able to explain it.
- We went by Konkuk University a lot.
[Kekeke]
A tongue numbing spiciness.
[Addicted at a certain point]
- That's right. / - But really...
[Addicted at a certain point
to the tongue numbing spiciness]
It's a tongue numbing taste, right?
Hot pot is really good when it's cold.
[Round 1 of samgyeopsal then
round 2 of JUN's hot pot]
- We just put everything in and boil it, right?
- Yes, that's right.
[Meanwhile, at the food zone]
Fire!
[JEONGHAN and DK are cooking 2 meal kits]
[100 points for making use of the meal kits]
[Adding ingredients to taste
to the meal kit budaejjigae (sausage stew)]
[The budaejjigae is finished]
[Meanwhile, JEONGHAN is]
[Mixing the sauce into the dakgalbi
(spicy braised chicken)]
With your hands...
- There has to be the touch of hands...
- Touch of hands.
[Rolling up the sleeves and
adding more flavor with touch of hands]
- Is it done?
- Yes, it's pretty much done now.
[Adding rice right away and
making fried rice]
[Budaejjigae, dakgalbi, and fried rice]
[The 3 meal kits are finished!]
- Let's take it. / - Really? Let's go.
[Budaejjigae, dakgalbi, and fried rice]
[The 3 meal kits are finished!]
Let's go!
We have to go quickly!
All of this will taste bad.
Let's go.
[JEONGHAN sprints with 2 frying pans]
Wow, you can run!
We have to run!
I can't run. Sorry.
Running with budaejjigae
is what looks cool.
[It's what's cool]
There are lots of people.
I'm just going to eat here.
[The dakgalbi has arrived safely!]
- What did you bring?
- We brought dakgalbi.
- That's nice.
- What are you eating over there?
Samgyeopsal.
Hot pot and samgyeopsal.
- I think they made too much.
We could've just come and eaten. / - Yeah.
But we have our own mood.
[(Protect the mood of our meal kits_★)]
Yes, let's enjoy the food!
[❤]
- I'll enjoy the food.
- Enjoy!
[If they add sesame oil to the fried rice]
Hey!
- It's nice. / - Right?
[GOOD...!]
To this...
This is it!
This is the table of a Korean!
Hey. A little...
Shake it around!
[Shaking and pretending to stir fry it
once more before eating]
Make it fly around more.
[Shaking and pretending to stir fry it
once more before eating]
Make the rice fly!
- No, then all of it will fly over to you.
- Okay.
You have to be careful.
- It's fine. Let's eat it here.
- Scarf down one bite.
[(A huge bite)]
It's good!
[(A bite for me too)]
Is it this?
[A spoonful of warm budaejjigae as well]
It's so nice because it's warm.
Good thing we reheated it once more, right?
I reheated it so that
you could have it warm.
Your heart is warmer than this.
[❤]
Your heart was warm.
It's fun.
[Tonight's dinner is better because
it's with the members]
But it's nice eating in this mood.
It's fun.
[Tonight's dinner is better because
it's with the members]
[(Sneakily)]
But it's really good!
Cheers!
We have nothing to cheers with.
- It's cola.
- What is this?
- Makgeolli. Do you want makgeolli?
- Makgeolli...
- It doesn't matter to me.
- I'll bring it to you.
One person has to
drink from a bigger cup.
[The big cup is pretty unique ⤤]
- It's for gukbap.
- Should I drink from that?
Do you want this?
Do you want to drink from this?
[The size of the makgeolli cup is so extreme]
I think it's too big.
- Thank you. / - I won't give you a lot.
[(Makgeolli)]
Thank you.
What's the name of this tavern?
It's...
It's INSE Tavern.
[~ INSE Tavern scenario suddenly begins ~]
- INSE Tavern. / - INSE Tavern.
How many years has it been?
- We've been open since 1700...
- I see. Cheers.
[Downing the refreshing makgeolli
with 500 years of tradition (?)]
- Fill our cups once more and go.
We drank it. / - Okay.
Please give us that makgeolli and meat.
[INSE Tavern is overflowing with orders]
- Bartender! Please give us some makgeolli here!
- Okay!
Please give me a drink.
[INSE Tavern is busy]
Thank you!
[(?)]
- Why are you talking like that?
- Thank you!
Grandpa, grandma. Stop!
Way of talking long ago. Grandpa, grandma. Stop.
[Way of talking from 500 years ago (?)
that can only be heard at INSE Tavern Kekeke]
- JEONGHAN!
- Yes!
Hey, it's so cold.
[The generosity of sharing a bite
if they come to the deck]
- Try a bite. / - Okay.
[The generosity of sharing a bite
if they come to the deck]
There's green onion kimchi!
I'm starting with the green
onion kimchi this time!
We have to go for the green onion kimchi.
- This is legit today. / - Yeah.
[The star that will take the caldron lid stage
this time is "green onion kimchi"]
Today is the most epic
when it comes to barbecue!
Eat meat!
Pick only the cooked pieces for them.
The kimchi
- has to cook for a bit longer. / - Okay.
[Delivering well cooked
samgyeopsal on a caldron lid]
- Thank you. / - Thanks! / - Ssamjang?
[Delivering well cooked
samgyeopsal on a caldron lid]
- Ssamjang sounds good! / - Ssamjang.
[Delivering well cooked
samgyeopsal on a caldron lid]
What did you all do today?
Today, we first ate, went to the playroom
and played Yutnori,
bet on going into the water by playing
Rock-paper-scissors, and went into the water.
That was DK!
[(Oh, that's why DK did that)]
After I wiped down completely,
I then realized I didn't bring clothes.
I passed by and DK was naked.
"Is nobody there?"
[The bathroom] [Kekeke]
"Excuse me? Help me!"
[The reason DK was so desperate]
[◀◀◀ After going into the river]
[After returning from the campgrounds]
[DK went in a rush to wash up
without carrying anything]
Is anybody here?
[An urgent voice fills the sleep zone briefly after]
Is anybody there?
[The savior who heard this sound]
[The savior who heard this sound was JOSHUA]
- Shua? / - Yes.
[Glad]
- Hey.
- Yes.
I'm sorry, but can you bring me
a t-shirt and any pants?
From where?
How long were you waiting in the bathroom?
You pretty much came down
right after I started yelling.
- Really?
- That was good timing.
- That was really good timing.
- You were really like a savior.
If I had woken up earlier and left the house...!
[If only]
There was nobody!
[Even the thought is like thrilling "Home Alone"]
You would've had to wait
until I finished the dishes.
I even thought of that.
"Since JEONGHAN
takes 20 minutes to do dishes..."
[(Pretty urgent prison break on the toilet...)]
"I have to sit by the toilet and wait here..."
"It's really cold, so should I wrap up
in a towel?" I thought about this.
If I was in your shoes,
I would've covered up in a towel and went up.
I'm saying this now, but...
Go into the water again?
[Chokes up...!]
[(Having fun teasing him)]
He's a funny guy!
[Hahahaha!!]
I'll do it if we do.
- I'll go eat more hot pot.
- Are you leaving?
No.
I want to eat hot pot.
Do you like mood, DK?
[Going into the water mood?]
[Tavern mood?]
It depends on what kind of mood it is.
[Going into the water mood?]
[Tavern mood?]
I'm trying to sort my mood...
I like moods, but this is...
This can also be done with mood.
I'll hear you out.
Right now, we... 1.
[This]
2.
[This] [This]
There are 3, right?
[This] [This] [This]
To wash.
[(Betting mood ON)]
Doing dishes
here.
[Doing dishes at the tavern faucet ⤥]
What do you think?
There's mood to it, right?
But if it's rowdy here and
we're all done eating,
- but someone loses? / - After losing...
[Lonely dishes in the crowd...]
- If you do them alone, it's very lonely.
- Doing that is very moody.
[Lonely dishes in the crowd...]
- What mood? / - Lonely mood.
"Have to hurry and go in there."
[That's the tavern mood!]
Eating raw onions.
[DK's mood]
I like it.
[Responds to a bet within 0.001 seconds]
Rock-paper-scissors?
- Since it's not hard. / - This is doable.
[Let's go]
Rock-paper-scissors!
[(Scissors)] [(Muk)]
Let's play Muk-jji-ppa. I went first.
[Suddenly switching to Muk-jji-ppa]
Muk-muk-muk-muk.
Ppa-ppa-jji!
[(Paper)] [(Muk)]
Jji-jji!
[(Scissors)] [(Paper)]
Ppi!
[(Scissors)] [(Scissors)]
- You said jji-jji-ppi! / - Jji-jji-jji.
[(Sword)]
Because of the samgyeopsal.
[(Shield)]
Peel it.
If you peel it and rinse it in water once,
I'll eat it right away.
- Really?
- Yes.
- But you can normally eat raw onions!
- I like raw onions.
Then...
It looks like you're doing dishes.
[Kekeke]
[JEONGHAN lost,
but DK is washing an onion in cold water]
I look very lonely, right?
[JEONGHAN lost,
but DK is washing an onion in cold water]
- Are you okay, DK?
- Yes!
- I feel bad for you.
- What are you doing?
- I'm washing an onion.
- Why?
- He's going to take a bite of an onion.
- A raw onion... A raw onion? / - A bite? / - No!
If you say it like that,
I seem like such a stepmother!
We played Rock-paper-scissors
and bet on eating an onion.
I have to eat it because I lost.
[(I'm definitely the one that lost...)]
What if you eat the whole thing
because it tastes good?
There's ssamjang here, right?
[JEONGHAN's raw onion eating skill]
[1. Put ssamjang on it like this first~]
Smear it on like this.
[JEONGHAN's raw onion eating skill]
[1. Put ssamjang on it like this first~]
Smear it on.
[JEONGHAN's raw onion eating skill]
[2. Take a big bite]
Hey! It looks like you're eating a fruit.
- It's good! / - It's good?
[Shaking]
It's really good.
- Really? / - Really.
[(Serious)]
An onion is that good?
Do you want to try it for real?
[(Oh... Is it?)]
Give it to me! You eat it so deliciously.
- It's really good!
- If someone eats something so deliciously,
it makes me want to eat it.
Take a bite.
It's sweet.
Hm! It's good!
The spicy smell
keeps coming up my nose.
[From a certain point,
these 2 are eating a raw onion together...]
But it's spicy, yet sweet.
[From a certain point,
these 2 are eating a raw onion together...]
It's nice.
Try the kalguksu (noodle soup).
[Meanwhile, the members are starting to get full]
- I'm really full right now. / - Eat some, MINGYU.
I'm about to die right now
But I want to keep eating meat.
No!!
But I want to keep
eating meat.
[(Sneakily)]
No!!
- No!
Then give me some kimchi!
It's mine!!
- Eat some of this.
- It's here.
[(Here)]
[(Chopsticks can't stop)]
MINGYU! I'm reminded of the rice
we had when we went
on a trip on our own long ago.
[Fried rice can't be left out]
- The Great Wonhyo rice?
[Fried rice can't be left out.
Done. Okay!
- Sesame oil! / - Hey, sesame oil!
[If they flatten it on the caldron lid
and add sesame oil]
How is it?
Try it! It's good. Try it.
- I think it's going to be so hot. / - It's good.
[INSE Tavern magic where food
keeps going in even when they're full_★]
Not the kalguksu, but the knife.
[INSE Tavern magic where food
keeps going in even when they're full_★]
Is it good?
I'm really
full.
[A taste they can't stop]
- It keeps going in. / - It keeps going in?
I'm going to work out,
[The plan after dinner] [1]
go to the sweat it out at the sauna, do the spa...
[The plan after dinner] [1 exercise] [2]
Wash up, rest and...
[The plan after dinner] [1 exercise]
[2 go to the sauna and sweat] [3]
Then we can sleep.
[The plan after dinner] [1 exercise]
[2 go to the sauna and sweat]
[3 wash up and rest] [4]
Should we clean up?
[EP5. Our memories shining brighter]
But I'm so full!
Yes, I'm so full!
[EP5. Our memories shining brighter]
[(Vroom)]
[The one enjoying speed
in the moonlit night is...]
[(Bang)]
[HOSHI is immersed in an action movie]
- Is it HOSHI? / - Who is it?
[(Bang)]
[HOSHI is immersed in an action movie]
- I think it's Kwon Soonyoung.
- Right? / - HOSHI?
HOSHI is the one who would
do something like that. [Ha]
Is he doing it in survival mode right now?
No, right?
[(HOSHI is just playing alone)]
I think HOSHI is just playing alone.
HOSHI!
[(No response)]
Are you not HOSHI?
Minghao!
No, that running is HOSHI's.
- HOSHI?
- Yes!
- What are you doing?
I was playing with the drone.
You're playing with the drone?
- I shot a music video.
- Okay!
Have fun playing and you'll...
You'll get caught by the drone!
Hurry up and run away!
[Running away]
- Wow, he's so cute.
- Right?
How crazy.
That's why HOSHI has a lot of fans.
You should do it, too.
[Heading to the fire pit for hot chocolate time]
[HOSHI shot a music video on a large stage (?)]
[Pretty seriously shooting with a drone]
[This is like dancing charades]
[Even props suddenly appear]
[Please look forward to what kind
of music video will come out...!]
There's the saying that humans adapt
and I feel like this is my house.
You've adapted?
I fall asleep so well here. It's so nice.
[At "IN THE SOOP"]
Sleep did that.
[Played a part]
Yeah.
Try this.
[JEONGHAN and DK are like
peaceful Animal *rossing civilians]
[The wild tiger sound breaks the peace]
Hey! The drone!
[Playing along]
Hey! Avoid the drone!
[(Hero HOSHI is being
chased by the evil drone)]
Do it with him, WOOZI!
Hurry up and come eat.
[(An action movie HOSHI shot by himself)]
He says he has to run away from the drone.
Wow! HOSHI seriously looks like
he would come out of a cartoon right now.
WOOZI! Hurry up and run!
WOOZI!
["I'll chase you until the end!"]
[(HOSHI eventually leaves
after being chased by the drone)]
Run away, HOSHI!
[(HOSHI eventually leaves
after being chased by the drone)]
[The music video shoot doesn't end]
At times like this, the mood is...
We shouldn't put the skewer on this.
We have to use branches as skewers
to create the mood.
Should we try if there are any branches?
[The magic word "mood" that makes
DK do everything you say]
- Should we look? / - Should we look?
[The magic word "mood" that makes
DK do everything you say]
I think there are branches though.
[(Picks it up)]
This?
That's okay!
[JEONGHAN loves it ❤]
- Nice! How did you find it so well? / - Right?
- First off, we have to sterilize it a bit...
- Are you going to cook it?
[Even done sterilizing (?) it in the fire]
[Now it's time to put the hotteok on
and cook it over the campfire]
I got it.
[Now it's time to put the hotteok on
and cook it over the campfire]
[Hoo~]
This is more than enough!
It doesn't burn as much as I expected!
Oh, it burned.
[How does the campfire-grilled hotteok taste?]
My back hurts.
- Is this done?
- It's good.
[Hero HOSHI reappeared]
Hey.
[(Endless fight with the evil drone)]
It's still following me.
[That punk]
That's quite a persistent fellow.
Hey! You got caught.
Is that okay? You got caught.
No, seeing how it's dark there, it's our team.
[Getting completely immersed]
Why is this so fun?
Take a sip of this. It's good.
Sit here and stare off into the fire, HOSHI.
- I haven't eaten yet.
- This is hot.
[Hot chocolate after a fight is... ❤]
It's good, right?
I should eat.
Enjoy!
[(The full version of HOSHI's music video
will be revealed at the end.)]
[HOSHI won in a fierce battle with a drone]
- Hey, Jihoon. / - Yes?
I shot one for "BRING IT".
[(Music video)]
Really? Good job.
I went down in the middle there.
You know what I mean, right?
I don't know what you mean.
[(Cutting him off)]
Nobody besides you does stuff like that.
Let's hurry up and eat!
Let's eat tenderloin and
- then sirloin. / - Okay.
[1:1 workout and meet routine]
[Eating tenderloin and sirloin again for dinner]
- What is this? / - Tenderloin.
[1:1 workout and meet routine]
[Eating tenderloin and sirloin again for dinner]
- This is tenderloin and that's... / - Okay.
[1:1 workout and meet routine]
[Eating tenderloin and sirloin again for dinner]
If there isn't enough as we're eating, there's
also a lot of samgyeopsal and moksal (pork neck).
[WOOZI (Born in 1996) / Meat lover /
Plans to eat pork if hanwoo isn't enough]
Okay.
[WOOZI (Born in 1996) / Meat lover /
Plans to eat pork if hanwoo isn't enough]
I'll bring small plates.
[While HOSHI goes to get small plates]
[WOOZI wipes off the blood from the meat]
[The best temperature for cooking meat is]
[(Checking like this and this)]
[HOSHI, who grabs small plates and chopsticks]
We have to be healthy and eat vegetables.
Greens.
[❤]
Oh, good! Lettuce sounds good.
[Even prepared to eat leafy greens]
Let's get right to grilling.
[Let's eat!]
Wow, we're cooking beef here.
[Putting the well cooked meat
on HOSHI's plate first]
[WOOZI takes a bite with the tongs]
It's good!
Beef is always good!
[Resetting with lettuce]
This sort of barbecue mood is so nice.
How is it so good even when
we're eating it so simple?
The color of the meat
obviously looks good!
[Moving straight onto sirloin]
Look at the color!
- Is this sirloin? / - Yes.
[Moving straight onto sirloin]
There's no way this could taste bad.
[While WOOZI and HOSHI are
enjoying a happy barbecue time]
It's not too hot. It's nice.
[While WOOZI and HOSHI are
enjoying a happy barbecue time]
[The 98s SEUNGKWAN and VERNON
entered the sauna first]
Come in.
[The 98s SEUNGKWAN and VERNON
entered the sauna first]
[Tidying up the shoes as well ⤸]
Wow! It's insane, right?
[(Excited 🍊)]
It's been a while since I've been in a sauna.
[Aftermath of mountain climbing]
[Unlike VERNON, who lied down right away]
[Maintenance BOO continues even in the sauna]
- Teach me after you're all done using it. / - Okay.
[(The foam roller)]
[Starting with massaging the calves]
[Every single tight area]
How insane.
[Every single tight area
is being relieved by SEUNGKWAN]
Wow... It hurts so much.
[Doesn't forget to finish off with stretching]
[(VERNON, the foam roller...!?)]
[Glances]
[But VERNON is already sleeping
[zzz]
[VERNON is fast asleep with
SEUNGKWAN as white noise]
[Relieving fatigue from
mountain climbing with heat]
Wow... The sweat is insane...
[The 98s' forest sauna experience is over]
Who wants to go to
the sauna in 30 minutes?
- We're going right now.
- We're going right now. / - You're going now?
I should change.
- What about DK?
- I want to lie down in the room for now.
But I think it'll be so cold if
I go in and come out.
Afterwards,
- we have to wash up and sleep. / - Me too.
[The sauna members go
to the sleep zone to change]
I'm going to try that now.
[The sauna members go
to the sleep zone to change]
[Meanwhile, the sleep zone is quiet]
[zzzz]
[Someone is snoring and sleeping...]
[Right then, the members
break the silence and come in]
- I worked out with MINGYU earlier, right?
- HOSHI.
[Right then, the members
break the silence and come in]
- No, SEUNGKWAN! / - Why?
[Right then, the members
break the silence and come in]
Do you want to go there with me?
- Nobody is listening.
- Really?
Guys! Please listen to me!
[Awoken from the rowdiness?!]
I slept well!
- Father!
- I slept well.
- Father! / - I slept well.
[It's S.COUPS] [Totally over insomnia]
- SEUNGKWAN. Let's go to the sauna.
- Huh? I want to go!
- Okay! Let's go after we change.
- Let's go to the sauna.
- I went to the sauna. / - Really? / - Alone?
[SEUNGKWAN has already gone to the sauna
with VERNON and showered]
No, with VERNON.
[SEUNGKWAN has already gone to the sauna
with VERNON and showered]
We'll be back!
[(Then) we should]
Enjoy!
Good night, chicken.
[Saying good night to the chickens
before going to the sauna]
Where's the sikhye
[Running over to get the sikhye from the tavern]
and other things?
It's in the refrigerator.
[Running over to get the sikhye from the tavern]
Sikhye!
Grab one!
[Can't leave out a sikhye per person at saunas]
- One. / - One.
- These eggs...
- We just need to take 4, right?
How much sweat
will come out today?
[Taking protein filled snacks]
- And we need to fill up on protein right away.
- I'm really looking forward to it.
[Taking protein filled snacks]
[Can feel a determined aura for some reason]
[A war with the sauna (?)]
[- "IN THE SOOP" ver. -]
Wow! there's even a jacuzzi!
Let's do it after we come out of the sauna.
[With the forest as a wonderful background]
Let's go!
[With the forest as a wonderful background,
the jacuzzi is enjoyed outdoors]
[Reservation placed for after the sauna... ★]
It's cold.
[Throws his cell phone] [S.COUPS and
JEONGHAN have entered the sauna]
It's hot! Change it right away.
[Throws his cell phone] [S.COUPS and
JEONGHAN have entered the sauna]
- Is it warm? / - It's warm. It's amazing!
[Protein companion] [JOSHUA and MINGYU
have also entered the sauna]
[Lastly, DINO has also entered the sauna]
I wish the eggs were a little warmer.
[(The ones they brought)]
Should we leave it here?
Careful with your hands.
[(So synchronized even when putting it down)]
Are the rocks hot?
They're sizzling.
Do you want to make a bet?
Sounds good! I'm fine with any game.
[0.01 second response at the word, "bet"]
- Cracking it with your head. / - Yeah. / - Yes.
[- Today's bet - Cracking the stone-plate
cooked egg with the loser's head]
Punishment.
Cracking the egg with your head
without using your hands.
[Serious about bets]
Should we play Rock-paper-scissors?
Or with something else?
Let's start with Rock-paper-scissors for now.
[Starting with a light round
of Rock-paper-scissors]
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Lightly starting with Rock-paper-scissors]
Okay. Then...
[S.COUPS is the one who suggested
the punishment anyway]
Crack it hard on S.COUPS' head.
But you have to crack it.
[(If you don't crack it in one go,
YOU will be the next target]
If you don't crack it, the baton goes to you.
[(If you don't crack it in one go,
YOU will be the next target]
He means you have to crack it for sure.
[Meaning that they should finish
everything in one go]
Is it possible not to crack it?
[Meaning that they should finish
everything in one go]
Don't you need to take off your hat?
[Meaning that they should finish
everything in one go]
- You have to take off the hat.
[What's the point of this... Seriously all ready]
[Get ready]
[Get ready????!!!!!]
[Why is there a raw egg...?]
What is this?
[Dripping]
- What is this? / - Hold on!
[Nobody expected this outcome]
- Hold on.
- What is it?
- What's with the stone-plate cooked egg?
- What is this?
[Kekekekeke]
What did you bring?
[(Seriously flustered)]
No...
Did you plan this?
What's wrong with this?
What... What are you doing with this?
[Denying reality]
What is this?
This is... Well...
[S.COUPS / Going crazy from
being hit with a raw egg]
- This is... / - Wow, this is so...
[Just a ridiculous situation Kekeke]
- It's ridiculous. / - Hold on.
We brought it because we thought
they were stone-plate cooked eggs!
Then these are all just raw eggs?
- They're raw eggs? Why are there
raw eggs there? / - Well...
[All of the eggs they brought are raw Hahaha]
Hey, we should go back to get them.
[Collecting the raw eggs they put
on the stones for now]
Hold on.
- Hold on. / - I...
[(The audience is highly satisfied)]
- It's protein, so stay like this!
- I...
I'm satisfied.
I got the broadcast footage.
But I was so flustered...
[(Lead role who stuck to his job_1)]
- Hey, we were also flustered!
- We were also flustered.
[(Lead role who stuck to his job_2)]
Did you see him? After he cracked it...
"What is this!"
[(DINO's expression)]
I cracked it and looked.
"What is this? Why is it like this?"
[(Reenacting the highlights)]
Why is it like this?
[Break+silence+kekeke= Insane combination]
There was silence just now.
- What is this? / - What is this?
[Break+silence+kekeke= Insane combination]
Oh my... It's dripping down my eyes.
- Wipe it off!
- You didn't know at first, right?
- You didn't know when he first cracked it,
right? / - No, I found out after I got hit.
- Oh, after you got hit?
- It cracked and my hair...
But DINO...
DINO hit me very sneakily.
[Officially stated by the one who got hit]
[DINO hit him sneakily (?)]
Not that...
He didn't just hit me, but he hit me and suddenly...
[The snap of his wrist was no joke]
- Hey, DINO! Go back and bring stone-plate
cooked eggs. / - Stone-plate cooked eggs.
I tried to not make it hurt...
[(For S.COUPS)]
What do I do about this?
Should I go wash my hair?
- No! Just stay like this.
- Hey!
- No, hey... / - It's protein, so it's okay.
[(?)]
- Hey! Your hair...
- I feel like the egg
- will fry here right now. / - Go rinse it out.
- Go rinse it out.
[(The egg is cooking...)]
Where do I go rinse it out?
[Going to the faucet before
the egg fries in his hair]
- I think I need go rinse it out
with water here. / - Here.
[Going to the faucet before
the egg fries in his hair]
- It's here, right?
- If he stays like this,
- won't it cook? / - S.COUPS!
With the stone-plate cooked eggs...
[When you come back,
stone-plate cooked eggs ^^]
My head.
[In the midst of this,
he brought the egg basket ⤤]
It was so hilarious.
[The shock of the raw egg hasn't left Kekeke]
DINO's expression was so funny.
- He hit him and... / - He was so flustered.
[The shock of the raw egg hasn't left Kekeke]
It was fun.
I'm so glad I didn't lose.
It was either S.COUPS or me.
[The thought of that moment is still chilling]
What is this?
- Even when I think about it again,
it's flustering. / - Seriously.
[(Deleting traces of the raw egg)]
- But it was pretty legendary...
- It was legendarily funny.
It's a video I'll watch from time to time.
- This can't be done even if it's planned.
- This is...
Are you done?
Let's go!
- I'll just bring eggs. / - Bring eggs!
[Stone-plate cooked eggs]
[Coldness returns because of the cold water]
It's cold.
It's hot.
[Ah]
It's really cold, right?
The water is so cold.
That was legendary.
- Seriously.
- It's so funny.
But I think we need a towel.
I think we need to wipe this.
Let's do that then.
Let's mix one raw egg in
[Betting-TEEN mode ON]
[Stone-plate cooked egg X raw egg= collab raffle]
with stone-plate cooked egg.
[Betting-TEEN mode ON]
[Stone-plate cooked egg X raw egg= collab raffle]
At random?
[At random, crack it on your own head (?)]
We'll each hold one egg on our heads.
- Wow... I hate it so much.
- Crack it for the person next to you.
[Just the thought of it]
That's good, too.
[S.COUPS adds onto it Kekeke]
Just from touching it...
- Just from touching it, can you not know?
- You don't know!
You don't know.
- Let's do it after we sweat a bit more.
- Yeah.
But now,
- DINO will probably bring it.
- It was fun, S.COUPS.
[(Calling DINO)]
- It was really fun. / - It was so funny.
[DINO's ringtone] [DINO left his cell phone]
- He left it. / - How flustering.
It's me.
[DINO's ringtone] [DINO left his cell phone]
What was cooked with a stone-plate...
[Checking the tavern refrigerator]
[Ah...!]
Seriously.
Oh, these guys!
[(?)]
They didn't take a proper look!
[The eggs were all labeled by category]
[⤣ JEONGHAN's pick, raw eggs]
[⤣ Stone-plate cooked eggs right below]
[(Egg assessor)]
[After shaking each one and taking them]
[Quickly returns to the sauna]
These are stone-plate cooked, right?
[(Eggs)]
You...
[(The whole story behind
the raw egg incident)]
- You took the ones on the very top, right?
- Yes.
The ones on the very top were raw eggs.
[If you look closely, it's written (?)...
Stone-plate cooked eggs]
On the bottom, there's tape that says
"Stone-plate cooked eggs"...
[If you look closely, it says (?)...
stone-plate cooked eggs]
- There are labels. / - It's written on tape?
[If you look closely, it says (?)...
stone-plate cooked eggs ❤]
Are raw eggs mixed in here?
- There are none.
- There are none?
If there was,
we were going to crack it on our own eggs.
[JEONGHAN has ideas when it comes to bets]
- Really? / - If there's one, we can mix it.
That sounds fun.
[JEONGHAN has ideas when it comes to bets]
Right?
I'll go bring one.
Are we not going to use the spa?
[※ There needs to be a bet for the jacuzzi, too ※]
- We have to use the spa!
Let's crack this and go use the spa.
[※ There needs to be a bet for the jacuzzi, too ※]
- With it on our heads? / - Yes.
[※ There needs to be an egg
on the head for the jacuzzi, too ※]
But are there no towels over there?
I'll bring towels if they're there.
[It's cold, but he's sprinting for a bet]
That was the most flustered
I've been as of late.
- That was the funniest to me as of late.
- I seriously did ab exercises.
[As they look back on
the intense raw egg event]
[JEONGHAN, who is serious about bets,
gets the raw egg]
It's cold!
[JEONGHAN, who is serious about bets,
gets the raw egg]
The towels are very cold.
[Doesn't forget the requested towels either]
They were outside.
[Preparing the egg raffle
as soon as he sits down]
Would I get it when there are 2?
Are you doing it right away?
No, later.
Is this too small?
[In the meantime, JOSHUA made
sheep ears for S.COUPS]
These are stone-plate cooked eggs we're eating.
[In the meantime, JOSHUA made
sheep ears for S.COUPS]
I'm starting to sweat.
The stone-plate cooked eggs we're eating.
[Copies and tries to make sheep ears ⤦]
I'm going to eat again later.
What if it's another raw egg when he cracks it?
[Aftereffects of being hit by a raw egg
are stuck in their heads]
I seriously won't stay put.
[Aftereffects of being hit by a raw egg
are stuck in their heads]
- This is a stone-plate cooked egg, right?
- Yes.
If you're not sure, crack it over here.
[(Suspicious first)]
[(Stares)]
It looks too small for your head, MINGYU.
[(Tada)]
[(Customized with no errors)]
It's nice.
It's nice!
[The lights... temperature... humidity...]
I'm sweating now.
- Okay. / - I'm starting to sweat now, too.
[Sweat is dripping after some time]
The ground is hot though.
- If SEUNGKWAN was here, he would
still be laughing. / - Yes, that's right.
How crazy.
I'm amazing, right?
I'm not
sweating at all. I need to sweat.
[(Soft and dry)]
- Do you want to switch spots?
- It's really dry.
- Yes.
- Yes, try...
- Switching spots. / - I guess it's too hot here.
[MINGYU↔DINO switch spots]
This side is hotter.
You'll probably sweat a lot
if you lean towards the stones, DINO.
- I'll get burned. / - You'll get burned.
- You'll sweat a lot from pain.
[What kind of joke is this]
- How old are you? / - How old are you?
[Mr. Pi Chulin (50s) / Specialty: Eyes of love]
How many minutes are you going to stay here?
I'll only ask you two.
[Only picks ⤦ these two ⤥]
You sweated so much.
I'm okay.
- I'm okay right now.
- Really?
Are you okay?
[(Not okay over here)]
I'm leaving in 3 minutes.
Then let's play a round!
[(The bet they talked about earlier)]
- Cover them. / - I'm going to cover them.
[※ No sorting the eggs ※]
[※ It's over once they pick it up ※]
There's no shaking allowed!
[※ No sorting the eggs ※]
[※ It's over once they pick it up ※]
- Just grab one and at the count of 3. / - Bam!
[※ No sorting the eggs ※]
[※ It's over once they pick it up ※]
Let's not do it at once then.
- Bam! Bam! Like this. / - Bam! Bam! Like this.
- Okay.
[With a relay to create thrill]
Let's play Rock-paper-scissors
and exclude 2 people.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Most nerve-racking moment]
- Rock-paper-scissors! / - What?
Rock-paper-scissors!
- Okay.
- Okay! The two of you are out.
No, there are 4!
[There's an error in the egg count,
so between MINGYU and DINO,
only 1 person is exempt]
Only one person is out.
The two of you, play Rock-paper-scissors.
[There's an error in egg count, so only between
MINGYU and DINO, only 1 person is exempt]
Rock-paper-scissors!
[The lucky one is]
Okay!
[The lucky one is MINGYU ★]
- Come here, Shua. / - It's one of these two.
Stop checking by touching them.
[- Not fighting, but picking eggs -]
- Then you mix them! / - Try it.
- It's these 4, right? / - Yes.
[- Not fighting, but picking eggs -]
Okay, here we go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
[MINGYU CAM]
Paper!
- Rock-paper-scissors! / - Okay.
[MINGYU CAM]
[(2 raw eggs)] [(2 stone-plate cooked eggs)]
- I'll go last. / - You're second.
[MINGYU CAM]
[(2 raw eggs)] [(2 stone-plate cooked eggs)]
Let's go. DINO. Go!
[MINGYU CAM]
[Switching the bet to being hit
with an egg chosen by the person on the side]
- Starting with DINO. / - DINO to S.COUPS?
[MINGYU CAM]
[Switching the bet to being hit
with an egg chosen by the person on the side]
I feel like it's going to be a raw egg.
[MINGYU CAM]
[Switching the bet to being hit
with an egg chosen by the person on the side]
The one I'm getting hit with, S.COUPS', is raw.
[MINGYU CAM]
[Switching the bet to being hit
with an egg chosen by the person on the side]
I think...
[MINGYU CAM]
[Egg picked by DINO →]
It's not!
[Egg picked by DINO → stone-plate cooked]
Mine is a raw egg.
This is seriously a raw egg.
[MINGYU CAM] [Current egg status]
[(2 raw eggs)] [(1 stone-plate cooked egg)]
Egg peel.
[MINGYU CAM] [Current egg status]
[(2 raw eggs)] [(1 stone-plate cooked egg)]
This is obviously a raw egg.
[MINGYU CAM]
Go!
[(Egg sorter)]
It's a raw egg. Go!
[MINGYU CAM]
[(Excited)]
- Do it on his forehead!
- Hey! On my head. / - No!
It's shaking so much.
[MINGYU CAM]
[As long as it's not me ^0^]
I don't think it's mine.
[MINGYU CAM]
[As long as it's not me ^0^]
[What is this???]
- It's not! / - It's not.
[MINGYU CAM]
[What is this???]
What is this?
[MINGYU CAM]
Then it's us two.
[- People left: JEONGHAN, DINO]
[- Eggs left: 2 raw eggs...?]
Should we do it together?
[MINGYU CAM]
[- People left: JEONGHAN, DINO]
[- Eggs left: 2 raw eggs...?]
1, 2...
[MINGYU CAM]
[- People left: JEONGHAN, DINO]
[- Eggs left: 2 raw eggs...?]
3!
[MINGYU CAM]
[Checking the eggs in a friendly way Kekeke]
DINO!
[MINGYU CAM]
[The results are a yolk party]
Were there 2 of these?
[MINGYU CAM]
[The results are a yolk party]
What is this?
Thank you!
There were 2 of these?
- Let's go out like this? / - It wasn't one?
[Hahaha]
How fun!
[MINGYU CAM]
DINO! Look here.
[(Eyes of love)]
JEONGHAN's! I cracked
[MINGYU CAM]
it pretty well.
[Even the producer likes the egg hat (?)]
- JEONGHAN... / - It's a hat.
[MINGYU CAM]
[Even the producer likes the egg hat (?)]
Can we take a photo?
[MINGYU CAM]
[Even the producer likes the egg hat (?)]
Okay! Let's take a photo.
[MINGYU CAM]
[Even the producer likes the egg hat (?)]
Let's take a photo, DINO.
1... 1, 2, 3!
[The raw egg was a raw egg... ★]
- We...
- Let's go out.
[Sweated and cracked eggs]
[It's time to go in the jacuzzi!]
It's so hot.
[Sweated and cracked eggs]
[It's time to go to the jacuzzi now!]
- Are we all going in? / - Let's go!
[Sweated and cracked eggs]
[It's time to go to the jacuzzi now!]
[⤤ Steaming~]
I seriously almost died.
[So refreshing outside-]
I'm so hot!
[S.COUPS, who got cold fast,
goes into the jacuzzi]
It's so cold. What do I do?
It's better here. Come here.
- Why am I missing a slipper? / - I don't know.
[DINO, who's wearing an egg hat,
also splashes into the jacuzzi]
It's not hot!
[DINO, who's wearing an egg hat,
also splashes into the jacuzzi]
Come on! It's not hot.
[(The egg hat steals the attention)]
- Okay! / - Come on!
It's cold.
[They all gathered and went into the jacuzzi]
It's cold!
[And then they looked up at the sky]
Look at the sky!
You can see stars.
It's so nice.
The stars are so visible.
There it is.
That's Cassiopeia.
- Hi, Cassiopeia.
- And...
[Then the members look up
at the sky for a long time]
Whoever loses at Rock-paper-scissors..
[Can't resist the instinct to bet]
Get out for 20 seconds?
Is there nothing new and different?
1.
[And suddenly, a timing game begins]
2.
- 3.
- 4.
5.
[(?)]
[Shooting merciless splashes]
- 1 is such cheating. / - He said 1.
[(Reporting the cheater)]
You're a cheater!
It wasn't me. It was him.
[First fake, second cheap]
- Is it you? / - I was 2!
1!
[First fake, second cheap]
- 2. / - 2.
- The two of them.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[S.COUPS is the loser anyway]
S.COUPS' concept today is good!
- Only S.COUPS got struck
with water a lot. / - 1.
[Kekeke]
- 2. / - 2.
[Overconfidence can be dangerous.]
Rock-paper-scissors!
[Like his friend, he's hit with water]
When we go,
we probably just have to run, right?
The living room will become an ocean, right?
[(The sleep zone)]
- Or after the last round,
- We didn't leave any towels outside.
[Betting-TEEN mode ON]
do you want to make the loser go first
- and lay out towels in a row?
Like a red carpet? / - The loser?
- Yes, that's good, too.
- Sounds good.
- Should we play the zero game? / - Okay.
[Yes?!]
- What are we doing with the zero game?
- They are excluded.
[The zero game, yes?!]
- You're excluded. / - You're excluded.
[#The_final_final_bet_is_the_zero_game]
[√ Winner is OUT] [√ The last person
will lay out towels in the living room]
- They're excluded?
- What are we doing with this?
[#The_final_final_bet_is_the_zero_game]
[√ Winner is OUT] [√ The last person
will lay out towels in the living room]
Go and lay out 10 towels.
[#The_final_final_bet_is_the_zero_game]
[√ Winner is OUT] [√ The last person
will lay out towels in the living room]
1, 2, 1.
1, 2, 2.
You're out.
[★ Today's lucky guy, MINGYU ★]
[Very serious... Very nervous...]
1, 2, 4.
Submerge your hands and do it.
So only the thumbs come up.
[Can't miss the detail]
Raise your thumbs.
[Giggles even at the little things]
I really like things like this.
Details.
I'll go then.
1, 2.
0.
[Careful inhaling and exhaling]
Listen.
1, 2, 2.
I'm out.
[JEONGHAN has escaped]
1, 2, 3.
He's out!
[(Escaped)]
[S.COUPS and DINO remain]
It's legendary if S.COUPS loses now.
[(A regular in the final round)]
- What's wrong with me today? / - Here...
- It's your day today!
Here we go.
1, 2, 0.
[(Looks down)] [S.COUPS lost]
0.
1, 2, 0.
[(Happy)] [(Tada) Today's footage maker)]
0!
- 0!
- 0! / - 0!
[All but one is partying]
- 0! / - Do a 0 dance!
[Showing his happiness]
We can go in about 4 minutes.
I was rooting for you, S.COUPS.
- How did he lose at everything? / - 1, 2, 0.
[Kekeke]
Even if you squeeze there, you have to...
[(Clenches his jaw)]
[Seriousness shown in his face]
I'm going to get up like this.
[The loser is getting up now...]
Are you going?
- You'll feel less cold if you take off your top.
- I should take it off.
- But the towel is like ice.
- Yeah.
- That's why I said it was hard
because I saw it earlier. / - The towel is big.
- I think this is enough. / - I think this is enough.
[S.COUPS leaves for a long trip with the ice towel]
Go!
[Kekekekeke]
Call us over!
Ack!
It's so cold!
[Footage maker returns all worn-out]
[Starts setting up a full course towel carpet
from the entrance to the bathroom]
[Even up until the last towel~]
What is this?
I lost a bet, so I have to lay this out right now.
What did you do, JUN?
- Whatever. / - Did you sing?
[A relationship where they ask each other
what they've been up to (?)]
No, I just heard you.
[A relationship where they ask each other
what they've been up to (?)]
[Screaming heard from somewhere
Kekekekeke]
[The forestmen run toward the sleep zone]
What is this?
[Returning to the sleep zone
with steaming bodies]
You don't get much warmer
from coming in here.
That was youth.
What is this?
There's a youthful vibe to this!
Great job, S.COUPS.
[The members go to wash up
while stepping on S.COUPS' towel carpet]
- You did so much! / - I went and he was inside.
[The members go to wash up
while stepping on S.COUPS' towel carpet]
- Hey, but you laid out the towels so well.
- Yeah!
It's done well!
[After going to the sauna]
[SEVENTEEN is washing up and cleaning]
Is someone washing up right now?
Shua and DINO.
I'll wash up after them.
What did you do?
I just...
- I heard the guys sing. / - Where are the others?
[JUN watched the members play]
- SEUNGKWAN and Minghao...
- Earlier, they all... I didn't see Minghao.
[Suddenly curious about the members]
- Are they sleeping? / - What is Minghao doing?
[Come to think of it... Where is THE 8?]
I guess he's sleepy after mountain climbing.
[Meanwhile, at the personal sleep zone]
THE 8!
Are you sleeping, THE 8?
Good night!
This smells good.
[The sleep zone is busy getting ready to sleep]
This?
[Powdery shea butter scent]
[Body lotion that captivates the members' noses]
[The members share good things]
Are you all washed up?
- Huh? / - Are you all washed up?
[The members share good things]
What are you going to do?
[Beast quantities that are more than enough
even when applied plentifully]
[All done rehydrating]
[Meanwhile, SEUNGKWAN grabs
the pillow mist that helps with good sleep]
[Sharing a cozy, sleepy scent]
I heard spraying this makes it cozy.
I hope the members feel cozy
when they sleep.
[Another night in the forest
passes by peacefully today]
Then let's go with something weak.
How about 22%?
[???]
- 22%.
- 22%. Okay.
We'll finish after exactly 3 bottles today.
Exactly 3 bottles.
[The members are
having drinks in the food zone]
Try just one bite, DINO.
[The members are
having drinks in the food zone]
I think Andong soju is really good.
- Really. / - But you know what's funny?
We drank here and...
Oh! Hold on!
Let's open another bottle!
- It's really good.
- I think we need
to go a little faster because of the appetizer!
[Planning to overdrink again today?!]
- It's sort of nice, right?
- You... you made this well.
[Planning to overdrink again today?!]
- It tastes like peppers. / - You made this so well.
- It's delicious.
[The fish cake soup appetizer calls for alcohol]
It warms me up right away.
It feels like I'm eating
after coming out of the sauna...
- That sleepiness...
- It's so nice.
How this warms me up on the inside...
Oh, it's nice!
Why is it so good?
[Very satisfied]
But it got so cold.
It suddenly got cold.
- It gets this cold?
- It's really interesting how
I saw that it would be warm for 2 days
and cold for 2 days at "IN THE SOOP".
[Feels like they experience all 4 seasons
in the forest during the short time]
On the weather report.
[Feels like they experience all 4 seasons
in the forest during the short time]
- But it's precise.
- But it's precisely cold starting today.
[Feels like they experience all 4 seasons
in the forest during the short time]
Even back on the first day,
[Looking back on
the weather, mood, and emotions]
- we said that it was hot.
- It was hot! / - Yeah, we said something.
[Looking back on
the weather, mood, and emotions]
"Let's eat something refreshing!"
We said this and ate bibimguksu (spicy noodles).
[It's very different now from
the first day at the forest]
It's cold in the morning now.
[It's very different now from
the first day at the forest]
But I...
I don't know why,
but Korea has a wintery smell, right?
When it's really cold.
- I get excited when I smell that.
- I like it, too. / - Me too.
- Me too.
- The smell of when winter is coming...
That smell makes me so excited.
I think it's the smell of foliage
or the smell of the wind...
- It feels like it comes straight into the nose.
- That's right!
[Season changes bring excitement]
There's a smell to that!
- There's a smell. / - That's right. The smell...
[Season changes bring excitement]
- It does.
- How do I explain this...
♪ Smells like fall
[♬]
There's that song.
"Your Scent".
Seriously...
That was so cute.
[Kekeke]
Seriously...
[Can't stand things like this ⤦]
It's nice... It's really nice.
Is there nothing to do?
Is everything sleeping now?
[The members in the sleep zone
are going to sleep one by one]
Boo Seungkwan and Wen Junhui?
Always a hot night...
Where are you sleeping?
On the second floor.
Good night.
[Bound for great sleep with good nights zzz]
[At this time, somebody
comes into the sleep zone]
[HOSHI soon heads outside with WOOZI]
Everyone is a little quiet today.
- Oh my! The moon is pretty, Jihoon.
- That's true!
[Briefly stopping on their way]
Today,
we can see the stars well.
[Briefly stopping on their way
and looking up at the night sky]
Wow...
It's insane.
That wasn't the only bright one.
That one with the 3 is that...
[(Stars)]
I learned this when I was young...
How do those 3 shine like that?
Today is insane.
[Countless stars in the night sky in the forest]
It's really insane.
- Meanwhile, a plane is flying by.
- Yeah.
I always think that.
Whenever you're on a plane, you look out
the window and below at the ground, right?
[(Outside)]
Then you can see
regions like this.
[Countless people on the ground
seen from the sky]
So when I see that...
[Countless people on the ground
seen from the sky]
I'm flying to another country like this,
[Countless people on the ground
seen from the sky]
but people below
are all each living their lives.
[Curious about others' lives]
- Yeah. / - But it's the other way around now.
Someone is riding in that plane
and flying somewhere
and has their own life.
That's quite amazing.
But I can
see the stars really well. This is insane.
[The stars in the night sky bring a lot to mind]
I can see them so well that it's about to scare me.
[(The stars)]
The sky is really high up.
[As the stars are shining, in the food zone]
It's my dream to drink alcohol
at a cart bar.
- It's pretty nice. / - I went once when
I went to Yeosu with my friend.
[DINO visited a cart bar with a friend in Yeosu]
- That street with cart bars? / - Yes.
[(I know it)]
But at the time,
- there were a lot of people.
- Yeah, there are a lot there.
- It's not easy to eat comfortably there.
- It wasn't comfortable.
[Couldn't comfortably enjoy the cart bar]
Being recognized could be okay,
- but the conversation topics change.
- That's right!
How the conversation topics change
makes me uncomfortable.
[DINO agrees with MINGYU's point]
I don't think things like that bother me lately.
For example, if I go drink with MINGYU or
the four of us go to drink outside
at a cart bar or wherever we want,
- nobody would point fingers at us!
- That's right.
In some ways...
It was during our debut...
[Cautious about everything
in their early debut days]
- It was impossible back then.
- We were careful and created our image.
[Cautious about everything
in their early debut days]
But even now, there's a need for that
to a certain extent.
But it has disappeared a lot though.
- And honestly, that's how many methods of
communication there are. / - It has opened up.
[Through various communication methods]
- There are ways. / - That's why...
"I drank a bit with the members right now."
[Through various communication methods,
SEVENTEEN can share their daily lives with CARAT]
Because we're showing more and more...
[Through various communication methods,
SEVENTEEN can share their daily lives with CARAT]
For some reason, I like it when I meet
CARAT when I'm out drinking.
When I meet them coincidentally!
So suddenly...
Let's say I went to drink.
If I run into them, I like it!
[Meeting CARAT coincidentally
makes S.COUPS happy]
Even as they pass by...
"We have a lot of fans. There are CARATs."
[(Arounds us)]
I met CARATs at a barbecue
restaurant in Daegu once.
[(Coincidentally)]
I gave them a drink and
I also received a drink and we drank together.
[A moment that will remain
a fun memory for S.COUPS]
I clinked glasses with them, drank,
came out, and paid for them.
[A moment that will remain
a fun memory for S.COUPS]
At our fan signing a few days ago...
There's this Japanese band that I like.
But a fan came and I recommended that song.
[CARAT shared news of a new album
from a band that MINGYU recommended]
They said that person released a new album.
[CARAT shared news of a new album
from a band that MINGYU recommended]
But I don't think I had
ever seen that CARAT before
based on my memory.
In that short time,
a new album came out.
[CARAT recommended a few tracks
off of the new album]
"Listen to this and this on that album."
[CARAT recommended a few tracks
off of the new album]
"I'll come again tomorrow!"
She said this and left.
[CARAT recommended a few tracks
off of the new album]
- But I was so curious.
- Yes, since it's also a singer you like.
So I listened and it was so good!
We met the second time and
- that person was so memorable.
- Yes, that's inevitable.
[A precious memory where he connected
through music with a new CARAT]
"I heard the song yesterday! It was so good."
[A precious memory where he connected
through music with a new CARAT]
Because a song that my fan
recommended to me is on my playlist,
- that felt sort of weird.
- It was weird!
- It must be.
- The fans give good suggestions.
- Because they know our ways well. / - Yeah.
[SEVENTEEN and CARAT
know each other better than anyone]
They give me a lot of recommendations, too.
[SEVENTEEN and CARAT
know each other better than anyone]
What was really nice is that
there was a fan
that really loved Michael Jackson.
- Michael Jackson?
- Yes. / - That's possible!
- But that's not easy.
- We can't really relate.
- It's not easy for our generation
- to fall for Michael Jackson.
- That's right.
But she came to our fan signing
and said she likes Michael Jackson.
[DINO's role model that inspired him
to become a singer was Michael Jackson]
I said a few songs that only I knew
since Michael Jackson has so many famous songs.
I said the song titles
and she knew them all!
That's why I suddenly spoke casually.
[DINO was excited to share similar tastes]
- "Wow, really?" / - You'd get excited, too!
"How do you know this song?"
Saying things like this.
[DINO was excited to share similar tastes]
It was so fun that
we could go back and forth.
So I think those sorts of experiences are precious.
It's very weird.
- I agree.
- It's really strange.
People... I...
[(One more bottle...?)]
I predicted it!
I'm going to go today. It's okay!
Let's open another bottle!
I'm...
Want to parody "Work Later, Drink Now"?
Sir! We have appetizers left,
but there's no alcohol!
I think my life
- is included in it. That concept is sort of...
- That's right.
[The conversation continues on all night]
- Just... / - You didn't light the fire. There's that.
The reins...
[The conversation continues on all night
and bottles keep increasing]
- I'm sorry. I love you. / - I love you.
[The conversation continues on all night
and bottles keep increasing]
It needs to be combined.
[The conversation continues on all night
and bottles keep increasing]
I was really worried about "IN THE SOOP",
but I feel like I'm leaving with more.
- It's nice, right?
- It's nice. I'm relieved. / - I'm...
- I love you. / - I love you. / - I love you.
[Darkness has disappeared outside]
[The members who talked all night
have returned to the sleep zone now]
[Everyone is sleeping at
"IN THE SOOP" once it's bright]
[While everyone is asleep
in the forest, morning dew has fallen]
[Warm sunlight is shining]
[A new morning has risen at "IN THE SOOP"]
[Cabin sleep zone]
[The mysterious alarm?]
[(Who is it)]
[At the cabin sleep zone,
a mysterious alarm rings?]
[(It's me...)]
[Alarm OFF ⤤]
[Going straight back into sleep mode]
[What about the group sleep zone?]
[Still in dreamland zZZ]
[(Gets up)]
[SEUNGKWAN (?) got up 1st]
[(Walking Bboo)]
[He opens his eyes and comes outside]
[Naturally walking towards the food zone]
What should I eat?
[Still sleepy]
[What he took out of the refrigerator]
[(Precious)]
[5 eggs ⤦]
[Cracks all 5 eggs]
[Beats them,]
[Beats them, cooks them,]
[Beats them, cooks them, and plates them]
[Looks delicious]
[SEUNGKWAN's breakfast is finished!]
It looks good.
[Looks delicious]
[SEUNGKWAN's breakfast is finished!]
[(I'm going to hurry up and eat)]
I'm hungry!
I'm proud that I made this.
Can't strawberry jam usually add mood?
[As much as he's proud]
[He wants to take a pretty photo]
Just eat it!
[Piling it on top of the bread]
[Takes a bite with no hesitation]
[(Hm, this is what it's about)]
[Filling both cheeks]
[Gulp gulp]
[Cleansing the palate with milk]
[Once his stomach is full]
I enjoyed the food!
[Washing the plates right after eating]
What is this?
[!!!]
What is this? Where am I turning this on?
[Out of it]
[Turning on cold water on the table Kekeke]
[Doing the dishes and still waking up]
[Should I take a cup of coffee outside]
Oh, it's a nice day!
Are they all still sleeping?
[Mr. Coffee comes out for a forest walk
with a cup of coffee again today]
Mood.
What is this?
Are there no clouds today?
It's so pretty!
[SEUNGKWAN's morning
mood spot is the fire pit]
[Huh...?]
Why is it wet here?
[The chair was wet from
the morning dew ⤥]
I'm so unlucky!
It's okay.
[Changing to a less wet chair]
[SEUNGKWAN is finally
freely enjoying a cup of coffee]
[Staring blankly...]
I feel like my neck is going to burn.
[T T]
[Since his neck is precious...]
When will Shua wake up?
Shua!
[Calling out to empty space]
Joshua Hong!
[(No way he would hear...)]
Is that window open? On the 2nd floor?
[And someone comes out of the sleep zone]
[Fixed morning wake-up member is THE 8]
[Where THE 8 goes right away is]
[Where THE 8 goes right away is the food zone]
[Going through the refrigerator first]
What should I eat?
- Minghao. / - Huh?
[In the meantime, DK arrived]
This is a dejavu.
I came in the morning yesterday
and you were the only one here.
I'm going to make huang men ji today.
Huang men ji?
What was that again?
Huang men ji.
- Is that like Andong jjimdak (soy sauce
braised chicken)? / - Yes.
[Huang men ji / A Chinese chicken dish
that similar to Korea's jjimdak]
- Hello?
What are you doing, THE 8?
[JEONGHAN called THE 8
as soon as he woke up]
Me? I'm cooking food.
[JEONGHAN called THE 8
as soon as he woke up]
Make me mala longxia, THE 8.
[♥]
- Today? Right now?
- Yes.
You eat mala longxia in the day?
Then do you eat it at night?
I think that's better at night.
You'll feel sick if you eat it in the morning.
[Spicy mala flavors]
[THE 8 is worried it'll upset his stomach]
What are you making right now?
Right now, huang men ji!
This will be good, too.
- Okay. / - Yes.
[(Got it)]
[THE 8's huang men ji recipe]
[1. Cut chicken in good sizes to eat]
[2. Cut mushrooms and vegetables]
[Doubanjiang + Chinese soy sauce +
oyster sauce = THE 8's sauce]
[Adding the prepped chicken to the oil]
[A ton of vegetables,
a ton of sauce]
[THE 8's bubbling huang men ji is done]
[Yum]
[(Mm~!]
Is it good?
It's so good.
[Satisfied]
[JEONGHAN has entered the food zone]
- You woke up? / - Yes.
[Yes]
I was going to call you.
[JEONGHAN is going to have TIME
to blank out since he's not fully awake]
[Pink sausage enters]
Oh, VERNON!
Yo!
[(Hi, did you sleep well?)]
Let's go.
[(VERNON's eyes are fixed)]
♪ It's amazing
Yo!
[(Looks good, how exciting)]
[JEONGHAN, THE 8, and VERNON are
gathered and starting breakfast]
Let's try it.
[JEONGHAN, THE 8, and VERNON are
gathered and starting breakfast]
- I'll enjoy the food! / - I'll enjoy the food!
[JEONGHAN, THE 8, and VERNON are
gathered and starting breakfast]
- There's the one we always order.
- Huang men ji?
[He ordered huang men ji often with
VERNON at the dorms]
This? Oh, really?
[He ordered huang men ji often with
VERNON at the dorms]
You order Chinese food with VERNON?
Yes!
But I...
I order it and he eats it next to me.
[He tends to eat it with him if THE 8 orders it]
Is it to your liking, JEONGHAN?
Yes, it's good.
What are you making, DK?
[Delicious sounds can be heard from the kitchen]
Curry.
[Smell of butter~]
[Smell of butter~ Stir frying onions, too]
Whenever I come here, I feel like
I run a Chinese restaurant.
[Smell of butter~ Stir frying onions, too]
[Stir frying pork, potatoes, and carrots as well]
It's fun stir frying this.
Isn't there some sort of tomato sauce?
[Adding a ton of tomato paste,
water, and curry powder!]
[DK's tomato curry is done!]
[(Hm... This taste is...!)]
- Hey, I changed the menu.
- To what?
Tomato stew.
[Changed the menu]
[Tomato curry ➨ tomato stew]
Tomato stew.
[Tomato stew (?) is coming out~]
Do you want a bowl of this?
Tomato stew?
[Mustard sauce is also here]
It's WONWOO.
I'll enjoy the food.
[DK's tomato stew time]
Eat a lot!
It looks like Hayashi rice! You made it well!
[The tomato stew draws attention]
- Well... / - How is it?
- It's good! Try it!
- Really? Let me try it.
Try it with the meat.
In a video,
I saw someone make Japanese style curry
with O**ogi curry.
You said that you like Japanese style curry.
- Is that why you made it? / - Of course!
[(Sort of moved)]
- It's good! / - It's decent!
[♥]
It doesn't seem
like tomato stew.
[Meerkats smelled
the tomato stew and gathered]
It's okay because I added a bit more curry.
[Meerkats smelled
the tomato stew and gathered]
It seems like curry.
[Meerkats smelled
the tomato stew and gathered]
Eat it!
Okay.
Since you made it for me...
- It's good, DK!
- Is it okay?
Eat it with kimchi.
With kimchi!
Come over here!
I think it's really good, DK.
[Scoops up a plate of DK's tomato stew]
- The curry is really good. / - Is it good?
[Starts eating a 2nd breakfast]
But it's really good.
[A delicious and happy time
with the members]
- Hey, DK!
- Yes?
Is it Cheongnyangsan?
Should we go out just to the temple?
Do you want to go to the temple?
- Honestly, going to the temple is doable!
- Right?
How long does it take to the temple?
- You're supposed to go up the mountain
after the temple. / - 20 minutes.
[Convinced by the advice of those who went]
- It only takes 20 minutes? / - Yes.
The sky bridge is tough.
The temple is okay.
Okay!
Should we go wake up HOSHI?
But why are you waking him up?
- We have to go at 1:30.
- We said we'd go mountain climbing together.
[HOSHI is still sleeping]
♪ Sleeping
[(Shall we wake up HOSHI)]
[Entering with strange laughs]
We came to wake you up!
[Hahahahaha]
Hurry up and wake up.
Are we going at 1?
Yes!
Let's go.
Not to dreamland, but mountain climbing!
We will see you get up and leave.
[Not an easy guy]
So you can't sleep again.
[This isn't simple...]
It's cold outside.
Can you really get ready?
- Yes.
- Okay.
It's cold outside, so dress warmly!
- Yes!
- Got it?
- Leave at 1?
- Isn't it 1:30?
When do you want to leave?
Do you want to leave at 1 or 1:30?
[(Whatever you want)]
- 1:30.
- 1:30?
You're going to sleep again, right?
[(Suspicious look)]
What if he sleeps 30 more
minutes and gets ready?
[(Awkward)]
- Okay.
- 1:30.
- 1:30? / - Yes.
[After establishing a time,
JEONGHAN and DK leave]
[A moment later]
This is how we switch up the mood.
[The meeting time is approaching]
[Will HOSHI be awake?]
HOSHI!
- HOSHI! / - HOSHI!
[(In that same spot)]
We have to go.
- We have to go! / - Let's go!
[It's not a dejavu...]
Let's go!
We have to go.
Are you all ready?
We have to go!
He's the same as when we woke him up earlier.
Wear pants!
[It's 1:30 ♪]
- I can't believe I'm mountain
climbing with HOSHI! / - Yeah.
Would you go mountain climbing with me
if I call you in Seoul as well, HOSHI?
Would you not go?
I would go.
"I would go."
[SEUNGKWAN and JOSHUA
are going to a cafe]
JOSHUA! Let's go to a cafe.
[SEUNGKWAN and JOSHUA
are going to a cafe]
They sell shaved ice, too!
- At the cafe? / - Yes!
[(Shaved ice?!?!)]
When are you going?
There are 30 minutes left.
Get ready.
[Gets up]
- Do you really want to eat it? / - Yes.
You're eating something delicious!
[(This is VERNON, who just ate breakfast)]
Boo Seungkwan!
[Back]
Choi Hansol!
[And forth]
[VERNON leaves to get ready to go out]
L'O**itane is the best.
The body lotion is so nice.
[JOSHUA is moisturizing]
It's nice.
[(Satisfied with the subtle scents)]
I've never gone on a drive with
SEUNGKWAN before.
A drive? That's right!
- I've never driven you before.
- Yes.
But...
[Q. How are your driving skills?]
I think I'm at a beginner or intermediate level.
But I'm still a little nervous
when I drive people.
[How will SEUNGKWAN's driving skills be?]
For some reason... Yes.
Let's go!
[Meanwhile, the Cheongnyang
Temple climbing team]
Okay!
[Meanwhile, the Cheongnyang
Temple climbing team]
[(Sigh)]
- HOSHI! Look at nature.
- Yes.
You're fully awake right now, right?
No.
You're not fully awake?
Yes, I'm making an effort for you, HOSHI.
Why won't my eyes open?
- HOSHI.
- Yes.
Please sing ♪ Green hills.
[(Like an AI speaker)]
♪ Golden sun
Raise it a key.
[(Input)]
[(Output)]
Nice!
[How JEONGHAN wakes up HOSHI]
♪ Looking for the flowing water in the creek
♪ Where we can hear the echoes
♪ Leaving for a trip
Nice.
Coming out like this makes me feel
like we came out over the weekend.
Right?
With my family...
It's been so long since
I've gone mountain climbing.
We're on a mountain!
Let's go!
I'm mountain climbing!
But what mountain is this?
Cheongnyang...
Right when you look, it's refreshing!
[No use in saying this]
- It's our mountain!
It's SEVENTEEN's mountain! / - Yeah!
[It's so nice]
- We can call this SEVENTEEN's mountain.
- That's true.
[Refreshing idols have come
to Cheongnyangsan]
It's nice.
[Refreshing idols have come
to Cheongnyangsan]
- More than anything, it's nice
because I'm with HOSHI. / - Me too.
It's nice mountain climbing with you, too.
[Me too!]
- Yeah. / - I'm going to be with
HOSHI all day long today.
[Plans to stick next to HOSHI all day]
- That sounds good. / - How is that, HOSHI?
- It sounds nice.
- Let's go and
do survivals, eat lamb skewers, and drink beer.
["Today's to do list"]
That sounds good.
Okay.
It won't be that cold when we go.
- Hello.
- Hello. / - Hello.
[(Friendly)]
My face has less pressure.
[Boom]
- Hey! Me too. / - That's right.
[Clap]
Should we go a little faster?
Sounds good.
- 1, 2. / - 1!
[Sudden scenario]
[Mountain climbing changed to boot camp]
Try this, JEONGHAN. It's really tiring.
[Tiger] [※ Beware of wild animals ※]
Mentality!
Let's go!
Hey!
[Passion] [After repetitive
mountain climbing and boot camp]
Cheongnyang Temple!
[Arrived at Cheongnyang Temple]
Shall we feel the landscape?
It's pretty here.
[Admiration automatically comes out
from seeing the grand mountain]
1, 2.
3!
[Taking a photo with
the landscape as background!]
[#Today's_mountain_climbing_is_complete]
If we keep walking like this,
the peak will come out.
- Consistently, right?
- SEVENTEEN is always running toward the top.
- If we are consistent, right?
- Yes.
Should we meditate here?
Sounds good.
Close your eyes and feel nature.
[Emptying what's on their minds
while feeling the wind]
[Meditation time of purifying their hearts]
[Peeks] [Meditation time of purifying their hearts]
[(The type that can't focus)]
When are we doing this until?
[Is he sleeping?]
- It's nice, right, HOSHI?
- Yes.
The world is clear, right?
- The green looks more green.
- Right?
It looks more dimensional, too.
I think it's very nice.
The wind is amazing.
Since we're here,
should we eat some seaweed?
[Plain rejection]
[Brought seaweed to the forest himself Kekeke]
- Are you eating seaweed?
- Yes.
[Each taking seaweed]
If you eat seaweed,
then you're recharged on salt.
- Cheers together?
- Okay.
Cheers with seaweed.
- Cheers. / - Cheers.
[_★]
[(Happiness of a piece of seaweed)]
[Saltiness after mountain climbing]
- How is it?
- It's really good.
Seaweed after mountain climbing.
It's good!
[The seaweed builds their appetite]
Let's get rice cake and eat it, too!
- Let's go!
- Okay.
It's nice.
You must be hungry because you didn't eat.
[(HOSHI)]
Hello!
- Hello! / - Hello!
[The members are at a cafe near
Cheongnyang Temple]
It's omija tea.
[The members are at a cafe near
Cheongnyang Temple]
- I'm Omija. / - "I'm Omija."
[Haha]
- It's pretty.
- People would think your name is Omija.
- We'll enjoy it!
- Yes.
But it's so pretty!
[Drinking warm tea after sweating]
Shall we try it?
Oh! It's sort of like maesilcha (green plum tea).
Is it good?
[Hm~ So good ❤]
It's sort of good because there's a bit
of honey in these squares.
[The honey is immersed sweetly in
the crispy and soft rice cakes]
- It's good.
- Yes.
It's nice that it wasn't dunked it honey.
- Really?
- Yes.
Eating something warm...
[Yum]
Your body is relieved, right?
[(Ah)]
You're not drinking makgeolli, right?
[It's not makgeolli, right? Kekeke]
- Can I try it?
- Yes.
The omija tea is fruity!
Shall we get going now?
Okay! Let's go!
[After enjoying the mountain and tea,
it's time to go down the mountain]
I think today will be pretty memorable.
[Mountain gods come down with canes Kekeke]
The fact that I mountain climbed with HOSHI
- and JEONGHAN!
- That's right.
This will be the most amazing memory.
[The most amazing moment of
"IN THE SOOP" to DK]
Be well, mountain!
Mountain!
You can do a good job, right, SEUNGKWAN?
[(At driving)]
[Meanwhile, what about the drive team?]
Yes!
[❤]
[Meanwhile, what about the drive team?]
Let's go!
I will drive you safely.
It's so crazy that SEUNGKWAN is driving.
[(Can't believe SEUNGKWAN is driving)]
It's so crazy right now.
Yeah. I said I really wanted
to get my driver's license.
- Yeah. / - Since I said that.
[SEUNGKWAN's dream came true]
It's so crazy.
How many times did you say you failed?
[(Failed at holding in their laughter)]
Well...
[Failed at holding in their laughter)]
I failed the driving course test 3 times.
But the driving course test...
It was very unfortunate.
[$#...!]
Where is this?
[Streets are still hard for a beginning driver]
Here!
[With VERNON's help]
Here.
[With VERNON's help, they find the way safely]
Nice! You're doing well!
Thank you.
[With help and support,
Bboo car is being driven well]
It's so nice that it's the season where
the color of the leaves change.
[With help and support,
Bboo car is being driven well]
This is so pretty.
[The time when the green trees
are changing to reddish hues]
I want to hurry up and
eat shaved ice and pancakes!
When we shot a reality show, VERNON
[Briefly sharing a memory]
came to my house in Jeju-do and ate.
VERNON was eating and...
His grandma cooks very well, right?
[(VERNON's)]
He said he was thinking of
his grandma for a second!
Then my mom put out side dishes.
He should've said, "Oh, mother!"
"Oh, grandma...!"
[(Still nerve-racking now)]
So...
He said grandma,
so I laughed so much.
- But my mom said, "I am a grandma!"
- "I am a grandma."
I feel like your mom would've said that.
I could imagine it.
This time around...
[Another family comes up since
they're talking about families]
During the tour,
[Another family comes up since
they're talking about families]
Sofia came to the waiting room, right?
[VERNON's younger sister]
- Her laugh was exactly like VERNON's!
- That's right.
[(Totally agrees)]
It's a given, but...
That was sort of amazing.
The vibe of siblings is...
[(Resembling)]
- Definitely. / - WONWOO's younger
brother is like that, too.
- That's right. / - WONWOO's younger brother
is pretty much his doppelgänger.
When I see you guys, I think,
"What if I had siblings?"
It made me curious about that.
But your mom seems like your older sister.
Really? My mom?
[(You're watching, right, ma'am?)]
[After chatting, they've arrived at the cafe]
We're almost there.
Let's go!
- I'm hungry. It's nice!
- I'm hungry! There's also salad.
- Hello!
Wow! Croffles!
- We have to eat croffles, too.
- We have to order this no matter what.
First off, we have to eat croffles.
- 1 injeolmi shaved ice and...
["Foodies order LIST"]
1 fresh fruit pancake and...
[Injeolmi shaved ice]
And 1 of these croffles.
["Foodies order LIST"]
[Injeolmi shaved ice+fresh fruit pancake]
- 1 croffle and... / 1 croffle and...
["Foodies order LIST"]
[Injeolmi shaved ice+fresh fruit pancake]
I'd like an iced americano.
["Foodies order LIST"]
[Injeolmi shaved ice+fresh fruit pancake+croffle]
For me...
["Foodies order LIST"]
[Injeolmi shaved ice+fresh fruit pancake+croffle
+iced americano]
Hazelnut latte.
["Foodies order LIST"]
[Injeolmi shaved ice+fresh fruit pancake+croffle
+iced americano]
What about you, VERNON?
["Foodies order LIST"]
[Injeolmi shaved ice+fresh fruit pancake+croffle
+iced americano+hazelnut latte]
An iced cinnamon rooibos.
["Foodies order LIST"]
[Injeolmi shaved ice+fresh fruit pancake+croffle
+iced americano+hazelnut latte]
Where should we sit?
- Here.
- It's so nice here.
The blue spot!
[The beverages come out first]
- Thank you. / - Thanks.
[The beverages came out first]
This is SEUNGKWAN's.
[Satisfied]
- Is it good? / - Yeah.
Do you want to try it?
[Oh! Yes!]
[Thirst quenched]
As expected, I think
hazelnut lattes are so good.
2, 3!
[(Taking a photo in the cafe randomly)]
- Thanks. / - Thank you!
[Most awaited injeolmi shaved ice comes]
- This is so much! / - It looks so good.
Hold on.
[Most awaited injeolmi shaved ice comes]
- It would've been bad if we ordered
a green tea shaved ice, too. / - Yeah.
Do you want some of the ice cream on top?
- Should we each try a bite
of the ice cream on top? / - A bite each.
But are those peanuts?
[Has an allergy]
[(...Ha)]
There are so many peanuts!
[Are you peanuts...?]
Are they peanuts?
[SEUNGKWAN tries it first]
No, they're... peanuts.
They're so peanuts.
Are these peanuts?
[Checking again]
[Chewing]
Somewhat...
I'll hope that they say
"No, they're almonds!"
I'll go report it myself!
- I'll go it report myself with a mic.
- Reporter SEUNGKWAN!
[Reporter SEUNGKWAN on the move]
Are these peanuts?
[(Sprinting Bboo)]
Ma'am.
Is the thing in the shaved ice...
Are there peanuts in it?
[Reporter SEUNGKWAN's close coverage on site]
[(Hoping that there are no peanuts)]
Sometimes, it tastes like peanuts
when it's not peanuts.
[(Hoping that there are no peanuts)]
- They're not? / - The results are...
[Reporter SEUNGKWAN runs over]
They're almonds and walnuts!
[Breaking!] [!News]
[Speed ★★★★★]
[Accuracy ★★★★★]
- I thought they were peanuts. / - I can tell
they're walnuts and almonds after chewing.
Now that you mention it.
[Sweet]
- But it's really good.
- Yes, it's good.
It's so good.
- It's good!
It's been so long since I've had shaved ice.
Me too.
The ice cream is so good, too.
[Endless dessert serving]
Thank you!
[Warm croffle & a pancake with tons
of toppings have come!]
Hey! This is legit.
[Warm croffle & a pancake with tons
of toppings have come!]
This is pretty much pizza crust!
[Warm croffle & a pancake with tons
of toppings have come!]
[Desserts are about to break the table]
[Big bite]
[Big bite] [This is what it's about]
It sort of tastes like egg bread!
Oh, really?
- I like egg bread.
- I like it, too.
That's what it tastes like?
It smells like that.
- Really... If I drink too much... / - Hello?
[(I want to try it, too)]
[The final night of "IN THE SOOP 2" has come]
[The survival game that's been pushed off]
[Relaxing walk]
[The members enjoy the forest
in their own way]
DINO! He has a connection to fire.
[If the fire pit zone is filled one by one]
I have a connection to fire.
Fire is all about your breath.
[If the fire pit zone is filled one by one]
Can the mafia wake up and kill 1 person?
[SEVENTEEN + mafia = best combination]
What are you doing, Boo Seungkwan?
Let's kill him!
Why did police stay still?
[Can't miss the suspicious gazes]
I actually thought I would die just now.
[The moment he comes out emotionally]
[The sophisticated defenses continue]
The mafia is...
[The time of being tricked and tricking]
[(Shocked)]
[And the identity of the mafia is revealed]
You're the mafia?
[(Shocked)]
[And the identity of the mafia is revealed]
This gaze!
[(Not believing anyone anymore)]
[(Fingers are filled with betrayal)]
This... This...
[(Not believing anyone anymore)]
[(Fingers are filled with betrayal)]
1, 2, 3!
[Please look forward to SEVENTEEN's forest life
with unending laughs until the end ❤]
Say you're not mafia.
[Please look forward to SEVENTEEN's forest life
with unending laughs until the end ❤]