♪ How about some pajeon by the stream?
[S.COUPS] [JEONGHAN] [JOSHUA]
♪ How about working out twice a day?
[JUN] [WONWOO] [HOSHI] [WOOZI]
♪ How about we fly in the sky?
[THE 8] [MINGYU] [DK]
♪ Or zone out into the fire while you lean on me?
[SEUNGKWAN] [VERNON] [DINO]
♪ In the SOOP
♪ SOOP du ru du du ru du
(Yes, let's go there)
[SEVENTEEN IN THE SOOP 2]
[The following content
includes ads and sponsorship]
♪ SEVENTEEN is In the SOOP
[SEVENTEEN IN THE SOOP 2]
[The following content
includes ads and sponsorship]
- HOSHI will go in the water, too...
- Are you doing it together?
[At the peaceful "IN THE SOOP"]
1, 2, 3!
[(Splash) Time to get in the water]
I take back saying he's the most kind after Jesus.
[Living and dying from bets]
I have a bit more strength in my legs again now.
[THE 8, SEUNGKWAN, and VERNON
finished mountain climbing]
Out of fragrant ones,
there are black tea and oolong tea.
[Time to relieve fatigue with
a tea ceremony has come to them]
It helps with breaking down fat.
[Enticed] [Shall I try it] [ðŸ”¥HOTðŸ”¥]
[(Kekekeke)]
[Even the end of their day is fun
for the mountain climbing team]
[Caldron lid samgyeopsal party
is opening up at the tavern]
[Shining]
MINGYU! The meat is insane.
[Devouring]
It's seriously melting.
[The filling dinner that just melts]
After I wiped down completely,
I then realized I didn't bring clothes.
[Laughter still doesn't end]
He's a funny guy!
[The meaningful night together passes]
[We want to go, too!]
[JEONGHAN, HOSHI, and DK's mountain climbing]
[Passion] [We look pretty cool
mountain climbing while running]
It's pretty here.
[They capture the grand landscape
with their eyes]
[Peeks]
[Meditating while feeling
nature with their whole bodies]
[The final SEVENTEEN's "IN THE SOOP 2"]
[What will happen today?]
[The afternoon where the cafe team,
JOSHUA, SEUNGKWAN, and VERNON,
and the mountain climbing team,
JEONGHAN, HOSHI, and DK, went out]
[Loneliness fills the forest]
[Where are the remaining members?]
[S.COUPS, WOOZI, and MINGYU
are sleeping still as if it's the middle of the night]
[WONWOO is rolling around after going biking]
[As expected, the 1st floor of
the sleep zone is still in dreamland]
[But where's JUN,
whose spot this is? â¤¤]
[JUN came outside as soon as he woke up]
[Currently 3:30 p.m.]
[(JUN morning)]
[Immediately wears a helmet
and rides the ATV]
[JUN's ATV carefully departs]
[GO toward the observatory
to enjoy off road biking!]
[Once he goes up and up the mountain road]
[The unfamiliar and awkward is only brief]
[Whew]
It's the end.
[Totally adjusted to ATVs]
[JUN reached the peak]
[Enjoying the freedom of being alone]
Let's go!
[While JUN is enjoying the drive in the forest]
[Another member, DINO,
has also woken up late]
[The official routine after waking up
has become heading to the food zone]
[Warming up instant rice]
[+Pickled radish]
[What is he trying to make...?]
[Shall I begin]
[After roughly cutting
the pickled radish with scissors]
[and crushing seasoned seaweed]
[He also scrapes a can of tuna and puts it in]
[The final touches]
[After adding a drizzle of sesame oil]
[It's finished once it's mixed well!!!]
[DINO's brunch menu: rice balls]
[After drizzling oil on a pan]
[And cooking the round rice balls, one by one]
[DINO's rice balls are finished]
[Even preparing cup ramyeon to eat with it]
[That's when he gets a call]
- Where are you?
- At the food zone.
What are you eating?
Ramyeon and rice balls.
- I called you right now to see
if you wanted to eat together. / - Really?
- I put the ramyeon in the water just now.
Let's eat together. / - Okay, then I'll come!
But it's cup ramyeon.
It feels like my legs have gotten stronger.
[Meanwhile, the mountain climbing team,
JEONGHAN, HOSHI, and DK, has returned]
Your jump has improved.
[Meanwhile, the mountain climbing team,
JEONGHAN, HOSHI, and DK, has returned]
Where are you going, HOSHI?
- Over there...
- The food zone?
- The food zone? / - Let's go together.
[You're going to the food zone?
Then let's go together Keke]
- Okay. / - I'm slightly hungry.
[You're going to the food zone?
Then let's go together Keke]
If there's even 1 pork cutlet,
let's put it in the air fryer.
- Should we? Pork cutlet... / - I'm hungry, too.
[Hungry JEONGHAN, HOSHI, and DK
have entered the food zone]
- What is this? Whose is this?
I should eat it. / - DINO!
[The rice balls on the table
automatically draw their attention]
- No! That's mine!
- DINO. Can we eat that?
Should I try food made by DINO?
What did you do?
Let's play paintball.
[Since there are people gathered,
should we play a survival game?]
- Paintball? / - We have to play a survival
game, DINO. / - Let's play a survival
game after we eat.
[Since there are people gathered,
should we play a survival game?]
The game where somebody will be upset?
The game where somebody always gets upset.
[The game that ends only if
somebody (?) gets upset]
There's mozzarella and
whole tenderloins. It sounds good.
[Mountain climbing team is getting ready
to fry pork cutlet (ft. air fryer)]
[S.COUPS, who is craving ramyeon,
has also entered the food zone]
Hey! The members are all eating right now.
[S.COUPS, who is craving ramyeon,
has also entered the food zone]
I'm going to eat ramyeon.
[Best condition]
- I heard you're playing a survival game.
- We're going to play now.
[After sleeping in, MINGYU
has also entered the food zone]
Put it in here.
[Ramyeon mania] [S.COUPS and
MINGYU are eating ramyeon again]
Why didn't you put this in?
[Ramyeon mania] [S.COUPS and
MINGYU are eating ramyeon again]
[Hoo~]
[Can eat comfortably now...]
DINO! Is it good?
I haven't eaten yet...
I'm going to eat now.
It's perfect if we each eat one.
[DINO in the center]
[The hungry hyenas gather around]
I ruined my hands cutting the pickled radish...
[(?)]
It would be fun to have a snack party
for the first time in a while.
It would be fun.
We wouldn't eat it all,
but we can gather in the playroom and
[A party plan of those who are
27.25 years old on average]
- we can put out snacks. / - On the last day...
[A party plan of those who are
27.25 years old on average]
That sounds good!
The last day is today!!
[However]
- A snack party sounds good.
- It's already the last day. / - Right?
I did it a lot in academy long ago...
I went to academy to do that.
[Kekeke]
- To eat snacks?
- Yes.
- Is that hangover ramyeon?
The weather has gotten so cold.
[Here is the hangover ramyeon]
Bean sprouts.
The bean sprouts aren't blanched at all.
[Obviously raw bean sprouts]
- It looks good. / - What if it smells bad?
[EP1. Refer to DINO's bibimbap]
[Bean sprouts are best when eaten raw]
The bean sprouts smell so bad!
[EP1. Refer to DINO's bibimbap]
[Bean sprouts are best when eaten raw]
It's good.
[EP1. Refer to DINO's bibimbap]
[Bean sprouts are best when eaten raw]
Where did you go mountain climbing?
- The temple. / - It's where we went!
[Sharing how mountain climbing went today]
We drank a cup of tea
and ate rice cake waffles there.
[Sharing how mountain climbing went today]
- The tea shop was open?
- But they weren't open yesterday.
[(Totally) (Jealous)]
- It wasn't open yesterday. / - Really?
We came down after we ate that.
- I think you can take it out now.
- I'm turning it off!
[The pork cutlet they put into
the air fryer is done cooking now]
[Using a new appliance]
- How many did you heat up? / - 3
[Using a new appliance, everyone gathers]
[Even with a glimpse, the visuals pass]
- As long as it's not dirty, right?
- You're going to take one, right, HOSHI?
[Even with a glimpse, the visuals pass]
It looks good.
It's weird.
[HOSHI's idea]
[Wraps it in wax paper and eats it]
- I'm going to wrap it around and eat it, too.
- Do you want to?
[HOSHI's idea]
[Wraps it in wax paper and eats it]
Should I wrap it around and eat it?
That's true. Let's each wrap one and eat it.
[Wrapping the pork cutlet well
as if he''s eating hotteok]
You're eating it like that?
[Pork cutlet sauce â¤¥]
This is a pork cutlet waffle.
- Pork cutlet waffle.
- Is it good?
- Hey.
- Is it okay?
[HOSHI is busy eating
after saying "Hey!" Kekeke]
[Everyone is getting ready to try
the pork cutlet waffle (?)]
It's good!
[Everyone is getting ready to try
the pork cutlet waffle (?)]
CARAT can wrap it like this and eat it.
[Going to trend between CARATs in 2023]
Let me try a bite, too.
Just a bite.
[+ Just a bite]
But the air fryer is really good.
- JEONGHAN.
- Yes.
How many people are playing
the survival game?
- It's good.
- Whoever wants to play!
It has cheese in it, too!
- Should we head over to
the survival game? / - Let's go.
[Feeling full and ready for the survival game!!]
[Done getting into survival game attire]
- Nice. You remember catching the drone
yesterday, right, HOSHI? / - That's right.
That's how you play.
I'm finally playing this.
[â˜† "IN THE SOOP" survival field is open â˜†]
- Let's split into teams. Muk-jji...
- Muk-jji...
- Muk-jji.
- Jji.
[HOSHI (muk) THE 8 (jji)
DK (muk) JEONGHAN (jji)]
Okay.
[JEONGHAN and THE 8 VS HOSHI and DK]
- I'll go over there. / - Okay.
- Let's do a good job. / - Okay.
[Seok and Soon are a team since
Boo Seungkwan has gone to a cafe]
["IN THE SOOP" Survival Rules]
[1. Lives - endless]
[2. Game time - however long SEVENTEEN wants]
Can I act dead after getting hit?
[HOSHI and DK's team is very worried]
I'm good.
[On the other hand, JEONGHAN and
THE 8's team is confident]
Don't be arrogant!
That's how you die on the battlefield!!
Got it?
- I got it. / - Okay.
[The 2 teams approach the survival game
with a sense of urgency]
I'm really excited.
Who's going to start?!
Ready, start!
[HOSHI and DK VS JEONGHAN and THE 8]
[The 97s attack first right upon starting]
[HOSHI] [DK]
[JEONGHAN] [THE 8]
Where are they?
[Back and forth]
[(Shooting first even if he can't see)]
Okay!
Wow! What do I do?
[Kekeke]
Come here!
[Sniper JEONGHAN]
[HOSHI] [DK]
HOSHI! Cover me!
[Protect lifetime partner DK]
[HOSHI moves carefully]
[Now THE 8 has also joined
and applied pressure]
[The guy who doesn't know what to do]
[Beware that this may be chaotic]
[JEONGHAN] [THE 8]
[JEONGHANG is just enjoying this situation]
Where's Kwon Soonyoung?
Move forward!
[â–¼ DK] [â–¼ THE 8]
[â–¼ HOSHI] [â–¼ JEONGHAN]
[HOSHI] [DK]
[Bam] [97s each take a hit]
[JEONGHAN] [THE 8]
Minghao got hit in the face.
[Onlookers keep increasing]
[(Save HOSHI)]
[Attacks in that time]
[JEONGHAN charges at a terrifying speed]
[JEONGHAN] [THE 8]
[Very excited]
[In the attacks that aren't easy]
[JEONGHAN] [THE 8]
[(Very chaotic)]
[(HOSHI's revenge mode)]
[Target: JEONGHAN]
[JEONGHAN eventually retreats]
[HOSHI found an opportunity to counterattack]
[JEONGHAN] [THE 8]
[2nd target: THE 8]
Is Minghao okay?
[Watching is so fun]
Minghao got hit so many times.
[Kekeke]
[Flails~]
DK!
[HOSHI] [DK]
[As expected, DK has no shoes on]
[Runs again]
[And quickly saves his shoes]
[No time for his feet to touch the ground]
[Running this and that way]
[(The enemy's pain is my joy)]
Are you okay, DK?
[The genre is suddenly a spectacle horror piece]
[HOSHI] [DK]
Should we keep the teams or switch them?
[2nd round]
What should we do?
- Let's switch them. / - Okay! Mix them.
[Switching teams]
Muk-jji!
- Okay! Let's go, HOSHI. / - Okay.
[JEONGHAN and HOSHI (jji)]
[THE 8 and DK (muk)]
Go!
[JEONGHAN and HOSHI (jji)]
[THE 8 and DK (muk)]
JEONGHAN is such a good shooter!
HOSHI is dead!
[...??]
[HOSHI] [DK]
[(He's alive)]
- Minghao. Let's strategize and
go on both sides. / - How?
[THE 8 and DK's team's strategy time]
- We'll narrow in from both sides.
- Okay...
Minghao! You know the strategy, right?
[Fighting!!]
We will move according to our strategy!
Please do it for real now!
[â¤¤ He even wore outerwear and came]
Kill them!
What are you going to hide behind?
[Can't lose] [It's also strategy time
for JEONGHAN and HOSHI's team]
- I'll go that way. / - That way? Then...
[Can't lose] [It's also strategy time
for JEONGHAN and HOSHI's team]
Hide in that large square. Okay?
[They pick the spot per what Coach JEONGHAN,
the survival game expert, says]
Okay.
It's starting.
Ready!
Start!
[This is the strategy from both sides...?]
[DK] [THE 8]
[It's been long since they forgot the strategy]
[HOSHI] [JEONGHAN]
[THE 8 and DK's strategy
from both sides is a huge failure]
[Back from the cafe, JOSHUA,
SEUNGKWAN, and VERNON are watching]
There are also grenades?
[Back from the cafe, JOSHUA,
SEUNGKWAN, and VERNON are watching]
I guess so.
There are grenades...?
[The identity of the grenade is...]
[DK abandoned his gun
and is throwing bullets]
[Finds a gap! HOSHI charges forward]
[DK's "How to Avoid the Bullets"]
[Attacking in various positions Kekeke]
HOSHI! Run more! Forward!
[Scolding]
HOSHI really seems like a soldier.
MINGYU!
DINO! Come in!
[(Yeah...)]
- Should I go in? / - Yes.
[Responds as if he's been waiting to hear that]
Come in!
I'll be back.
[While they switch players]
[JEONGHAN vs THE 8 and DK]
[OUT HOSHI] [IN MINGYU]
[HOSHI LOADING]
[JEONGHAN]
[2:1 is overdoing it even for sniper JEONGHAN]
[THE 8 doesn't even need bunkers]
[DK charges forward to "Just do it"]
[â–¼ DK] [â–¼ JEONGHAN]
[â–¼ THE 8]
[JEONGHAN is forced into a corner in an instant]
[But he quickly counterattacks!!]
[DK] [THE 8]
[As JEONGHAN's lonely fight continues]
JEONGHAN!
[â¤£ MINGYU is changing]
- I'll go! / - I'm so tired. Hurry up and come.
[Hey...]
[(Please do a good job)]
Ready, start!
[JEONGHAN and MINGYU VS THE 8 and DK]
[MINGYU] [JEONGHAN]
[JEONGHAN's charge is encouraged
by MINGYU's appearance]
[DK] [THE 8]
[Agile DK opposes that]
[â–¼ MINGYU] [â–¼ JEONGHAN]
[â–¼ DK] [â–¼ THE 8]
[MINGYU goes forward little by little]
[DK] [THE 8]
[He discovers MINGYU moving forward]
[(DK's shoe)]
[(Just looking for an opportunity)]
JEONGHAN!
[MINGYU] [JEONGHAN]
[ID: 26 year-old Kim Mingyu
only looking for JEONGHAN~!]
JEONGHAN! My head!
[Screaming out JEONGHAN's name
1004 times Kekeke]
JEONGHAN!
[Screaming out JEONGHAN's name
1004 times Kekeke]
This can't happen right now.
We're being attacked.
[Right then, DK slowly presses in and comes]
[MINGYU] [JEONGHAN]
[Immediately aiming towards MINGYU]
[A mess within 5 minutes of joining]
It hurts a lot!
[JEONGHAN moves forward
towards DK to get revenge]
[MINGYU] [JEONGHAN]
[(+MINGYU has attached onto him)]
- Why are you here? Go over there!
- Where?
There!
Why are you here and getting hit by everything...
- Why... / - Hurry up and go!
[MINGYU, who gets hit the most (?) out of
the ones who gets hit the least and JjongJjong]
I wanted to do it with you.
[MINGYU, who gets hit the most (?) out of
the ones who gets hit the least and JjongJjong]
[DK] [THE 8]
[THE 8 and DK's attacking skills
improved after MINGYU joined]
[MINGYU] [JEONGHAN]
[After hiding behind him]
Minghao! Move forward!
[Eventually, he gets hit and flees]
JEONGHAN!
Ack!
[Simultaneously with the wails...]
I'm tired!
The end.
[Simultaneously with the wails... The end]
I got hit in the head too much.
I was doing it and I got hit.
The moment I got up... Bam bam bam!
[Sharing what happened as soon as it's over]
I looked at you while shooting
and I saw the paint land
and explode right on your head.
[The competitive "IN THE SOOP"
survival game is over]
- I got hit and... / - I feel so good.
[The competitive "IN THE SOOP"
survival game is over]
- It was fun.
- But I felt it, too.
Did we do it for longer than we thought
or did it just get dark fast?
[EP6. Always remember that we're together]
It got dark fast.
The paint flew all the way over here.
[The lingering feelings from
the survival game aren't leaving]
Rather than going there to do it,
[(A survival game arena)]
as expected,
playing on our own is more fun.
- When you go and get hit once,
they say, "You're dead" and it ends. / - Yeah.
The last day!
Shall we make it?
[It's the last dinner of "IN THE SOOP 2"]
Okay!
What kind of pasta is it?
Make me something good!
[JOSHUA and SEUNGKWAN came
to the food zone first]
Can you make me pasta
that has sirloin in it?
- Okay.
- Pasta with beef in it.
What are you doing?
He said he would make
a spicy tomato based pasta.
[(Tapping) (the butt)]
Really?
I have marinated galbi
(short ribs) and pork cutlets.
[I'm going to grill marinated galbi]
[SEVENTEEN comes together one by one]
[Boom]
[Clap]
What are you doing?
[Right now]
Shua. Pasta.
[(He's making it)]
Shua is busy again.
[JOSHUA is getting ready
to make pasta sauce]
Why?
[JOSHUA is getting ready
to make pasta sauce]
- Thyme! It's what I like. / - You like it?
[Feels happy from discovering
ingredients that he likes]
[Even today, he makes a sauce without a recipe]
- Sugar... / - Sugar...
If I mix in water...
[Ingredients that go in]
[Tomato paste] [Minced garlic]
[Sugar] [Thyme] [Water]
SEUNGKWAN!
[Ingredients that go in]
[Tomato paste] [Minced garlic]
[Sugar] [Thyme] [Water]
Does it look like tomato sauce or not?
[JOSHUA's tomato sauce came to be!]
- Nice! / - Right?
It can come apart.
Because I'll leave it be so that oil comes out.
[Now if he stir fries the meat and sauce
together on a pan]
I just need to reduce this.
It smells like pasta.
[The sauce is getting better
and better as it reduced]
It's getting pretty good.
[The sauce is getting better
and better as it reduced]
I think I need to reduce it slightly.
[How will it taste to SEUNGKWAN....?]
It's good!
[As expected, thumbs up!]
I ate a pepper!
- It's good! / - It's good.
[A taste that even JUN acknowledges]
Is it good?
- I think it'll be really good. / - Right?
[A ton of noodles in the tasty sauce!]
It's so my style.
I think it'll be better if I take this frying pan
and we scoop it up and eat it together.
[As JOSHUA's pasta is being finished]
That's right! We can use tongs with this.
[WOOZI is preparing
another beef party today]
[Flipping it over at the right time]
This is it!
[(Even sprinkling) (salt)]
[Cutting it right away with no plates needed]
[Straight into his mouth]
[Satisfied]
[Devouring the meat as if he's breathing it in]
It's like you're eating at an omakase alone.
Beef omakase.
For several days now,
I've been eating the same way like this.
Because I'm too lazy to cook.
But...
It's delicious all the same?
I could get sick of it, but...
The meat is so good because it's AA.
[â¤]
It's hot.
[JOSHUA experiences WOOmakase]
Because I don't get sick of it...
The fact that it tastes like this
with only salt is so...
[(Satisfaction â˜…â˜…â˜…â˜…â˜…)]
The meat is really good.
- Right?
- And you grill it well.
- It's really good.
- It's so good.
[(This is it~)]
[Meanwhile, the additional dishes
are being finished inside]
The bibimmyeon (spicy mixed noodles)
is finished! [â¤]
The pork galbi smells so good!
Galbi is always the best choice.
[Browning]
- It can't be hated. / - Yeah.
[The last dinner in the forest is
busily becoming finished]
Okay! Let's eat this!
[The finished dishes come out one by one]
It looks good!
Is it WONWOO's bibimmyeon?
I need to eat a bite!
Come to eat it.
It's not easy eating
bibimmyeon made my WONWOO.
[WONWOO's bibimmyeon
can only be tasted in the forest]
That's right.
[WONWOO's bibimmyeon
can only be tasted in the forest]
Alright! Let's go!
[As well as JOSHUA's tomato pasta
& SEUNGKWAN's galbi!]
- Pa*do, marinated galbi, and pasta. / - Pasta.
[As well as JOSHUA's tomato pasta
& SEUNGKWAN's galbi!]
The menu choice is amazing!
[A full table of food is finished!]
Shall we try it?
Try it!
[JOSHUA's first bite is of
SEUNGKWAN's grilled galbi]
Is it good?
It's good!
[Also slurping the bibimmyeon that
WONWOO made himself for the first time]
It looks good!
- WONWOO's first time ever making this.
- Yeah.
[(SEUNGKWAN's chin is lowered
the more delicious it is)]
I usually cook
soupy ones very well.
[A taste that makes him fix his chair â¤]
It's good.
SEUNGKWAN, you have a connection
to pork galbi! Is it good?
- Try it.
- It's good. The pork is decent.
[Try it first]
- Hmm!
- There's no way it could taste bad.
[Eating the bibimmyeon along with
SEUNGKWAN's galbi that he loved]
[Can't miss out on JOSHUA's pasta]
[Can't miss out on JOSHUA's pasta as well]
Wow! This seems like
school cafeteria spaghetti.
- It's because it has cheese in it.
- The mood is nice.
[The secret behind the school cafeteria
style spaghetti is "cheese"]
I like things like that way more.
- We used to fill the whole tray with just
rice and things like this. / - Yeah.
[When it came out in the cafeteria] [Hahaha]
That's the mood.
[From long ago]
It's good.
[It has mood from long ago, but it's better â¤]
- JOSHUA cooks well! / - Is it good?
If you brag to the members,
it'll get tough for you, JOSHUA.
[Kekeke]
- No!
- Don't say anything today.
[Someone smells
the yummy smell of food and runs over]
I came to eat a bite!
What are you coming from?
I came from sleeping,
but I'm OFF today.
- There needs to be days like those.
- I'm not doing anything.
[Actually today, S.COUPS...]
[He lied down in the sleep zone right after
eating hangover ramyeon with MINGYU]
[How S.COUPS rests]
[Everything is OFF on days off]
[Since he's hungry even he's OFF!]
[So delicious!]
- It's cold! What are they eating?
- Eat!
- Is it spaghetti?
- There's spaghetti and...
- Is that the spaghetti that Shua made?
- There's also bibimmyeon.
How is the spaghetti?
Is it good?
- It's good.
Shua cooks well.
Did you sleep again, HOSHI?
I slept again.
[(Yes, he slept again)]
Is the bibimmyeon good?
[Even HOSHI, who came after sleeping well]
[He wraps the bibimmyeon around]
[And takes a huge bite!]
[The type to put food in his mouth
first without sitting down]
[(He's eating well Haha)]
I decided to take around HOSHI today.
He fell asleep because he was tired.
[Kekekeke]
- I woke him up and dragged him here right now.
- That's amazing.
[Why HOSHI slept so well...]
HOSHI! Look at nature!
[He was dragged around by him since morning]
Let's go!
[Runs and goes up the mountain]
Run more, HOSHI!
Come out to the front.
[Became his NPC and
also played the survival game]
[(I want to be alone...)]
HOSHI!
[(Yes, that's not okay)]
Eat dinner, HOSHI!
[Clingy mode all day long]
- Did you sleep well? Were you tired? / - Yes.
If JEONGHAN has a son or daughter,
- they don't need to lose weight.
- The kids will cut ties with him.
"I'm not going to hang out with dad."
They'll say this.
[(Not knowing how dad feels...)]
[Around the time HOSHI
recharges (?) with bibimmyeon]
Where are we doing the lamb skewers?
[The main chef of dinner part 2 enters]
The lamb skewers are at the fire in front, no?
We can do that, but won't it be cold outside?
[JEONGHAN is already done
preparing the ingredients]
It's cold.
[JEONGHAN is already done
preparing the ingredients]
Let's just eat here.
[Grilling and eating at the fire in the cold VS
on induction heat warm]
- Okay! / - Here.
[Grilling and eating at the fire in the cold VS
on induction heat in the warmth]
[Removes the lamb meat from the skewers]
Can you remove them one by one?
[As the lamb meat is being grilled
with an appetizing sound]
I'll bring it for you!
[As the lamb meat is being grilled
with an appetizing sound]
[THE 8 starts cooking mala longxia,
which is JEONGHAN's favorite]
[The combination of spicy pepper oil
& crayfish is... â¤]
It's really good!
[(The sight of it alone makes them salivate)]
[The quiet kitchen is now rustling]
It's Konkuk University!
It feels like the holidays!
[The food zone feels like the holidays]
- Everyone! Please show your faces!
- Show our faces?
[(Can't miss a moment like this)]
1, 2, 3!
[Nothing_less_or_more_
just_be_like_IN_THE_SOOPâ¤.jpg]
[(Hop)]
Oh, Minghao!
[Kekekeke]
Minghao is excited!
He's a chef!
[Energy.at.a.peak]
[Kekekekeke]
[The cooking by THE 8, who is energized]
[It's shining before it's even finished-]
[Excited Chef THE 8's
mala longxia is coming out~!]
Add a bit of oil.
What is this?
It's crayfish.
- This is crayfish?
- Yes.
Right now,
this place is totally Konkuk University.
[Mala longxia, lamb skewers]
[Dinner tonight is totally a feast of Chinese food]
There's even dried tofu!
[Mala longxia, lamb skewers]
[Dinner tonight is totally a feast of Chinese food]
There's dried tofu?
[Mala longxia, lamb skewers]
[Dinner tonight is totally a feast of Chinese food]
How are you supposed to eat this?
Minghao is going to teach you.
[Straighten the back of the crayfish
as much as possible and push up the meat]
[Eat the meat that's sticking out~]
It's coming out well.
[Amazed]
It's really good.
Eat!
[Hurry]
This is better!
The one that Minghao made is better!
[You and I are both crayfish-holic]
[Entranced]
JEONGHAN really seems like Jang Chen!
This is the mood.
[(Bare hands)]
You're not using utensils?
[When eating crayfish...
utensils are unnecessary]
[Happiness is at a MAX with crayfish]
There are probably no teams
that love Chinese food this diversely as ours.
That's also difficult.
- You went to a cafe! / - Yes, we went to a cafe.
[Now that they mention it, JOSHUA,
SEUNGKWAN, and VERNON went to a cafe]
I heard you broke a cup.
[Now that they mention it, JOSHUA,
SEUNGKWAN, and VERNON went to a cafe]
[They broke a cup...?!]
- You're very up to date. / - That's right.
Shua told me everything.
[They broke a cup...?!]
- Hello? / - If I drink too much...
[At the cafe a few hours ago]
[(※ Refer to the end of episode 5)
VERNON tried to eat the pancake,
but slipped and broke a cup]
- Hold on. / - What do I do!
[(※ Refer to the end of episode 5)
VERNON tried to eat the pancake,
but slipped and broke a cup]
I'm sorry.
What do I do about this?
♪ I'm sorry
Give me one of those, VERNON.
It also got on the chair.
What are you doing?
Are you all watching?
[(There's also DINO)]
[~There are more onlookers than eaters~]
I've been sleeping so well here.
I think I sleep around 9 hours.
- You even took a nap!
- Yes!
I sleep 12 hours, too.
[Suddenly, a battle of good sleep begins]
Whenever I wake up, it's night.
[He slept at night though]
Your pattern is completely different than ours.
I sleep at night!
But when I wake up, it's night.
Do you want to go around with me
tomorrow like HOSHI did?
[WOOZI as well]
No, no way. I'll decline.
[(Turning down completely)]
Do you think you'll go work out, HOSHI?
Or today...
Should we go to the next course?
There's another course?
[(...?)]
The next course is
- zoning out into the fire and drinking a cup of
whisky. / - I think I'll go work out around 11.
[The next course just for HOSHI]
[ðŸ‘‰ The next course of JEONGHAN's tour]
Should I do it then?
[Together until the end of the day]
Then be with me until the next and final course.
I'll let you skip the sauna!
[(TY)]
Or you can eat this, go to the fire pit,
and have a cup of whisky.
[(Recruiting people to go to the fire pit
and drink a cup of whisky)]
It's seriously so cold there!
You're cold because you're dressed like that!
Come out with long pants and socks!
[(M... mom...?)]
Why are you getting angry?
Because I want to be with you.
Stay with me?
[(... â¤)]
Living like this brings me so much joy!
- Right?
- Yes!
I'm so upset that this is the last night!
Why does time fly by so quickly
at "IN THE SOOP"?
Is it because it's the forest?
[DK's monodrama along with washing dishes]
Because we're in nature?
The forest told me this...!
How to just feel as time passes.
The forest told me this!
- That doing dishes is very tiring...
- That's right.
But it's nice!
[~Dishes monodrama is over~]
I should go to the sauna.
I can't handle this.
Sauna!
[â¤]
Sikhye (rice punch)!
[WONWOO is the very 1st one
to arrive at the sauna]
[Enters with sikhye in hand]
[Let's lie down first]
[Soon after, DK arrives at the sauna]
Huh? Jeon Wonwoo?
You're a regular!
Sir!
You're always here!
[The regular customer that comes
to the sauna everyday]
What?
[The regular customer that comes
to the sauna everyday]
It's warm!
[(DK also lies down next to WONWOO)]
I have to go after we count to a hundred.
No! Let's be together.
I've been in here for too long.
[WONWOO trying to leave VS
DK trying to stop him]
It's cold! It's so cold!
[Another regular customer, MINGYU, enters]
Since MINGYU is here now,
I can go, right?
- You can't.
- I can't?
I think I've been here for over 20 minutes.
[T T]
What would you do if you went outside?
Hurry up and wash up and sleep.
You're going to sleep?
It's not bedtime!
- I'll go! / - Bye!
[(I'm going to go)]
[Hops]
[If someone leaves...]
[If someone leaves...
someone else also comes!]
[~ 97s sauna gather ~]
When I was young,
my dad told me to go in the sauna
for 10 minutes before getting dead skin
scrubbed off, so I really hated it.
- We never knew we'd like it this much, right?
- I like it now.
Come in!
[New customers HOSHI and JUN
also enter the sauna]
It's so cold!
[New customers HOSHI and JUN
also enter the sauna]
It's so hot here.
[New customers HOSHI and JUN
also enter the sauna]
- It's nice! / - Come here!
[New customers HOSHI and JUN
also enter the sauna]
The towels are refreshing.
Were you here for a long time?
20 minutes?
[â¤¾Masked sauna visitors who entered the saunaâ†·]
[The training (?) suddenly
begins in the sauna]
[(Strange acts suddenly begin)]
3... 2... 1...
- Bye, everyone. / - Bye!
[(Can't stay any longer)]
Bye!
[(Steaming heavily)]
[A ton of steaming]
[Steaming from all over the body]
[They don't miss this refreshing moment
and take a photo]
[~ This is the taste of saunas ~]
[The customers come one after another
after finishing the sauna session]
[And the members ring in
the last night in the forest]
[Each person tries to go to sleep]
[Slam-]
Coups...?
He's sleeping.
I'm going to sleep.
Yes, sleep early!
Okay. I'm so sleepy.
[Leaving the voices out the window
that are still loud behind him]
[(Also a good night for JOSHUA_)]
[Right then]
[VERNON excitedly runs somewhere]
[The place that VERNON joins is]
If VERNON also sits down...
[Restless SEVENTEEN's
hangout spot is the fire pit]
Night has come.
You kept saying that you want to play mafia here.
[(DINO)]
No! But we don't have to play.
- Let's play! / - Then do you want to play now?
[(Mafia game)] [Let's go!)]
Okay.
Okay! Then briefly...
[They'll play just one brief game then!]
Thank you!
- I'll be the narrator. / - Okay.
["Mafia" 1R] [- Narrator: DK -]
Okay.
Night has come.
I'll pick the mafia.
I'll pick the doctor and police.
[Quickly also pick
the "doctor" and "police" as well]
Morning has come.
It's JEONGHAN!
[Unprecedented developments Kekekekeke]
What I think is...
When I said this, DK's eyes...
- Well, I...
- Why are you looking at the narrator's eyes?
- Why are you looking at me?
- What about the narrator's eyes?
- Don't look at me! / - The narrator's eyes...
[(Shuts down guesses made from gazes)]
The narrator's eyes went straight to DINO.
[HOSHI's guess]
[The narrator's eyes went straight to DINO!]
When I said it was DINO, the one who felt safe...
The one who felt safe!
It's MINGYU!
[The mafia is MINGYU!]
"I saw your face when I spoke."
Will you choose MINGYU?
[(As the mafia)]
It's really not me...
[Sad MINGYU]
What about you, DINO?
You're going to stay still?
But I said it was JEONGHAN first.
[(Says something else)]
- What are you? / - What am I?
[^^ (with. a subtle smile)]
- Think about it on your own.
- There's something to it!
[(?)]
- Think about it on your own.
[Kekekekeke]
- There would be something.
- My job is...
Campfire caretaker.
Yoon Jeonghan's tick came out.
[(?)]
Take care of it well! All of it's dying!
[(The fire is)]
- I'm the tongs manager. / - Tongs manager.
[Then I'm] [DINO (Born in 1999, tongs manager)]
I like money!
I'm a barista!
[WOOZI (born in 1996, forest barista)]
I think it's MINGYU.
[Attack with backbone] [(Mafia)]
- Let's go with MINGYU!
- We need to go with MINGYU once.
[Then let's put MINGYU on the stand]
- Okay. / - Then MINGYU... / - This is so unfair.
[Then let's MINGYU on the stand]
- 1, 2, 3. / - No, but...
[Quickly putting MINGYU on the stand]
It's really not me...
[T T]
Can you think about it one more time?
An innocent...
- ...mafia has died. / - Hold on.
[MINGYU was really the mafia]
- He's the mafia? / - He's the mafia.
That's why I wasn't motivated.
- I'm going crazy... / - Did I point him out less?
[A guy like me... I have crazy gut feelings...!]
[(Ke)] [(Outraged)]
- DINO should be the narrator! / - Yes, I'll...
["Mafia" 2R] [- Narrator: DINO -]
Hey! Boo Seungkwan!
- Come here! / - Come here! Let's play mafia.
[How SEVENTEEN plays mafia]
[A system where they join if they stand out]
Night has come.
[Impatient narrator]
Please include me as well!
Me too!
- First, I'll pick
- Okay.
- the doctor. / - Come in, SEUNGKWAN.
- SEUNGKWAN is coming. SEUNGKWAN, too.
[(Dashing Bboo)]
- Including SEUNGKWAN, I'll pick quickly.
- Okay.
Yes, the doctor and police.
[Mafia starts right when he sits down]
And...
Mafia.
[Who will be this round's mafia...?]
I'm done!
Morning has come.
Since SEUNGKWAN just joined,
[Suspicious of the new face first]
shouldn't he have something? SEUNGKWAN?
- But DINO might not have given SEUNGKWAN
anything. / - I don't think he gave him anything.
[(Knows DINO well)]
- You don't think he did? / - For no reason?
We have no idea.
[(Hm...)]
DINO and SEUNGKWAN's relationship.
[Only they know their love hate relationship]
[(Discovers HOSHI)]
- HOSHI has something. / - HOSHI has something.
From what I can see...
[Discovers a wild beast's eyes
seeking dried persimmons]
His eyes... His eyes aren't of a mafia.
[Discovers a wild beast's eyes
seeking dried persimmons]
There's something right now.
[(HOSHI looking for an opportunity)]
He's either the police or something right now.
- I think he's the police. / - He's the police.
[(HOSHI is)]
A job where he can look cool!
- I think he's the police. / - He's the police!
- He's the police.
- A job where he can look cool. / - I think...
[HOSHI = a job that can look cool = the police?!]
Mafia is...
[(Guessing mode ON)]
It's MINGYU.
[Focused only on MINGYU]
I knew you'd say that.
Even when I keep looking at you now...
[Focused only on MINGYU]
This awkward smile.
[Suddenly changes]
[Focused only on DK, who's next to MINGYU]
This awkward smile!
[Suddenly changes]
[Focused only on DK, who's next to MINGYU]
- I kept looking at DK, too. / - Me?
[(+Suspicious of DK)]
Me?
I was awkward?
It's so different from the 1st round!
He's good!
- Let's go with DK. / - Okay.
[The opinions narrow in on DK]
- I think DK was slightly awkward.
- I also think it's DK...
[The opinions narrow in on DK]
Even this smile is awkward.
[(Tiger has met his prey)]
Please extend your arm forward, everyone.
Your thumbs... SEUNGKWAN?
[When you can't say you're frustrated
when you're frustrated.mov]
- I'm really not mafia. / - 1, 2...
[DK's final defense]
- Hold on. Give me a chance
to make my defense. / - Your defense.
[DK's final defense]
Was I...
Was I awkward?
[(Unfair)]
- It's so awkward. / - Was I like I was
when we were on "MMTG" right now?
[(Unfair)]
The defense when you're a civilian is really fun.
[HOSHI's gut feeling is very different (?)]
No, I have nothing to say when
I defend myself as a civilian. I'm a civilian, so...
[(Time for his defense)]
- Really? / - How irritating.
[Annoying]
- Here we go now! We even heard his defense.
- I'm really not mafia!
[What will happen to DK,
who is on the stand?]
1, 2, 3!
3!
[Unanimously DK]
- 1, 2, 3! / - They all say they're not mafia.
- An innocent civilian has died.
- He was a civilian.
[Innocent civilian DK is OUT]
- That's seriously so messed up.
- Mafia doesn't die in the 1st round.
[Innocent civilian DK is OUT]
Night has come.
Please pick who to kill, mafia.
[Time for mafia to choose]
Morning has come.
[Morning has come again]
Campfire caretaker, JEONGHAN, has died.
[Campfire caretaker (?) and
civilian JEONGHAN is OUT]
Campfire caretaker.
- I know who it is! / - It's HOSHI!
[SEUNGKWAN suddenly has a gut feeling?]
Do you trust me or not?
- Hurry up and do it.
- Let's hear him out.
- I wish there was purpose to your defense.
- Yeah.
[(Boldly rolls his eyes)]
[â¤£ Fed up...]
[Dibs on WOOZI â¤]
The flow is good right now!
[- Flow with no context -]
- Since SEUNGKWAN doesn't
know what happened before! / - He doesn't
know what happened. / - He has no idea!
If you're going to be like this,
exclude me when you're mafia.
[With this flow, WOOZI is mafia?]
Morning has come.
[â—€â—€â—€ 15 minutes ago, practice game]
- WOOZI is mafia. / - WOOZI.
[They unanimously voted him as mafia
within the first 10 seconds of the game]
- It's obviously WOOZI. / - It's not.
[They unanimously voted him as mafia
within the first10 seconds of the game]
Hey! Quickly kill me and start.
- Yes! Then kill him quickly.
- Just kill me.
- 1, 2, 3! / - 2, 3!
[Voting with no time for a defense]
Okay.
An innocent civilian has died.
[WOOZI got OUT within 30 seconds...]
WOOZI! Why didn't you act like a civilian?
- No! / - Just exclude me.
[But he doesn't want to retract his gut feeling]
First off, civilians have 1 more chance after.
[Current situation] [Mafia 1] [Police 1]
[Doctor 1] [Civilian 2]
I don't think voting for WOOZI
is a bad idea. What do you think?
[Following the friend and votes for WOOZI]
Seriously...
- No! But still...
- I don't think voting for WOOZI is a bad idea.
Such idiots...
[VERNON... You punk...]
If you're really a civilian, please defend yourself.
[(Wanting sincerity)]
Be sincere. A sincere defense.
- I'm not! / - But earlier... Earlier, I was...
[Mafia]
- I was mafia the previous round.
- Did he play like this?
[(Mafia before, currently???)]
I'm not saying he's mafia, but mafia's defense is...
[Logical (?) testimony of previous mafia]
- You sort of lose motivation.
- You don't have anything to say in particular.
[Logical (?) testimony of previous mafia]
Then should we go for it? WOOZI?
[(Driving momentum)]
It's VERNON.
[(Changes routes)]
- It's me? / - Because...
[Suddenly]
Because he called him mafia,
he's relieved since he's mafia.
[VERNON got caught by HOSHI's radar]
He wants to hurry up and kill him.
Let's go with VERNON.
- Okay! Then let's go!
- Suddenly.
- Mafia is driving me crazy.
Then go for it!
Should we go with VERNON or WOOZI?
[Is WOOZI or VERNON on the stand?]
Or we can go around and say a word.
You picked WOOZI.
[(Dibs on WOOZI)]
I'll think about it a bit more then.
[(Oh hold?)] [(Dibs on WOOZI)]
What about you?
- I'll also think about it. / - Then...
[(MINGYU is also on hold?)]
- Then who is it this time?
- WOOZI! Who do you think it is?
[Hmm]
- This is mafia!!!
- It's WOOZI!
- It's WOOZI! / - This face...
[98s are certain + enraged]
- These eyes! / - This is...
- It's not.
- This is...
- Go straight! We need to go straight! / - Straight?
- I also became certain with this.
[Go straight (?) with WOOZI as mafia]
You know!
This isn't forced right now.
I think it's WOOZI.
[Hyenas have bitten the prey]
- I've also become certain. / - Idiots.
[HOSHI also picks WOOZI]
- WOOZI!
- These idiots.
- Hurry up and run the game.
- Please raise your hands, everyone.
- Do I give my defense?
- DK is dead, right?
- I'm dead! / - Then since everyone is
coming towards me, I'll speak.
[- WOOZI's final defense -]
I wasn't saying anything because
I wanted to make the game very fun.
I actually know everything.
Okay?
Police. Please wake up and tell me.
[â—€â—€â—€ 5 minutes ago]
[WOOZI is the police]
[And on the first night,
he found out who mafia was...]
I'll just say this much. Kill me if you want to.
[~ It's up to you to decide ~]
But because he's talking like this...
[What's with his persuasion skills]
You idiot!
I don't think it's WOOZI...
If it's not WOOZI,
- I think it's VERNON.
- Really?
Or unexpectedly,
he couldn't made him do it again.
[It could be MINGYU one more time]
- That's possible.
- I also thought of that though.
But I'm definitely that now.
I definitely become comfortable.
You got comfortable because
you're doing it once more.
[Being mafia]
... Oh.
He got it now that he's done it.
Since it's been a while.
[Can't stop being suspicious of one another]
Wow, I'm becoming certain.
- Is it me?
- VERNON.
Is it me? Okay.
It's VERNON or WOOZI.
[Is the mafia WOOZI or VERNON?]
But it's really not me!
Then VERNON!
- It's really not me!
- We also heard his defense. Let's go.
[(Yelling)]
- "It's really not me." / - It's really not me.
- Please put up your thumbs, everyone.
- Save me just once.
1...
- 2, 3! / - It's really not me.
It's really not me though!
[VERNON ends up being on the stand]
VERNON
was a civilian.
[Innocent civilian VERNON is OUT]
- Night has come. / - Then...
[Night has come again...]
Guys! Then even if I die,
please kill that person.
Why did the police do nothing?
Night has come.
Mafia. Please wake up and pick.
[Current situation] [Mafia 1] [Police 1]
[Doctor 1] [Civilian 1]
And...
[! Checks the identity of mafia !]
- Seriously... I...
- Police. Please wake up and speak up.
[Skipping police WOOZI,
who caught mafia in the beginning]
Doctor. Please wait up and save.
[Time for the doctor to pick]
Please save me.
[(Doctor)]
[Self healing]
Morning has come.
Innocent WOOZI...
[Innocent civilian (=police) WOOZI is OUT]
- The doctor is so selfish. / - He's dead.
[Oh...]
[Got it]
- It's him!
Hey!
- 1, 2, 3! / - Hold on. Let me defend myself!
[The mafia is MINGYU?!]
- Okay. Defend yourself.
- Let's listen to his defense.
Why is it me?
[(Mafia)]
It's you!
[Just because]
- Yeah, but there should be a reason.
- He's the doctor.
- Okay. Let's go. It's you. / - It's not me.
[Ganging up on mafia = no particular reason]
- Why is it me? The doctor should've
saved WOOZI! / - Please raise your thumb.
[Unfair for MINGYU]
- Why? / - He made it obvious
that he's the police earlier.
[Unfair for MINGYU]
He spoke as if he knew everything!
What happens if I die?
I was certain that it was WOOZI.
[- HOSHI's stance: Why MINGYU is mafia -]
But WOOZI died.
But I don't think it's you.
[- HOSHI's stance: Why MINGYU is mafia -]
It's not me.
- Then it's you. / - That reason that it's not you...
[Magical logic] [It's just you, MINGYU]
It's not me either.
But either way, the majority says this,
so you have to die.
[HOSHI and SEUNGKWAN unite
and put MINGYU on the stand]
- 1, 2, 3. / - But you did a really good job.
[HOSHI and SEUNGKWAN unite
and put MINGYU on the stand]
- You're mafia.
- Good job.
That's right. I'm mafia.
[MINGYU = mafia]
Because you were mafia once...
[Always fun to catch the culprit]
- You were mafia again this time!
- What was really funny earlier was...
[Always fun to catch the culprit]
I felt so guilty when you said that.
You got comfortable because you were mafia
once before, right?
[Scared when VERNON's made that sharp remark]
- You said "Oh!" / - He did sort of hesitate.
- What was really funny earlier was that
WOOZI was the police.
[(((Narrator's stance:
Police WOOZI's performance)))]
- But from the beginning, WOOZI told me mafia.
- In the 1st round. / - He picked in the 1st round.
[(((Narrator's stance:
Police WOOZI's performance)))]
So I
said he was mafia.
[1. Caught mafia from the start]
But as soon as he woke up,
everyone picked WOOZI as mafia.
[2. But soon after, they gained up on WOOZI]
- As I watched...
- It was so ridiculous that I said, "These idiots."
- These idiots.
[(Seriously hit with reality)]
- You figured out who mafia was?
- He found out right away.
- He found out with 1 try.
- He knew it since the 1st round.
- So it was sort of... I guess
I took WOOZI's strange energy that
comes out when he's given a role
[The reason he picked WOOZI as mafia]
[Why he picked WOOZI as mafia]
and isn't even funny as laughter.
That's ridiculous!
You can't package that either.
[(Embarrassed)]
You're just going to look like
you have terrible gut feelings.
[(Embarrassed)]
Terrible gut feelings?
- Let's play one last round.
- Are you going to play JEONGHAN?
[Last round of mafia?]
- JEONGHAN...
- Okay, I'll leave after one last round.
- Do you want to play a round of the liar game?
- Who's going to be the narrator?
- I'll be the narrator.
- Okay.
- Here we go. Mafia! / - I don't want to be mafia.
[Narrator of the last round is JEONGHAN]
I'll pick mafia first.
- MINGYU...
- Mafia!
I'll pick mafia.
[The grand finale of SEVENTEEN'S
"IN THE SOOP 2" ver. mafia]
I'll pick the police!
[The grand finale of SEVENTEEN'S
"IN THE SOOP 2" ver. mafia]
The police! I'll pick the doctor.
[Who will be the ending fairy mafia?!]
- Wake up. / - Okay!
[The last mafia game finally begins]
Day has come.
It's so cold.
[The last mafia game finally begins]
I think JEONGHAN would've picked well.
[(Belatedly waking up)]
What's up with Boo Seungkwan?
Let's kill him.
Why didn't you wake up?
Hello! I'm Reporter Ju.
[Look at that rhyme]
- I'm being cornered.
- He's so good!
- It's so unfair. I don't think I can do it.
- "Let's kill him." "Hello, I'm Reporter Ju."
Reporter Ju is seriously...
[Number 1 at escaping danger with his wits]
The reason I woke up late is...
- Look at that witty ad-lib.
- He's fast!
While I've been here...
[(Suddenly a mono-documentary)]
- Let's kill him.
- He has something else.
- Let's kill him. / - He's really
the police or doctor this time.
- Yeah, there's something.
- There's something that can look cool
again this time. / - Something is important.
- Something is important. / - He sort of...
[Kekeke]
There's something he can accomplish.
- No!
- But he's not the police.
- Because... / - I was like this
earlier as well, but I wasn't anything.
[I'm in serious mode right now]
I'm just saying this.
Wow, DINO...
Yes, around when I got up...
- Around this time... It's about time he got it.
- DINO... It's time that DINO does it.
I got that feeling.
[It's about time that DINO is mafia now]
- From his eyes.
- But...
Isn't it meaningless to say that
it's about time we do it now?
[But blaming the timing is meaningless]
That's right. It's meaningless.
Since we can't keep twisting it.
- I always died because of that. / - Yeah.
[(Timing victim 1)]
"It's time for WOOZI to do it."
- But it's really time that it's WOOZI.
- What are you talking about!
Always!
- But this time, it's for real.
- But it really is time for you to do it.
It's for real this time.
[(Certain VERNON)]
It's about time!
- Oh! That was sort of convincing.
- It's for real this time.
[Kekekekeke]
- Because it's the last round! / - For real!
[Agrees with VERNON's logical persuasion]
- It's for real this time. / - These idiots!
[(Shakes head)]
But I really think it's SEUNGKWAN.
I want to pick SEUNGKWAN once, too.
[Suddenly cornering in on SEUNGKWAN]
- SEUNGKWAN.
- Yes, let's pick SEUNGKWAN.
[Suddenly cornering in on SEUNGKWAN]
Raise them, everyone!
SEUNGKWAN! Do you have anything to say?
[- SEUNGKWAN's final defense -]
JEONGHAN...
- He wouldn't give me anything. / - But I don't
think he would've picked SEUNGKWAN.
[Reason why SEUNGKWAN is a civilian (?)]
- What do you mean! / - It's really true.
I can relate so much. / - He was upset!
No, I could relate.
- But I don't think it's SEUNGKWAN.
- Just this... That's right.
My gut feeling is...
[HOSHI's gut feeling is]
- It's DINO. / - Let's go with DINO.
[HOSHI's gut feeling is still DINO]
- I pick DINO, too. Really. / - Yeah.
[DK also suspects DINO as mafia]
I also thought he would give me a role,
but I'm just...
Right now, I'm a real civilian.
Everyone... Civilian... They're all that.
[(Sick of this civilian repertoire)]
- Okay! Then kill me! / - Okay. Since we have
to kill anybody in the first round now.
[â¤£ Voluntary tax payment (?)]
- Are we going? / - Kill you?
- Then kill SEUNGKWAN.
- Do you pick DINO or SEUNGKWAN?
[SEUNGKWAN sounds good!]
Then let's kill SEUNGKWAN then.
[SEUNGKWAN sounds good]
Let's kill SEUNGKWAN
- and then kill DINO. / - Okay.
[The next one is DINO]
Killing SEUNGKWAN also sounds good.
1, 2, 3!
What's the meaning of this!
[Unanimously SEUNGKWAN]
An innocent civilian has died.
[Innocent civilian SEUNGKWAN is OUT]
Look down, everyone.
I think it's more fun knowing and watching.
Please wake up and save someone first.
Oh, that's nice.
[Doctor HOSHI]
[Doctor HOSHI â†’ saves DINO]
Police! Please also wake up
and check someone.
[Interesting]
[Time for the police to check for mafia]
Mafia, please wake up and kill someone.
[Mafia also picks after]
Yes, please wake up.
Innocent civilian
HOSHI has died.
[Innocent civilian HOSHI is OUT]
[Kekekekeke]
Why is your energy so high?
- Then who is... / - These 5.
[Currently WOOZI, MINGYU,
DK, VERNON, and DINO are alive]
Did the doctor save anyone?
[Currently WOOZI, MINGYU,
DK, VERNON, and DINO are alive]
- Everyone but the doctor is alive.
- He couldn't save him!
[Currently WOOZI, MINGYU,
DK, VERNON, and DINO are alive]
- Wow! I got a feeling!
- Who is it?
It's VERNON.
[(Strong denial)]
He has denied it strongly.
[Hahaha]
Thinking about this intently is meaningless.
[Reasoning is meaningless with mafia]
You wouldn't be it 3 times, right?
[It wouldn't be MINGYU, right?]
- Seriously not 3 times! Not 3 times.
- Not 3 times, right?
[It wouldn't be MINGYU, right?]
Wow, but it would be amazing if it was WOOZI.
- On the outside, WOOZI sort of looks
like a detective right now. / - His fashion...
His fashion makes him look like a detective.
He's in the violent crimes division.
[WOOZI / District Chief Investigator]
Who are you? Who...
I'm not sure out of the 5 right now.
- Out of those, DINO... / - I see.
[MINGYU is suspicious of DINO]
This guy has a job.
- It's still DINO for me. / - I don't have a job.
[DK was suspicious of DINO from the start]
- Do you not have a job?
- It's still DINO for me.
[DK was suspicious of DINO from the start]
"DINO"?
It doesn't matter if you kill me though.
Then die!
It does matter.
[You have to listen to
what people say until the end]
But I... How should I say this?
It's a good thing to leave a lot of civilians.
- Let's kill DINO first. Let's do it quickly.
- We'll go with DINO. / - Hold on!
Who do you think it is, WOOZI?
I think it's MINGYU, but...
Would he really do it a 3rd time?
- I think it's DK. / - It's really not me.
[Thoughts are all divided]
- That's why I'm torn. / - I really...
Then let's vote.
He also picks DINO.
[(Dibs on DINO)] [(Dibs on DK)]
- It's also DINO for me. / - Okay.
- But... But...
- It's Kim Mingyu.
- It's not me.
- But what he's saying also makes sense.
[The general consensus wavers
from WOOZI's defense]
MINGYU! I think...
[The general consensus wavers
from WOOZI's defense]
I've been thinking hard about it right now.
3 times?!
- Why is it MINGYU? / - So 3 times!
[As mafia]
- The reason why it's 3 times. / - 3 times!
[The reason why MINGYU is mafia 3 times]
- In the beginning, it was just suspicion.
- But if it's JEONGHAN...
[It's possible because
the narrator = JEONGHAN]
- If it's JEONGHAN... / - I was thinking that
it wasn't you because it'd be 3 times,
but just now,
you kept making cornering remarks and
I wondered why you needed to clear that up.
[MINGYU's remark is also suspicious]
You're saying that it's MINGYU, right?
- It's MINGYU for me.
- MINGYU?
Okay. DINO!
For you, is it me?
No!
[Lost his way finding mafia...]
Who is it?
- You want to do something, right?
- It's verified for me. / - It's verified?
- It's verified.
- It's verified?
I feel like we could stick HAACP stickers on you.
[(Granting DICP stickers)]
I...
[Then who will DINO choose?]
- We have to do something.
- Hurry up and go!
I think it's DK or WOOZI.
[(DINO's dibs 1)] [(DINO's dibs 2)]
Hurry up and just pick 1 person.
- Hurry up and decide who to pick! I'm cold.
- Just do 1 person.
Seriously!
I can't play games with you guys!
But WOOZI...
[(Cracks up-)]
It must be so unfair for him.
[(Copies SEUNGKWAN)]
[(I know~ I know it all~)]
Okay! He'll definitely pick DINO.
- For me, it's DINO.
- What about you?
It's DK! This is for real.
Hey! This is for real.
This is DK.
- I guess I'm awkward no matter what I do...
- Okay. Then I pick DK as well.
- Really. This is really DK. / - DK? Okay.
That's more than the majority right right now.
- Hold on.
[Eventually, DK goes on the stand...!]
Does it end if the civilian dies now or
is there another round?
[Current situation] [Mafia 1] [Police 1]
[Doctor 0] [Civilian 3]
- There's 1 more round. / - There's 1 more round.
[Current situation] [Mafia 1] [Police 1]
[Doctor 0] [Civilian 3]
- That's why we're killing you.
- Really? Okay, since there's another round.
[Current situation] [Mafia 1] [Police 1]
[Doctor 0] [Civilian 3]
- 1, 2, 3.
- But I'm seriously a civilian.
A civilian has died.
[Innocent civilian DK is OUT]
I'm sorry.
- Please look down.
- This was sort of my fault.
His fault...
Police! Please wake up and check.
Doctor! Please wake up and save someone.
[Doctor HOSHI is already OUT]
Mafia. Please wake up and kill someone.
[Who is mafia...?!]
- Day has come.
- There are 3 people left.
It's VERNON.
[Innocent civilian VERNON is OUT]
I knew I would die.
Is there no doctor or police right now?
Hold on. There are 3 people left now?
[(Mafia spoiler)]
Seriously!
There are 3 people left?
[Currently WOOZI, MINGYU, and DINO are alive]
- Everyone is acting very well right now.
- That was close.
[Currently WOOZI, MINGYU, and DINO are alive]
- You're acting really well.
- Wow. Hold on.
This round is so fun.
[Getting interesting]
- It's fun. / - This round is so fun!
- Dying early and watching is actually more fun.
[Getting interesting]
This is really fun.
♪ That was close
It's really not me.
[(Mafia candidate 1)]
It's really not me either.
[(Mafia candidate 2)] [(Mafia candidate 3)]
Seriously... Goosebumps.
[Suddenly a horror film]
- Or... But...
- Do you not know who it is?
I really have no idea.
[It's a variety show for the ones who know]
There's that, too.
Very unexpectedly,
it was really WOOZI this time.
[Brings up WOOZI being mafia]
WOOZI has never been mafia.
That could happen...
- But...
- I'm saying that it could happen!
- It's really... / - Since there are only 3 people.
- That could happen!
Everyone really has...
They have their own clear reasons.
[Reasonable reasons for the mafia candidates]
Everyone has their own reasons,
but they're so clear.
[Reasonable reasons for the mafia candidates]
What am I supposed to do?
[(Having the most fun Kekeke)]
You're not playing alone.
We're also here, so you don't have to worry.
Is it you?
Then each person... We're stalling a lot,
so each person will pick.
[Narrator JEONGHAN's speedy process]
Who do you pick, DINO?
Let's go, DINO.
I'll listen first.
[The wizard of pushing and pulling]
It's fun!
- You go first this time.
- Okay, I'll go first this time.
[Kekeke]
What is this?
I'm scared!
- This round is fun.
- I really have no idea!
There's nothing to think about
because you can pick anyone since it's you!
It's not me!
It's really not me!
No, it's you!
[So much fun for those watching]
- Do you really think that? / - Yes.
- No way. / - If WOOZI is mafia,
then he's seriously a jerk.
[He suddenly gets very gullible]
No way. Hold on.
[Unexpected dramatic story]
Why are the two of us just fighting?
If WOOZI is mafia,
then he's seriously a jerk.
The mafia is a jerk.
[That's true]
- The mafia is a jerk. / - It's true.
Your logic is incredible.
Can you hurry up and pick?
- I think it's MINGYU.
- Okay, MINGYU. And WOOZI?
[DINO picks MINGYU]
- MINGYU. / - Then let's hear MINGYU's defense.
[WOOZI also picks MINGYU]
It seriously can't be me.
[Unanimously voted MINGYU's last defense]
It could be you.
[Silent certainty]
I also thought it was you in the beginning.
3 times?
[WOOZI's unsure gut feeling in the beginning]
There's something weird about him.
It's not him.
[WOOZI's unsure gut feeling in the beginning]
That's what I thought.
So I inspected other people.
[(?)]
- But it wasn't.
- As expected! Detective Lee!
- Next time... It's him? / - Oh no!
[Detective Lee Jihoon / Mafia arrest rate 1122%]
I inspected him.
- You're the police?
- Great job!
1, 2, 3!
[Mafia MINGYU has been arrested]
- Mafia has died!
- I actually
thought I would die just now.
[The psychological game between
the policeâ†”mafia played a huge role]
Honestly, I was going to kill WOOZI.
[The psychological game between
the policeâ†”mafia played a huge role]
- I knew I would die.
- I thought it'd be obvious if I killed him.
[The psychological game between
the policeâ†”mafia played a huge role]
I knew I would die.
- Do you know why I picked DK? / - I don't.
[Why VERNON suspected DK as mafia]
When it was mafia's turn,
there was a sound to my right.
[A suspicious sound was
heard during mafia's turn]
That was MINGYU.
I made that sound.
[That culprit who made
that sound was DK Kekeke]
- You made that sound?
- That was me. / - The rustling?
[That culprit who made
that sound was DK Kekeke]
Sensed rustling?
You made sound during mafia's turn?
But that brief rustling gets heard sensitively.
I'm sensitive to it!
It gets heard sensitively.
[Rowdy + very chaotic mafia ends]
Okay! We...
- We had such a good time. / - It was fun.
[Lingering feelings from mafia don't disappear]
- We'll go to the food zone!
- Earlier, SEUNGKWAN also...
[Lingering feelings from mafia don't disappear]
When SEUNGKWAN was the doctor,
I heard his chair move.
DINO...
[Kekekekeke]
I was really scared earlier.
[(Mental breakdown again
when he thinks about it)]
Hey! Then are these members eating?
Let's have a drink!
Sounds good!
Let's go!
Since it's the last day anyway!
- Let's drink tonight! / - Okay!
[(?)]
Let's just go!
You should stop going!
We're going to drink like horses without reins!
[What will happen at the hyper
members' party with late night food?]
Like horses without reins...
[What will happen at the hyper
members' party with late night food?]
♪ IN THE SOOL (alcohol)
[What will happen at the hyper
members' party with late night food?]
Hurry up and make something.
[JEONGHAN is the main chef of tonight's
party with late night food]
What are you going to make?
[JEONGHAN is the main chef of tonight's
party with late night food]
Whatever is in the refrigerator.
[All ingredients in the refrigerator
are on the menu]
- Dumpling stew and... / - Yeah.
[All ingredients in the refrigerator
are on the menu]
[Late night dish 1.
Seafood jjampong dumpling stew]
- Should I just add that much? / - Yes.
[Late night dish 1.
Seafood jjampong dumpling stew]
- Put in more?
- No.
[After putting in all the meal kit ingredients,
it's finished once it's boiled~]
- Should we eat beef? / - Sounds good!
[Late night dish 2. Grilled beef]
You have to cook that medium rare!
[Please make it me(dium) ra(re)]
- Me-ra? / - Yes, then it'll get tougher.
I.G.T?
[I(t) g(ets) t(ougher)?]
Stop shortening!
[Shortening all sorts of things]
Should I just cook it or fry it?
Just cook!
[Cooking to medium rare]
I'll make you something really good!
- What are you going to make?
- You're going to make that, right?
There was also stuff to make tzuran oil.
[Sprinkles tzuran powder to oil]
[Once it's lightly stir-fried, tzuran oil is finished]
[Adding lamb and stir frying one more time]
Fire!
This is it!
- This is it!
- This is it! / - The fiery taste is going in!
[â˜… Performance lamb skewers â˜…]
But you dropped a few!
[Can't resist a few pieces of lamb escaping Kekeke]
- 2. / - 2.
[Adding chives â¤¤]
[Late night dish 3.
Tzuran lamb skewer stir fry]
- I thought of something really good.
- What is it?
Mozzarella, corn! Corn cheese!
[Late night dish 4. Mozzarella, corn! Cheese]
- That sounds great!
- I like it!
I feel like I heard that way of talking before!
Mozzarella, corn!
Corn! Cheese.
Kwon! Soonyoung! Kwon Soonyoung!
[Nostalgic]
[Copying how HOSHI speaks Kekeke]
- It's that way of speaking.
- When we made PPTs before our debut.
On stage, Kwon! On variety shows, Soonyoung!
Kwon Soonyoung!
Kwon Soonyoung.
What is this?
[Surprised by the feast of late night dishes]
What do you mean?
We're going to eat it all together
at the playground.
VERNON! Please take spoons and chopsticks
and go to the playground.
Take more than enough.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4...
[GETs the whole utensil container]
5, 6, 7.
7 people!
That's nice.
You got it down.
[(Utensil fairy)] [(You're pretty good! Ha)]
[Taking the late night dishes
that they made all together]
[The members gather
at the playground one by one]
[A simple party with late night food
on the last night at the forest]
It's amazing.
- It's nice!
- Yeah.
The mood is nice.
- It's cozy and nice here in the playground.
- It's cozy.
The dumplings are really good.
[The food... mood... everything is perfect â˜…]
- Is the dumpling stew good? / - Yes.
[And "cheers" can't be skipped out on~]
- Cheers! / - Cheers!
Oh, nice WOOZI.
[â¤£ Unrivaled one shot]
- But this is also... / - Don't fall for it!
[(Predicting over-drinking to happen)]
But you didn't have to pour it in here.
- Seriously... / - They gave me a glass!
[(Predicting over-drinking of beverages)]
Should I also drink it from this glass?
[Bringing a soju glass]
- Okay. / - But because of the color,
it seems like alcohol.
[(Water that's like alcohol)]
- What is SEUNGKWAN bringing?
Is he cooking ramyeon? / - Menbosha?
Menbosha...
It's so cold. All of this...
[Playground] [(SEUNGKWAN is coming~)]
- You're here, SEUNGKWAN?
- Come and eat! / - Eat!
[SEUNGKWAN joins with menbosha]
How many people do we have right now?
Should I count? 7 people? 8 people?
Count.
Are you asking something hard?
I can count, but I could also ask!
[Only 2/3 of the members are here,
so it's 8 people]
The members today are very diverse.
It's so nice because it's diverse.
We have so many locations!
[SEVENTEEN's music video
caught the eyes of the members]
We did it once in Paju and then
at the department store.
[SEVENTEEN's music video
caught the eyes of the members]
And then...
- But I think the "Left & Right"
music video is decent. / - I like it.
I like the "Left & Right" music video.
[Me too â¤]
- "Left & Right" came out well. / - It was so fun.
This was really funny!
[It's been a while since they've seen
the "Left & Right" music video]
[Source: PLEDIS ENTERTAINMENT]
Things like this are fun.
[It's been a while since they've seen
the "Left & Right" music video]
[Source: PLEDIS ENTERTAINMENT]
DK held in his laughter.
[It's been a while since they've seen
the "Left & Right" music video]
[Source: PLEDIS ENTERTAINMENT]
It was so fun.
- I like when things are planned like this.
- Me too.
[Thanks to this, memories are coming back]
Starting tomorrow, for 2 weeks?
Is it for 3 weeks? We're not going overseas, right?
- We have to practice for the dome tour
for 2 weeks. / - Dome tour practice.
[As of today] [They are preparing
themselves again before the dome tour]
We have to work hard.
[As of today] [They are preparing
themselves again before the dome tour]
- DINO! Please sing us a song.
- Yeah.
Yes, sir!
Since the guys cooked for us,
make it worth their while.
[♬ "Darl+ing" - DINO]
[(Original by: SEVENTEEN /
Lyrics: BUMZU, Lee Jihoon, Bae Sungyeon /
Song: BUMZU, Lee Jihoon, Hwang Hyun)]
He's singing so sincerely!
[Cracks up at sincere DINO Kekeke]
I like it so much.
[(From his face, it looks like a music program)]
How can he make people laugh
with the first line like this?
[CARAT mode]
[(Born to be an idol)]
[(Loves) (it) (so â¤)]
[Taking all 13 members' parts for himself]
[Definite fan service-â˜†]
[- How the youngest can survive
with only having 12 guys older than him -]
[The performance still has
conviction until the end]
[Good job, Lee Chan â¤]
[Even a clean ending >3<]
- You're seriously so good!
- It's nice.
Cheers!
[(The bosses are at part 2 of a company dinner)]
I came here to work at an event.
- That's why he's an idol, right?
- Yeah!
[♬ "RUN" - SEUNGKWAN]
[Original by: BTS] [Lyrics: Pdogg, Bang Sihyuk,
RM, SUGA, V, Jung Kook, j-hope] [Song: Pdogg,
Bang Sihyuk, RM, SUGA, V, Jung Kook, j-hope]
[Flashy footwork]
[♬ "DOPE" - SEUNGKWAN]
[Original by: BTS]
[Lyrics: Pdogg, earattack, Bang Sihyuk, RM,
SUGA, j-hope] [Song: Pdogg, earattack,
Bang Sihyuk, RM, SUGA, j-hope]
[Lethal STEP]
[As service, he sends
dandelion spores flying]
[Once the DOPE (?) karaoke time ends]
[They return to the sleep zone one by one]
[(SEUNGKWAN is going to sleep)]
- WONWOO!
- Huh?
- I love you!
- Me too!
Please tell me you love me, too.
[Today as well, this is the site of
extortion for "I love you"]
I love you.
[Today as well, this is the site of
extortion for "I love you"]
Me too.
You have to tell me you love me, too!
- Aishiteru (I love you).
- Okay.
Daisuki da yo (I like you a lot).
[(MINGYU is also going to sleep)]
Sleep well. Good night!
[The last night darkens like this]
[And the last day approaches brightly]
[The clear sounds of the landscape
that rung in the morning in the forest]
[The sound of the refreshing
river water running]
[Everything will be missed now]
[And the final morning in the forest has come]
[Being able to turn off the alarm]
[Being able to turn off the alarm
and feel the freedom right now]
[Sleeping]
[THE 8 is also ZZZ today]
[Time for them to enjoy]
[sleeping in, which they
won't be able to take for a while]
[The very 1st member to wake up]
[The very 1st member to wake up is JOSHUA]
[â†¶ Checks his face before going out]
[Continuing on from the last season,
JOSHUA wakes up 1st on the last morning]
[Fast steps that naturally head to the food zone]
[JOSHUA, who woke up 1st,
has entered the food zone]
What should I eat?
[Very seriously thinking about the menu]
[Takes out sanitary gloves first]
[Puts the frying pan on the stove right away]
[(+Minced garlic)]
[(+Mozzarella cheese)]
Wow! There's still a ton of meat.
[Prepared all the ingredients]
[What will JOSHUA made for breakfast?]
["JOSHUA's Recipe"]
[1. A huge scoop of minced garlic in oil]
[2. Sprinkle a ton of red pepper flakes]
["JOSHUA's Recipe"]
[3. Add as much meat as you want]
[Stir frying]
["JOSHUA's Recipe"]
[4. Season to taste with black pepper and salt]
[5. Lastly, add cheese]
[Cover the cheese with meat
so that it melts well]
[As the cheese melts in the heat]
[Place bread on a plate]
[Then top the bread with a ton of meat â¤]
[If you add ketchup, mustard,
and red pepper flakes to taste,]
[JOSHUA's version of
a philly cheesesteak sandwich is finished!]
[Presses down the bread]
[Takes a huge bite-]
[While JOSHUA freely enjoys his brunch]
[SEUNGKWAN is running on the treadmill]
[SEUNGKWAN is running on the treadmill
since the morning?!]
[Why is Self-Care Man running so hard?]
[â—€â—€â—€ SEUNGKWAN yesterday]
[Started with the brunch he made himself]
[Shaved ice and pancakes at the cafe]
[Marinated galbi + bibimmyeon
+ pasta for dinner]
[As a late night snack, he had chicken +
menbosha + buffalo wings and more...]
[Yesterday, SEUNGKWAN enjoyed all foods...!]
[He didn't know yesterday...]
[That today would be so tiring...]
Let's go!
[Fighting, yeah]
[The fast and furious sprint that seems
as if it'd destroy all of yesterday's food]
[The one who ate everything yesterday
is running fast and furiously]
[Like that, he did cardio on an empty stomach]
[Exhausted]
[Trembling Bboo]
[Takes hold of his trembling legs]
[Takes hold of his trembling legs
and returns to the sleep zone]
What did you eat for breakfast?
Something like a philly cheesesteak?
I ate something like a sandwich!
It must've been good.
What are you going to eat?
I'm going to eat cereal!
Oh...
Then make me something.
[(I want to eat your cooking)]
Should I make you something? Okay.
What do you want to eat?
Something simple is also fine!
Should I make you a sandwich?
Yes! What you ate is fine, too.
Okay! Then I'll make you what I ate.
I'll put out the ingredients
beforehand this time.
Right away...
- The one I washed is right here.
- Please make it well!
[GETs the pan he used earlier]
- Please make it delicious!
- Okay!
Look forward to it!
Okay!
[WONWOO, who is rapping in the morning,
has entered the food zone]
DK! D DDD DK!
[(Hi DK)] [WONWOO, who is rapping
in the morning, has entered the food zone]
D DDD DK.
Does it take long?
What is it?
He's making me a sandwich.
Make one for WONWOO, too!
- Do you want one as well, WONWOO?
- Okay!
Sounds great.
[â¤]
- Philly cheesesteak.
[(He's serious about their meals)]
[DK is eating cereal because he's hungry â¤¤]
WONWOO!
You also slept for a very long time!
Me? I sleep for a long time.
How many hours do you usually sleep?
16 is a given.
If I sleep at 1 or 2,
I usually wake up at 8,
but I slept so well today.
- That's right. Usually...
- Everyone slept so well at "IN THE SOOP".
[Slept well every night at "IN THE SOOP"]
[Crashing]
Is it going well?
[(Looks very busy)]
It'll turn out well.
Wow! I forgot the most important thing.
What I couldn't do earlier.
[He forgot it earlier]
[He forgot onions earlier!]
[Slicing onions]
[Showing off wrist snaps
while stir frying the meat]
Wow! I succeeded!
Succeeded?
I succeeded!
The heat was too high earlier.
[â—€â—€â—€ Breakfast today]
[Starting to cook after
turning on 2 stovetops]
[He added the meat]
[He added the meat and there was ðŸ”¥]
Wow! Why is it so strong?!
[(The heat)]
[JOSHUA experienced a bit of failure (?)]
I think it needs just a little more.
[The dish became perfect after failure]
After I put this here...
[He plates the bread beautifully]
It's insane.
[As well as the meat with slightly melted cheese!]
This is it!
[As well as the meat with slightly melted cheese!
This is it!]
- Is it this?
- Yes.
And where did I put the tongs?
[Truly a Korean] [An American who sings
when searching for something]
Be careful with your hands.
It looks good!
It's really good.
[#JOSHUA's_very_very_
delicious_brunch_is_finished]
How you finish it so easily...
[#JOSHUA's_very_very_
delicious_brunch_is_finished]
Incredible.
I was a little sad earlier
because I didn't put in onion.
I forgot.
I put onion in this time.
[(Even serves cola)]
Eat it with ketchup!
[Mm!!]
It's good!
[Very_proud_look.mov]
It's so good.
[WONWOO also takes a bite-]
[Entranced sandwich eating]
There's more meat!
Eat it if you want.
Shua! This is so my style.
It's sort of... It's that style.
[The good sandwich shop that
SEVENTEEN's DK is in love with]
- It's savory and good.
- That's right.
That's right. Onions!
[Refills meat]
It's better with ketchup, right?
[Adds ketchup as well]
- WONWOO! Put ketchup on it. / - Put it on?
[(Shares how to eat it well)]
Put ketchup on it.
It's good even if you add it.
[Sees them enjoy it]
I'm proud.
[Sees them enjoy it
and he's 1230 times more proud]
I enjoyed it.
[While WONWOO and DK
enjoy JOSHUA's brunch]
It was quick, right?
[While WONWOO and DK
enjoy JOSHUA's brunch]
[THE 8 is working hard on making something]
Minghao! Nice!
[SEVENTEEN's trait (?): fancy wrist snaps]
Xu Minghao's wok work!
- I think I've improved so much at cooking.
- Yeah.
What are you making, Minghao?
[(Focused)] [What's Minghao making?]
What is it, Minghao?
Stir fried dried tofu.
Please make it delicious.
I really like dried tofu.
Can this taste bad though?
Just in case you cook it wrong.
[Joking around]
Okay.
[Cuts him off without listening]
[(Takes a bite just in case)]
It's so good!
[No point in saying]
It's so good?
I'm already looking forward to it.
- DINO! / - Yo!
[Hungry DINO has entered the food zone]
I'm hungry.
If DINO was here,
I would've made him one right away.
- Toast?
- Yes.
DINO! There's some meat left.
- Put bread around it and eat it.
- DINO! Let's eat together!
Okay! Sounds good.
[Warm] [The eldest guys
each take care of the youngest]
Come here and warm up some rice for us.
[Warm] [The eldest guys
each take care of the youngest]
What?
Warm up some rice.
Okay.
[(Used to it)]
Budaejjigae (sausage stew)?
Budaejjigae, stir fried dried tofu, and...
And tzuran lamb!
Very nice!
[While DINO is warming up instant rice]
[THE 8 starts making the tzuran lamb]
[Next to him, JEONGHAN also
adds ham to the budaejjigae]
Oh, it looks good, Minghao!
Wait! I'll make it delicious for you!
[Adds onion after his big talk]
[Adds onion after his big talk...?]
All of it fell.
[Goodbye to the onions that drop out~]
[Seasoning with various spices]
[Once he stir fries it fancily]
Hey! We're at a good restaurant today.
[A good tzuran lamb restaurant is OPEN]
I'll enjoy the food!
- JEONGHAN! Can I eat first?
- Yes, you can!
[The one who THE 8 called
before the meal]
Yes.
[The one who THE 8 called
before the meal was VERNON]
Eat!
Eat?
Yes.
Okay.
Come quickly!
[(Quickly?)]
[Quickly only takes his hat]
[Goes dressed as a pink sausage]
What are you doing, JEONGHAN?
He's going to grill tofu.
[(JEONGHAN)]
I wanted to eat it.
- Enjoy!
- Okay.
[A full feast]
[These 2 enjoy their meal]
- Yo! / - Yo!
[Pink sausage VERNON
has entered the food zone]
- What's up! / - What are you eating?
[Hungry JUN has also entered the food zone]
It smells nice.
- I should steal food.
- Come quickly.
I'll make rice.
[VERNON, who has taken a seat is]
[Scarfing it down]
VERNON definitely eats
the food I make the best!
He eats so well that I want to feed him.
Is that why
you always call me?
[Why THE 8 also takes care of
VERNON every time they eat]
If I don't call you...
[Why THE 8 also takes care of
VERNON every time they eat]
- You would just eat bread with jam.
- You don't really eat.
I really like everything.
I really like everything you make.
[Very delicious]
[JUN also joins after warming up rice]
What time is it right now?
A lot of the guys are awake!
- What time is it? / - It's 1.
- No, it's late right now.
1:10.
We ate an hour later than usual.
I thought you'd be done eating
when I got the call.
[Another person enjoying THE 8's dish]
[Meat delivery service comes
your way if you're enjoying the food]
We're eating so much at
"IN THE SOOP" this time.
Minghao eats well.
The food I make is to my taste.
[That's how the last lunch in the forest ends]
Let's go drink tea!
Do you want to do a tea ceremony?
Do you want to go drink tea, WONWOO?
- Yes, let's go.
- Let's go do a tea ceremony.
[Tea ceremony family leaves]
♪ In the SOOP, I feel good
We'll do the tea ceremony, meditate,
and clean up the ceremony.
["Today's Agenda"]
What else do we have to do?
We have to go sit on the campgrounds.
["Today's Agenda"]
Jump into the water.
Jump into the water again. For the last time.
["Today's Agenda"]
Or do you want to go up
that mountain? The observatory?
[While the tea ceremony family
goes to the tavern]
No!
[While the tea ceremony family
goes to the tavern]
- What do you think, DK? / - I'll go if you do.
[While the tea ceremony family
goes to the tavern]
Wen Junhui, go!
[JUN was going to work out alone,
but got caught by MINGYU]
[(Let's see)]
[(Eagle eyes)]
1, 2.
[(Press) (ure)]
Are you pressing down right now?
Only at the end!
So it's barely touching.
That's right!
Tighten up here. That's right!
[Master of juicing muscles]
You're good at working out now, too!
That's right!
Help me!
[(Urgent) JUN is dispatched]
1.
2!
Okay.
[Fun time working out together ends]
I have to take this.
[â¤¦ Personal archery equipment]
But I did it once!
No, twice!
When you guys were playing foot volleyball,
I also did it at night.
It's nice because we have more time than usual.
We always have to squeeze
time in our schedules to do it.
[They could completely relax
and enjoy life freely in the forest]
- That's right. / - We can just freely
[They could completely relax
and enjoy life freely in the forest]
do things whenever we want to.
I worked out really hard. We got our
money's worth of what they installed here.
[(The strength zone)]
I'll go pack up first.
[24-hour hot place]
[The strength zone is closed]
[Meanwhile, what about the other members?]
[HOSHI and SEUNGKWAN are eating late]
[JOSHUA is ZZZing on
his favorite sofa in the playground]
[S.COUPS and WOOZI are still
enjoying their trip through dreamland]
[Their last break looking up at the sky]
Shall we meditate until this boils?
And feel the wind.
And don't open your eyes.
[With eyes closed]
And feel your breathing.
[The members follow THE 8
and focus on meditating]
[Facing the sunlight
shining through the branches]
[And feeling the gentle breeze blowing]
[Let's focus on the sound of nature]
[The standard of meditation]
[(They might be at
an intermediate level of meditation)]
[And]
[And...?]
[WONWOO decided to capture things
with his eyes instead of meditating]
[He is fully capturing the forest landscape]
[and blue skies that will be
remembered for a long time]
[(I'm going to open my eyes as well)]
[Gathering the energy of nature and stretching]
[THE 8 opens his eyes last]
[WONWOO is sad to let all this go,
so he captures the landscape in photos]
Oh, it's warm.
[(THE 8 is starting to prepare
the tea ceremony now)]
[They're watching THE 8 do that]
[Soul 0g]
[Empty eyes of the 3 brothers]
What does "IN THE SOOP" mean to JEONGHAN?
[Sudden interview] [Q.]
"IN THE SOOP" is...
- ...lingering feelings.
- Lingering feelings.
- Foolish guy.
- Why is it lingering feelings?
I become foolish when I come here.
["IN THE SOOP"]
I get endlessly comfortable.
I become foolish.
[(?)]
Can't we drink it now?
It's not boiling.
[á…á…á… 30 seconds later á…á…á…]
- Is it still not boiling? / - Yes.
[(What about now?)]
It makes a sound when it boils.
Like this.
[Right then, the water starts boiling Kekeke]
- There's caffeine even in black tea, right?
- Yes.
There's a little bit.
[THE 8 pours warm tea in their cups]
Minghao. Why are you drinking from a big cup?
- The owner's cup is supposed to be different.
- Oh, is that so?
- Why does the owner's cup
have to be different? / - Because...
[So curious]
The owner brews it!
[(The tea)]
- Are tea ceremonies a little prejudiced...
- It's not prejudice.
[Joking ON]
Isn't it prejudice?
Only the owner drinks from the big cup.
[Kekekekeke)]
Then...
If you were it, then you'd be given a different cup.
[(The owner)]
It depends on who's doing it?
- It's their own style.
- It's sort of an authoritative hobby.
[(Having fun teasing THE 8)]
It's a style thing, but... This is my style.
[Stop joking]
- Oh, it's not normally like this?
- It's not like that?
It's normally not the same one.
This is just a comfortable set.
So they're the same cups.
If we went to a real tea ceremony shop,
the owner would give you cups
that match you well.
[They normally pick cups that suit each person]
There's something like that!
Something different from the owner.
An authoritative hobby.
They can be different.
The owner thinks "This cup suits you"
and gives that to you.
Everyone has a different vibe.
[(Each person)]
[Swoosh]
Can you not do it up to here?
Like this, Minghao.
[Typical rejection]
[Accepts his request]
[Quickly gives up Kekeke]
The black tea is also good, right?
Yes.
[(Nods)]
[(I want to try it, too)]
It's clean.
Oh! There's a bird!
[Glad]
It left...
Oh! It's so nice.
You're all done, right?
[Finishing their time with a cup of warm tea]
Shall we go now?
Minghao! Where are you going?
[THE 8 â¤¥]
Let me put down my stuff.
He wants to be alone.
Where are you going now?
[Jjong] [Jjong]
Hold on! Let's rest for a bit.
[Jjong] [Jjong] [Jjong]
Why do you like resting so much, DK?
Because we came here to rest!
[Filled with warmth]
[The tavern is closed]
Go meditate over there. On top of that tree.
[Filled with warmth]
[The tavern is closed]
I want to stop meditating.
[Filled with warmth]
[The tavern is closed]
Hello? Yes.
Yes.
[Who is he talking to?]
Someone is drunk here...
Someone is drunk and sleeping on the street.
[Obsessed with scenarios]
[(Sniffle)]
Yes, this is Andong...
- Are you the driver? / - No.
[Surprised DINO]
You're so drunk, sir!
[^^]
How do you feel? It's the end.
[Scenario has ended]
When I think about leaving,
it makes me want to stay just one more day.
That's right.
Just one more day.
Just one more day now that we're going.
[A little bummed to leave]
What is everyone doing?
Let's go!
Let's go home!
[With the warm sunlight]
[And the gently flowing streams]
[The picturesque high and
clear skies are behind them]
[And the members are ready to go]
[As they each pack their bags]
[Checking if they left anything
behind one more time]
Everyone is slowly packing their bags.
[(Crashing)]
[Looks like us when
we pack our suitcases Kekeke]
[The members gather one by one
in the living after cleaning up]
It's nice if we take it.
[The members gather one by one
in the living after cleaning up]
- Look at how the leaves are changing color!
- Where?
This? The red?
[The green mountaintops have changed to red]
Be well, forest!
Forest!
[JEONGHAN and HOSHI
are relaxing in front of the food zone]
- I heard I snored in my sleep yesterday.
- Really?
- On the bottom? When you took a nap?
- At lunchtime. Yes.
[The schedule following
JEONGHAN was pretty tiring for HOSHI]
[Also spending the last moments
in the forest together]
[It's really time to leave now]
[Refer to episode 1]
[Like a dejavu, VERNON comes out first]
[One by one, they come out of the sleep zone]
[And gather in the playground]
Let's go, bro!
[Clings on]
We're leaving!
Did you rest well here?
Yes!
I rested really well.
I rested so much.
I rest so much!
- It was nice. / - For me too!
[â¤]
- JEONGHAN?
- Yes?
Your hat.
[※ Looking for JEONGHAN who lost his hat ※]
Where was it?
The 2nd floor.
I thought you were leaving it.
[Always happens when packing on trips]
[Definitely checked, but leaves the hat]
That surprised me.
[Always happens when packing on trips]
[Definitely checked, but leaves the hat]
[Once WOOZI also enters the playground lastly]
Guys! How was it for you all?
HOSHI! Your face looks good.
I just slept so well.
[(Proof he slept well in the forest)]
I feel like I definitely rested well
during the 5 days.
- I talked a lot with the members, too.
- We rested so well.
- That's right. We rested so well.
- We rested really well.
[(Very satisfied)]
- We ate a lot of good food, too.
- We worked out well here, too.
If we happen to go to "IN THE SOOP 3",
stick with me, HOSHI!
You 2 should be roommates!
[(Looks away)]
Let's try a lot of things, HOSHI!
- Okay.
It was sort of like a forced break, right?
[Looking back on the 5 days
that seemed like a forced break]
A forced break.
[Looking back on the 5 days
that seemed like a forced break]
It was a break with reason.
The weather was pretty chilly,
- so having a campfire was my favorite.
- When we zoned out into the fire.
[The fire pit where they
could melt their bodies]
It makes you all emotional.
[(It was so nice)]
- We also played mafia.
- Even mafia...
It's been so long.
[Mafia was better because it's been so long]
You drank a bottle of whisky
in front of the campfire!
[Mafia was better because it's been so long]
You always drink alcohol!
You drink it everyday.
- In the SOOL (alcohol). / - In the SOOL.
- ♪ In the SOOL
[Real "IN THE SOOL", MINGYU]
For the first time in a while,
I didn't drink alcohol yesterday.
- Yesterday... / - You drank yesterday.
- It's not that I didn't drink.
[?????]
[Can feel the hot glares from the members]
I drank a little bit.
[Adjusts right away]
- He drank a little bit.
- I was so refreshed in the morning.
[A refreshing morning thanks to drinking less]
- I think it was over here.
- ♪ Why are you lying?
Thank you so much for
playing volleyball with me.
- Volleyball was so fun. / - Volleyball was fun.
[Can't forget the memory of playing
bouncy ball volleyball, which was nostalgic]
Foot volleyball was also fun.
[Can't forget the memory of playing
bouncy ball volleyball, which was nostalgic]
When the broadcast comes out,
we'll think, "Yes, that's what we did then."
Let's come once more next year!
We can watch on the broadcast
how we each spent our time.
[Can check what everyone did on the broadcast!]
- Yes.
- That's right.
[Can check what everyone did on the broadcast!]
- Since everyone rested well...
- Our nostalgic photos! There!
- Let's look at the photos and go out.
- Let's go.
We also have schedules tomorrow.
[Returning to their original jobs tomorrow]
- Let's go practice well for the dome tour now.
- Great job! / - Yes.
What is this?
They even prepared marbles.
MINGYU.
READY TO TIME OFF.
[On one side of the table]
I want to take one of these!
- Take it! / - Take it!
["IN THE SOOP" limited edition
marbles only for SEVENTEEN]
It says our names, too. READY TO TIME OFF.
["IN THE SOOP" limited edition
marbles only for SEVENTEEN]
- READY TO TIME OFF.
- TIME OFF.
It's ours this time.
[And the walls are filled]
It was TIME OFF.
[Photos are posted all over]
It's nice.
- Were the motorcycles really fun? / - Yes.
[Photos are posted all over]
In 5 days,
we've made memories like this.
Yeah.
- It was so nice.
- Yeah.
[With memories from "IN THE SOOP"
during the last 4 nights and 5 days]
[Our time that was full]
SEUNGKWAN's pose
[Looking back on fun 5 days together]
would come out on SEUNGKWAN's Ins*agram.
That's true.
[Looking back on fun 5 days together]
It came out well.
This is really... This is too bad.
I wanted to try this.
[Samgyeopsal on a caldron lid]
- It was really good. / - It was really good.
[(Only those who ate the samgyeopsal
on a caldron lid can say this)]
That was really amazing.
[(Only those who ate the samgyeopsal
on a caldron lid can say this)]
We ate hot pot with samgyeopsal.
[(Only those who ate the samgyeopsal
on a caldron lid can say this)]
- That was seriously insane. / - Really?
[(Only those who ate the samgyeopsal
on a caldron lid can say this)]
Are you riding a motorcycle
when we go home, WONWOO?
Yes, that's right. Bye! Ride it and go.
That would be so great then.
VERNON... Where's VERNON?
[When the eldest S.COUPS takes a marble]
Right after you...
I'm also taking JEONGHAN.
[Everyone takes the token of a perfect break]
The one on the bottom.
It feels like I'm taking a dragonball or something.
[Everyone takes the token of a perfect break]
It's very heavy.
Can we make a wish
when the 13 balls are brought together?
- It's cool. / - MINGYU! You can't drop it!
[The members leave the playground]
I think you'd be good at things like that.
[Time to leave the forest now]
Resting is really great,
[The worries they have
before coming to the forest]
but I was worried that we would really struggle
[The worries they have
before coming to the forest]
once we went.
[The worries they have
before coming to the forest]
But they disappeared within a day.
To me, "IN THE SOOP" is
[Q. What does "IN THE SOOP"
mean to SEVENTEEN?]
a good reason for me to rest.
But that doesn't mean that
I hid myself and couldn't rest.
It's such a great reason.
I think it would be that.
In the midst of being busy,
the members are all together in one place
[In the midst of a busy tour,
they are in the same place together]
and we can laugh, chat, and sleep together.
I'm so happy that we even have time to do that.
I think it was one of the few moments
where I could be at peace.
It was nice when I could zone out into the fire.
[Even zoning out into the fire
in front of the warm campfire]
It was nice being at the campgrounds, too.
[Even zoning out into the fire
in front of the warm campfire]
Mountain climbing was also nice.
[Campgrounds, mountain climbing,
survival game] [Everything in the forest was nice]
The survival game was also fun.
[Campgrounds, mountain climbing,
survival game] [Everything in the forest was nice]
I think I can go back and work hard again now.
[The break gave him strength to work hard again]
If we go to "IN THE SOOP 3",
I think I can rest again.
Since we're normally so busy,
we didn't have time to converse.
But through "IN THE SOOP" here,
I could converse a lot with
the members, so it was nice.
[Precious memories of talking with the members]
There were so many nice things!
We could come in the morning,
do something, eat, and rest.
[They could freely enjoy their time
without any set agenda]
Then we could come at night,
do something, and eat again. This was nice.
[They could freely enjoy their time
without any set agenda]
It was a forced break.
Nobody wakes us up and we can just sleep.
[Without worrying about alarms
and schedules, sleeping in was enjoyed
for the first time in a while]
That was really nice. And...
[Without worrying about alarms
and schedules, sleeping in was enjoyed
for the first time in a while]
I think I rested well enough.
Once we go back,
I think I can prepare well
for the dome tour now.
What I always feel at "IN THE SOOP" is
that while being in SEVENTEEN,
[The assembly of all breaks
he can have with SEVENTEEN]
I can experience all sorts of breaks.
[The assembly of all breaks
he can have with SEVENTEEN]
So...
[The assembly of all breaks
he can have with SEVENTEEN]
I definitely think it's a healing point.
[Definitely] [SEVENTEEN's "IN THE SOOP 2"]
A brief break in the middle
of a very long project.
It's a relief that I have the members.
[That we came to the forest together]
When else would I come to a place like this?
Honestly, at "IN THE SOOP"
[A time only filled with laughter
while briefly escaping their daily lives]
while we rest briefly,
[A time only filled with laughter
while briefly escaping their daily lives]
we also laughed and had fun.
[A time only filled with laughter
while briefly escaping their daily lives]
I could converse with the members
while riding on canoes and that was amazing.
And it was so nice working out
with the members, too.
Even having tea ceremonies with the guys...
[Even the tea ceremonies in nature]
We could converse and be in the wind
and hear the sounds of the cups.
[Even the tea ceremonies in nature,
every moment brought healing]
It brought a lot of healing.
Whether it was mentally or physically,
[("IN THE SOOP")]
it was a schedule that
gave us strength in both ways.
Even in a whole year of schedules,
it's my favorite schedule
that goes in the top 3 in my book.
It was so fun in the sauna, too.
When we were in the spa,
it felt like we were at a bathhouse
with the members for the first time in a while,
so that was nice.
After the spa,
it was cold when we ran back home.
[A memorable moment that
will be remembered as a scene of youth]
We held onto our own padded jackets and ran.
[A memorable moment that
will be remembered as a scene of youth]
That was sort of like our youth.
[A memorable moment that
will be remembered as a scene of youth]
When else could we spend
4 nights and 5 days
and just eat, lie down,
[Very much]
and rest like crazy?
After "IN THE SOOP",
I also want to do "IN THE SEA" and
go in front of the beach.
[â¤]
We can play with sandcastles in front of
the beach and go swimming. It sounds fun.
It was a space where we made
lots of good memories,
so I think I'll miss it a lot
and it'll come to mind very much.
To me, "IN THE SOOP"
is a space where I can be cleansed.
[Could cleanse his body and heart
at "IN THE SOOP"]
I love you!
To me, "IN THE SOOP" is
a place I need to go once a year.
Actually, I didn't know these 4 nights
and 5 days would pass by so quickly.
I think it sort of feels like a resting place now.
[A resting place he wants to come to
when he's struggling]
I also had a lot of time to think.
[(In the forest)]
I think I'm okay because I'm a bit refreshed.
"IN THE SOOP 2" was snow in a storm.
[To VERNON]
In the middle of a storm,
it's actually the most silent, right?
I think this place is sort of like that.
[A silent time in the forest]
Once we leave this place, we'll probably
get swept away by the storm again.
Something I always feel
when I come to "IN THE SOOP"
is that it comes to mind so much in the dorms!
[(In the space shared by all 13 members)]
It's so nice when all 13 people are together.
[Just happy being with the members]
If it's not now,
I really don't think it'll come back.
[The precious moments with the 13]
I normally don't take many photos,
but I took photos of the members
and watched them a lot.
[And he captured the members with his eyes]
Their faces...
But since we're the only ones here,
[In the forest]
we were just able to focus on one another.
- Bye, "IN THE SOOP"!
- Bye!
- We'll be back!
Thank you!
Say a word, HOSHI!
It was fun!
- It was fun!
"IN THE SOOP".
[Happier with the 13]
Bye!
[Forced break of 4 nights and 5 days]
JEONGHAN!
You should've fished here.
["IN THE SOOP" SEVENTEEN Season 2]
[- THE END -]
No. It's pretty hard to catch them.
["IN THE SOOP" SEVENTEEN Season 2]
[- THE END -]
♪ Though we're tired and exhausted
We just keep on walkin'
♪ But our feet hurt
That's why we're here to rest
♪ How about some pajeon by the stream?
How about working out twice a day?
♪ How about we fly in the sky?
Or zone out into the fire
while you lean on me?
♪ Baby, it's okay to sleep in
as long as we're here
♪ It's okay even if it rains,
we have an umbrella
♪ In the SOOP, I feel good
♪ Let's take a breather
♪ Yes, this is the place
♪ You can let the weight on your shoulders
down for a moment
♪ Let's leave right now
♪ (I'm saying, let's go there) In the SOOP
♪ SOOP du ru du du ru du
(Yes, let's go there)
♪ SEVENTEEN is In the SOOP
Soldiers!
We are almost at the enemy camp!
Are you ready?!
- Yes! / - Yes!
[The soldiers' responses that lack confidence]
Once we're there, we have one goal!
Fighting and winning!
I hope you all keep that
in mind and arrive safely.
["IN THE SOOP" ver.]
[- Shoot me and go -]